Oops! Sorry, Princess Twilight!
That was meant for her!
INCOMING!
Whoa!
Toola Roola! Coconut Cream!
What are you doing?
That was meant for
my ex-friend!
I'm not your ex-friend!
You're my ex-friend!
Both of you, stop!
So you see, friendship
isn't always easy
but there's no doubt
it's worth fighting for.
Awwww!
Hmm. That sounds familiar.
Hmmm. No. Uh uh.
Aha! Here it is!
What is that?
Come on, Starlight.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
This is the friendship journal
my friends and I used to keep.
It's filled with all the
things we've learned!
Like... "friendship
isn't always easy
but there's no doubt it's
worth fighting for."
I'll.. judge a book by its
cover just this once.
Thanks for coming, everypony!
I've got a surprise for you...
What is it, Twilight? Do I
need to prepare myself?
It's this!
Oh! What is that thing?
Why is it so smelly!
Wait a minute!
[gasp] Is this our old
friendship journal?
I haven't seen this
thing in forever!
Hooo-wee, it's lookin' a
little uh, overripe.
I'll say!
There's a smooshed apple
in Applejack's lessons.
Fluttershy's lessons are so
small, you can barely read them.
I.. uh.. wanted to leave
room for all of you.
I-I don't even
know what this is.
It is called
calligraphy, darling.
If you're going to make words,
at least make them fabulous.
Looks like you got a
little aggressive
with your friendship
lessons, Rainbow Dash.
What can I say?
When I learn something,
I learn it hard.
I found Pinkie's page.
Hee hee! Well, I
am surprised!
That wasn't
the only surprise..
♪ Ta da! ♪
Starlight and I decided to
make one for each of you!
That's amazin'!
A perfect copy!
I learned the spell years ago
when I needed to make copies
of a certain...
...manifesto.
Ah! Even better than
a perfect copy.
Oh, I'd forgotten all
about this lesson.
Ha ha! Remember this one?
From when I helped Daring Do?
"Never underestimate
the power of friends
who've always got your back."
Aww, Cheese Sandwich!
Party cannon!
Ah! Birthaversary!
After Twilight
remembered the journal,
I had so much fun reading all
the stuff you've all learned.
I just had to have
my own copy.
And that brings me to the
second part of the surprise.
My idea.
How would you girls feel
about making our journal
available for everypony?
If we can get these lessons
into other ponies' hooves,
maybe they'll benefit from them.
Well, I think
that's a great idea.
I'm in! YAY!
We always said we wanted to.
Sounds fabulous.
Hahaha, I'm awesome.
Oh, yeah, uh, good idea.
Toola Roola: No! I don't want to
play with you anymore!
Why not? You love
playing hopscotch.
No, you do. Because
you always win!
Twilight: Hey, girls.
Couldn't help but overhear...
You might want to
take a breather,
maybe read Rainbow Dash's
chapter on Rainbow Falls.
It might help.
Sure, Princess.
Apple Bloom: Thanks, Twilight!
The friendship journal's
makin' us super popular!
Oh...
We were thinkin' of
putting together
a Cutie Mark Summer Camp.
Now everypony's definitely
gonna sign up for it!
This is going to be awesome! Heh heh.
A Cutie Mark Camp
is a great idea.
Yeah, but the purpose
of the journal
isn't supposed to
be marketing.
I just hope those foals
actually learn something
from our lessons.
They will. I'm sure ponies all
across Equestria will--woah!
Uh, hello.
Can I... help you?
We're here all the way
from Fillydelphia
because we got copies of
your friendship journal.
Wow! How wonderful.
What was your favorite
friendship--
Will you sign them?
Oh. Uh, I guess so.
So, what did you
think of the lessons?
Oh, we haven't read them.
These are keepsakes.
We gotta keep them
in mint condition. Heh.
Oh.
Wow, that was worth the trip!
Don't worry, Twilight, I'm
sure lots of other ponies
are being inspired to
be better friends.
Well, I for one found the
journal terribly illuminating.
Ah!
I agree.
I'm seeing sides of these
ponies I didn't know were there.
I only wish they'd
left Rarity out.
She clearly doesn't belong in
that book with the rest of them.
Oh, I know!
Who does she think she is?
Certainly she did a
fine job setting up the
Ponyville Days Celebration,
but does she really
believe it was a success
just because of her?
Ha ha ha!
The nerve!
But that's not what
she was saying!
Rarity!
Oh. Poor Rarity.
She overheard all the mean
things those ponies were saying!
She must be devastated.
I'm going after her.
Go ahead.
I'm going to have a
chat with these two.
Rarity, wait!
Agh!
Twilight, isn't it amazing?
Our journals are everywhere!
Pinkie! I've got to--
Ponies keep stopping
by to tell me
my entries are hilarious!
I even had somepony come all
the way from Las Pegasus
to say how much he
liked my lessons!
I am so glad to hear
someponies are being inspired
by the journal!
Hey look! There's Pinkie
Pie, the funny one!
Giggly feedback
is the best kind!
Well, at least you're
getting a positive reaction.
I just saw Rarity.
I'm afraid this whole journal
thing really upset her.
Aww. That's too bad.
Wait, that wasn't
even funny.
OK. Well, I guess
I'll catch you later.
Yup. Bye, Twilight.
Ha! Classic Pinkie!
Oh! She's even funnier
in real life!
You've known
me for years!
Rainbow Dash: Maybe it's
time to call it a day.
I ripped out all the Twilight
Sparkle lessons
'cause they were getting in
the way of the good ones!
What do you mean you
skipped the lessons?
We've all had
valuable experiences!
Hey, here's a great idea!
Why don't you guys talk to
Twilight for a while
so I can get back to things
like working and napping and...
well, pretty much anything else.
Aw, we don't want to
hear her boring lessons!
Come on, tell us again about
when you met Daring Do!
Heh heh. Again?
Haven't we already
covered that one?
A couple dozen times?
We can't get enough of it!
Come on, you don't want
to disappoint your fans!
Uh.. It's just that I, uh,
really need to get those
stormclouds back
in their.... pens.
Cool! We'll come along and you
can tell us the story there!
Rainbow Dash! Rainbow Dash!
Rainbow Dash!
Oooh..
What's going on now?
Please! Just leave me alone!
Fluttershy? What's wrong?
We want answers!
Yeah! We're
entitled to know!
What is it, everypony?
We want to know why
Fluttershy keeps learning
the same thing over
and over again.
Be assertive, already.
Even I've learned
more than she has!
Why can't I be in the book?
What? Really? Are you
attacking my friend
because you want
to be in a book?
It's OK. I've
got this, girls.
Listen up! I am
more assertive.
And yes, it took me
a while to get there.
But can you honestly say that
you could learn something
one time and completely
change who you are?
I didn't think so!
Wow. You're way different from
the Fluttershy in the book.
I don't know how
I feel about that.
It feels like
everypony in Equestria
is missing the friendship part
of the friendship journals.
Rarity? Are you all right?
Gah!
What are you doing?
Why I'm creating
a gown, darling!
For what?
I don't know!
I'm stress-sewing!
Stress-sewing?
When I overheard those
two at the cafe,
I suddenly understood why
I've been getting
cancellations for days!
What? Why are ponies
cancelling their orders?
Because.. nopony
likes me anymore!
They're boycotting me!
I'm sure if I go out there
and talk to those ponies,
they'll see that they're
being unreasonable.
I need a hundred blankets
and I need 'em now!
Sorry, Twilight.
Right away, Pony
who still likes me!
I don't need nothin' fancy.
What's the matter, Applejack?
I'm popular, Twilight!
I'm popular and I
don't like it one bit!
You go ahead, I'll stay here.
Applejack, who are
all these ponies?
They call themselves "the
Sweet Apple Admirers."
They say they read
my journal entries
and they felt like a
part of the family.
And now they want to actually
become part of the family!
Your journal entries?
Yeah, you know, all the stuff
about how friends are like
family and whatnot.
Can't you get rid of them?
And kick out my own family?
Granny Smith!
Hang on, let me help!
There she is!
YEEEEEE-HAAWWWW!
Oh. I wish we'd never
released that journal.
There you are.
OK. I just left Rarity; I
think she's doing better and-
Oh, boy.
Window staring, huh?
Was it that bad at
Sweet Apple Acres?
It's bad everywhere.
I thought I was
doing something good.
I thought I was helping.
How could our friendship
journal have led to so much...
anti-friendship!?
Oh, Twilight, it's
not your fault.
Of course it's my fault!
If I hadn't had the big
idea to make copies,
none of this would
be happening!
I'm afraid I made life
awful for my friends.
I really think you're
being too hard on yourself.
Am I?
Wah!
I didn't know where else to go.
I've got so much cookin' and
cleanin' and familyin' to do,
I ain't got time
for anything else!
At least ponies aren't
laughing every time you talk!
Not even I want to be
funny all the time!
I'm telling you, my days
of hilariosityness... ness...
are OVER.
You think you've got problems?
I know I'm awesome but I can't
even go to the bathroom
without somepony trying to
tell me how cool I am.
Uh...Rarity, what
are you wearing?
My emotions, darling!
Stress couture!
I don't know what I'm going to
do if I have to defend myself
one more time!
Oh. Er.. sorry, Darling.
Force of habit.
OK, so maybe they are
having a hard time with it.
That doesn't mean you
did anything wrong.
Yes, I did!
Releasing the
journal was my idea
and it backfired in ways I
could never have imagined.
It's not your fault.
It's everypony else's!
They're just focusing
on the wrong things and-
Wait here!
I've got an idea!
I can't wait any longer.
I've got to fix this.
Everypony, please stop!
Princess Twilight?
I'm with the Canterlot
Chronicle, quick question...
What would you say to ponies
who wonder why you moved
to Ponyville in the first place?
I moved here to learn
about friendship.
That's why the
journal even exists.
It took some time for me
to get the hang of it,
but it was each of these
ponies standing next to me
who taught me the lessons
in those journals.
Applejack.
Pinkie Pie.
Rainbow Dash.
Rarity.
And Fluttershy, too.
Then it was all of you.
I've learned so much
from--
What I mean is, some
ponies would argue that
it doesn't seem believable that
the six of you would be friends.
Believable?
Well, sure.
I read this journal cover
to cover and I have to say,
your character would have
been much more interesting
if she'd stayed in Canterlot.
My character!?
We are real ponies.
This journal is a
record of things
that actually
happened to us.
We made mistakes and
we learned from them.
What about Rarity?
Are we really supposed to
believe she learned anything
she wrote in there?
That's why you
gotta be Team Dash!
She's the only one who didn't
really need to learn anything
because she was already so cool!
Twilight was better
before she got wings.
Fluttershy is just
so painfully shy,
it's hard to relate.
I mean, come on!
Wait a minute, everypony!
Are Pinkie Pie and
Applejack related or what?
Listen to me!
LISTEN TO ME!
♪ I never claimed to
be perfect ♪
♪ My mistakes are all
written in ink ♪
♪ None of us claimed
to be perfect ♪
♪ And it's sad that's
what you all think. ♪
♪ Our flaws help to make
us special ♪
♪ They bond us and
keep us strong ♪
♪ Our flaws are what
brought us together ♪
♪ So stop acting like
something's wrong. ♪
♪ We're not flawless
We're work in progress ♪
♪ We've got dents and
we've got quirks ♪
♪ But it's our flaws that
make us work, yeah ♪
♪ We're not flawless
We're work in progress ♪
♪ So tell me what flaws
you've got, too ♪
♪ cause I still like
what's flawed about you. ♪
♪ They say I'm a big shot ♪
♪ That my ego's the
size of a whale ♪
♪ My confidence comes off
as cocky ♪
♪ But it gives me the
courage to fail. ♪
♪ Sure I can be a drama queen
A bit stuck up, it's true ♪
♪ And I can be too
eager to please ♪
♪ There's such thing as being
too honest too cause... ♪
♪ We're not flawless
We're work in progress ♪
♪ We've got dents and
we've got quirks ♪
♪ But it's our flaws that
make us work, yeah ♪
♪ We're not flawless
We're work in progress ♪
♪ So tell me what
flaws you got too ♪
♪ cause I still like what's
flawed about you. ♪
♪ Ponies think I'm all
bubbles and laughter ♪
♪ That I don't seem sincere ♪
♪ I might joke around a
little too much ♪
♪ But I'm just so
happy you're here. ♪
♪ It took me a while
to be confident ♪
♪ To really come out
of my shell ♪
♪ But no pony has
to be perfect ♪
♪ By now don't you know us
so well because, yeah ♪
♪ We're not flawless
We're work in progress ♪
♪ We've got dents and
we've got quirks ♪
♪ But it's our flaws that
make us work yeah ♪
♪ We're not flawless
We're work in progress ♪
♪ So tell me what
flaws you got too ♪
♪ Cause I still like
what's flawed about you. ♪
So you see, everypony?
None of us ever
claimed to be perfect.
Without our flaws,
there wouldn't be any
friendship lessons to learn.
Without our flaws...
... there probably wouldn't
be any friendships at all.
So that just
happened.
Girls! I found two ponies
who have something
I think you should hear.
Um... we just wanted to say
thank you to all of you.
Yeah. Our friendship...
well, we were having trouble
until we read your journal.
It showed us that friends can go
through all sorts of tough times
and come through
stronger than before.
It's made us better friends
than we've ever been.
Really?
Mm-hm.
Oh, I can't tell you how
much it means to hear that.
Thank you for telling us.
We've had a tough
couple of days.
But knowing we've helped
fillies like you...
It makes everything we've
been through worth it.
Absolutely.
Fads come and go;
friendship is forever.
There are worse things than
not being able to do anything
without being told I'm awesome.
And we can't change the way
other ponies think about us,
but we can change how
we let it affect us.
Or how we don't
let it affect us.
Heh. Heh. Go ahead. Laugh!
Reckon we still have to
deal with them, don't we?
Stay in the friendship
moment, Applejack.
They can wait a little longer.