[hissing]
Mm hm.
[hiss]
Oh!
Antoine believes what
he eats is his business.
Do other predators
feel that way, too?
Would any prey
like to respond?
Muriel? Does it bother you
when Antoine tries to eat you?
Just because you're
on opposite ends
of the food chain doesn't
mean you can't work toge--
It doesn't mean you can't--
Ahem!
It doesn't mean you
can't work togeth--
Oh! I'm sorry, but the
more you distract everyone,
the longer this will take.
I AM listening to you, but if
you really want to be heard,
you should join our
Predator-Prey-Support Group.
Then you could talk
to everyone here.
You could teach all
these hungry predators
the delights of a
carrot-based cuisine.
Sorry, everyone.
I think somebunny just
wants a little attention.
Now, since we all
need to get along,
what if all Predators promised
to only eat vegetables
while staying at
the Sanctuary?
Oh, Sandra.
You can do it!
♪♪
[gasp] Angel! Sandra! Wait!
Hm. It might look like chaos,
but Fluttershy makes it work,
even with Angel running around.
Oooh. Perhaps I can help
those two get along,
before something here
can go terribly wrong.
♪♪
Zecora found this little guy
and brought him to my office,
but I thought he might do
better at the sanctuary.
♪♪
Bringing him here seemed
the right thing to do.
I've never seen geckos breathe
smoke, though, have you?
Oh! I certainly haven't!
I thought we could take
a look at his diet,
plus it's about
time for me
to give all the animals
here a check up.
That's a wonderful idea.
If we really want to
know what's going on,
we need to make sure the
problem isn't your food.
I wouldn't worry too much.
It's probably just
something he's been eating.
Oh, um! Is there anything
else we can do for you?
Ahh! Seeing what
you two do,
the real question
is: "Can I help YOU?"
You mean... me and Angel?
Mm hm.
Oh, he's fine!
We're fine... I-
I just don't always have
time to indulge him.
But we're best friends.
Even the best of friends
need help from time to time.
Come visit me in my hut,
should you change your mind.
OK, thanks! But Angel
and I are great!
Ah! Goodness,
Fluttershy!
Is this the list of
what you do every day!?
How do you find time
for anything else?
Between here and teaching at
the school, I'm not sure I do.
You're going to love
it here, little gecko.
What is it? Not
fluffy enough?
Oh, I'm sorry.
We need to see if your
food is causing your issue.
Huh?!
Mm. Not now, Angel.
They're snake treats
made to look like
chocolate chip cookies!
They're vegan!
Pinkie Pie made a
whole jar of them.
They're all yours
if you promise....
No more trying to eat
Muriel the Baby Elephant.
♪♪
Ah!
No, Angel. I have
too much to do.
Oh! Careful, girl. That neck
is still pretty sore.
Don't forget to shift
your weight, Scout.
What does she want?
Her neck is feeling better,
but a massage every day
for the next week wouldn't
hurt. I'll add it to my list.
Heh. Fluttershy, I've said it
before, but I'll say it again.
This place would be
a zoo without you!
Angel!?
"Listen to you for once?"
Just WHAT exactly is
that supposed to mean!?
Come back! I meant
tell me, not... oh!
Well, whatever it is,
you're the only one
he can tell about it.
Li'l fella just wants
you all to himself.
Unfortunately,
that's not an option.
Aw, he's not causing
any real trouble..
[crash]
Ah!
[birds squawk]
Other than that, possibly.
[crash]
[elephant trumpets]
Or that. I'll just
stop talking.
[groan] I'll take care of it.
I hope this is
important, Angel.
I've barely made a dent in
my to-do list for today.
♪♪
Concentrated
Carrot Extract?
That's for reviving
energy-sapped herbivores.
Are you feeling run down?
You just like the
taste!? Ah! Angel!
That extract is
in short supply!
What's gotten into you?
Every day this week
you've been causing trouble
when I have work to do!
Of course I know you
can't talk to anypony else.
But that's not MY fault.
I have responsibilities!
You're right. We
can't go on like this.
I guess we do need to
see Zecora for help.
No need to sit
and silently stew.
Tell each other
what's bothering you.
He's so impatient, even when
he knows I have work to do.
Well, that's not true!
We talk all the time.
Of course talking at
the Sanctuary counts;
that's where I am when I
don't have a class to teach.
What do you mean,
that's the problem!?
You feel like I'm the
only pony you can talk to
and all I do is ignore you.
Well, I feel like
you don't care
about my responsibilities!
Heh.. Um, as you can see, we're
kind of at an impasse.
Ahh, such luck your
coming here, indeed.
Behold, the antidote
you need.
Is... this what you
meant by "help us"?
When trouble brews
between you two,
turning sister
against brother.
True understanding
is what's due,
each must come to
know the other.
There's no time to
waste, go directly home,
but you both must taste
when you're finally alone.
♪♪
Not yet, Angel.
Zecora told us to take it
together when we got home.
♪♪
Oh! I suppose we could dust
off the ol' picnic blanket.
It'll be just
like old times.
We'll drink the
potion and settle in
for a nice tea party.
I can barely remember
the last time we did that!|
I've been so busy
at the Sanctuary...
Though.. I really need to keep
an eye on Zecora's gecko
and I haven't finished
any of today's chores...
If I don't, the animals won't
get the care they need!
Oh. Maybe we should save
the potion until aft--
Angel! Zecora said
to go home first!
I know she said we have
to take it together so...
I guess I have to now.
I wonder what it's
going to dooWHOOOAA.-
Whoa whoa whoa! Hang on, hold
up, am I a pony!? Why am I a pony!?
Eeeeek!
♪ [dramatic sting] ♪
Question: did we
switch bodies?
♪♪
Whoa! Whoa!
Seriously, I'm a
pony? La la la la!
Talking is so cool!
Do you think this was what
Zecora meant to happen?
How are you gonna do
your chores!? Really?
That's what you're
worried about?
Pff. Well, maybe I don't
WANNA switch back!
I've only been able to
talk to YOU since we met,
and now I can talk
to anypony I want!
Roses are red,
violets are blue,
you sell flowers
and so do you!
Rubber baby buggy bumpers!
Toy boat! Toy boat!
Toy boa-AH!
Oh, come on!
I am so too listening! Quit
bein' so bossy because -- Ah!
Are there carrots around here!?
You think Zecora gave
us the wrong potion,
so you're gonna go to
her hut in the forest
and get something
to switch us back.
All by yourself?
You REALLY don't know what
it's like being a bunny.
Good luck with that. I'm
gonna go find those carrots.
"I need to finish your
chores?" Ha, ha, ha!
I don't work for you!
And caring about other
animals is a you thing.
♪ [horror sting] ♪
The stare!? You
can still do that?
Ugh! No fair making me do your
bidding against my will!
♪ [horror film music] ♪
All right! I'll go
do your lame chores
while you go see Zecora.
♪♪
Anypony know where
that useless list
of Fluttershy's chores is?
Dr. Fauna: Hey, Fluttershy.
I was starting to wonder
if you'd make it back.
Fluttershy! Oh,
yeah! Uh, that's me!
Definitely Fluttershy,
a hundred percent.
Oh...kay.
See how.. shy I am?
I talk to animals...
I want to
marry Discord...
Your list is
over there.
Oh. Yeah. There's my
good ol' list of chores
that I will absolutely
NOT rush through
because I definitely do not
have better things to do.
Well, well, well.
Remember me?
Ohh. I hope the gem tart stall
is still there again.
I could use a snack.
You nearly bought every tart
they had last time, Spike.
I can't imagine they
wouldn't show up
when there's a great
customer like you.
Oh. Hi, Angel.
What's going on?
Do you know what
he's trying to say?
Nope.
Sorry, Angel. You should
probably find Fluttershy.
If I see her, I'll let her
know you're looking for her.
♪♪
AND we're gonna keep
at it until you start
to develop a
taste for it.
Uh, check Muriel's trunk...
Ah, seems fine to me.
As long as we don't
need those keys..
Anyway. Let's see. Massage
Clementine's neck...
Get Scout to switch legs?
Eh. Probably best not to wake him.
Did the thing with the
thing, yada, yada, yada,
animals, animals, animals.
All that's left is.. monitor
Zecora's gecko until bedtime!?
All right, dude. How
about we do bedtime now?
Yeah, eating makes
me tired too.
Which reminds me, there's
some carrot extract
with my name on it.
OK! Let's get you fed
and off to dreamland.
What do you eat, anyway?
Whaddya say, Snake? Can you
find something else to eat
if I borrow those cookies
for my friend here?
♪♪
I'm sure
that's normal.
There you go.
Problem solved.
I don't see what's so
hard about this job.
Fluttershy is
SUCH a whiner!
♪♪
Quite a day, my fuzzy friend!
Did things work out
for you in the end?
I'm sorry, dear bunny,
that things seem so grave,
but I don't understand
when you sign and wave.
A single link to all the world.
only one in all the land.
How special she must be to
you, the one who understands.
Perhaps if you explained
what you wanted
to somepony who understood,
if you truly felt
heard and valued,
all would return to good.
And if you were
to both apologize,
having learned
this little lesson,
I imagine that
might bring an end
to the friendship
therapy session.
♪♪
Dr. Fauna: Fluttershy?
Do you mind helping me look
for Muriel the Baby Elephant?
Oh, she's having
dinner with Antoine.
Antoine the PYTHON!?
It was on the list:
"Remember Antoine wants to
have Muriel over for dinner."
Not over for dinner! He
wants to have her FOR DINNER!
Wait. WHAT!?
♪♪
Bad snake! Open your mouth
this instant, Mister!
♪ [tense music] ♪
What is going on!? You did
all the chores on your list.
Huh!? Didn't you!?
Well, technically,
I did'em, kind of.
But more technically,
it's not my list.
You wrote it!
Did I, though?
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU!?
You do NOT wanna know.
Huh?
Angel?
What's wrong
with her... him?
What happened!?
He's exhausted!
Fluttershy, I need a jar
of concentrated
carrot extract, STAT!
Ah! It's locked in
the supply room.
Where are your keys!?
Uh....
Any ideas how to get the
keys out of the elephant
that's inside the snake?
OK! Point taken. And
I totally deserve it.
I did not provide you with the
care that Fluttershy would.
But NOW you know
what it's like
not to get the
level of attention
to which you've
become accustomed!
The point is Fluttershy is
trapped in my bunny body
and if we don't help
her, maybe none of us
will get her attention. I get
that you don't want to help me,
but don't you want to help her?
♪ [military snare drum] ♪
♪♪
Here goes nothing.
Now we just need to get
those keys out of there..
Ha, ha! Nice
one, snake.
I guess Fluttershy was right.
Predators and prey
can work together.
♪♪
This place is so. Much. Work!
Oh! I know. I have no clue
how you do it all,
but we are so grateful.
♪♪
I can't believe she
does this every day!
I just wish I could
tell her myself..
What?
♪♪
You're awake!
"It was so hard getting
to Zecora's hut?
And impossible getting back?
You can't believe I
survive like this?"
Well, I can't believe
you work here every day!
These animals are crazy!
No wonder you don't
have time for me!
My life is hard? No,
YOUR life is hard!
You never appreciated me?
No, I never appreciated you!
You're sorry? I'm sorry too!!
Come here, you little bunny
who's a pony who's a bunny! Ooo!
Oh, my goodness! I'm
back! I'm a pony again!
Oh, Angel, I promise to always
make time for you from now on.
What do you mean maybe I won't
have to? You want to do.. WHAT?
...and that's when I realized
Fluttershy doesn't have to
be the only one I talk to.
I can come here and
talk to all of you.
And now that I know how much
work goes into this place,
I suppose I could kinda, sorta
help out every now and then.
Oh, Angel! That is so sweet,
but now that I know what
you go through every day,
I understand why your time
with me is so important.
I promise to always
make time for you!
Turns out your friend, here,
doesn't have a problem at all.
He isn't a gecko.
He's a fire lizard!
I forgot that before
they get their flame,
it's hard to
tell them apart.
I'm glad to discover where
the source of it lies,
or the fire that he breathes
would be quite the surprise.
Speaking of surprises...
Can you please
never do that again?
♪♪