"And that's when the yellow birdie
thought to himself:"
"Hm... My favorite little tree
isn't such a little tree anymore."
"So she sang her song, big and strong."
"And they all lived in that great,
big tree happily ever after."
The End.
Applejack!
Were you reading a bedtime story to...
...an apple tree?
Well, you know, bein' replanted in a whole
new place is very upsettin' for a tree.
And Bloomberg here is one of my favorites.
No fair, Applejack!
You've got a luxurious private
sleeper cart for a TREE...!
...while I am crowded and cramped
in a same cart with all the other ponies.
How am I supposed to get my beauty sleep?
But Bloomberg's the whole
reason we're makin' this trip.
He needs his rest so we can give him
as a gift to my relatives in Appleloosa.
You talk about it as if
it's your baby or something.
Who you callin' a baby?! Bloomberg's no baby!
Don't wet wittle Rarity make you all saddie-waddie.
Bloomber's a big and strong apple tree.
Yes, he is. A coochie-coochie-coo-coo-coo.
It's widdle Rarity, who's all saddie-waddie.
For crying out loud in the morning!
Do you guys mind?
I was up early fire-roasting those snacks
you're all eating and I pooped!
Speaking of, somebody's popcorn kernels didn't get popped.
Okay, fine.
Goodnight.
Maybe it's time we all got a little shut-eye.
We've got a big day ahead of us tomorrow.
Psst...! Pinkie Pie!
You asleep yet?
No. Are you asleep yet?
If I was sleeping, how could I
have asked you if you were asleep?
Oh yeah!
When we get to Appleloosa, you think
we'll have to carry that heavy tree...
...all the way from the train to the orchard?
What tree? You mean Bloomberg?
No. Fluttershy.
Fluttershy's not a tree, silly.
What's going on?
Rainbow Dash thinks Fluttershy is a tree.
I do NOT think she's a tree. I was just...
Did you say she was a tree?
No! Well... yes. But not exactly...
You know she's not a tree, right?
She's not a tree, Dashie.
I'd like to be a tree.
Oh, for Pete's sake!
Well, that was kinda huffy.
Huffy the Magic Dragon.
Could you all be quiet NOW?!
Bloomberg?
Bloomberg!
Sorry, but I tend to snore a bit.
Goodnight.
A buffalo stampede!
I just love their accessories.
They're getting awfully close to the train.
Ooh, looky!
Now they're going tricks!
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh! Now do a backflip!
Or... just jump?
Hm...
Something tells me this isn't a circus act.
Hey there! Where are you headed in such a hurry?
Wow. You're pretty quick for someone so...
...bulky. No offense.
I just wanna know...
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Wow...
I've got you now...
They've got Bloomberg!
Help!
And Spike!
Dragon-napping Spike. I'll show her.
Hey there!
Welcome to AAAPPLELOOSA!
Braeburn, listen...
Hey, cousin Applejack. Mind your manners.
You have yet to introduce me
to your compadres. Shame on you.
Braeburn, listen. Somth'n terrible's happened...
Terrible is right. Your train is full seven minutes late.
That's seven minutes less for you to
delight in the pleasures and wonders of...
AAAPPLELOOSA!
Boggles the mind, we settler ponies built
all this in just a past year, don't it?
And as you can see, we have all of the finest comforts.
Like horse-drawn carriages.
Okay, you pull now.
Eh, we just switched.
And now's there horse-drawn horse-drawn carriages.
Listen, Braeburn, I...
And here's our local waterin' hole:
The Salt Block.
That's enough salt for you!
Can't I at least get a glass of water?
Over there is the office of Sheriff Silverstar.
And here's where we have our wild west dances.
And here's where we have our mild west dances.
But Braeburn, we...
And here is the most wonderful sight in all of...
AAAPPLELOOSA!
Our apple orchard.
Braeburn!
First harvest should be any day now.
-Braebu...
-Good thing too.
-Brae...
-Cause we need that grub to live on.
BRAEBURN!!!
Uh... yes, cous?
You have a very nice town n' all
but we have a huuuge problem.
Some of our friends are missin'.
-A stampede of buffalo!
-The took Spike!
-Rainbow Dash went after them!
-And we can't find Pinkie Pie!
And we had an apple tree with us
for your orchard, but they took that too.
Did you say buffalo?
Dem buffalo, they want us settler ponies to take
every single tree you see here off this land.
They sure as hay don't want any new ones added in.
But why?
Beats me.
We put a lotta hard work into this land so we
could feed our town, our families, our foals.
And now they're sayin' all these trees have to go?
T'ain't fair.
Oh, I can't wait to get my hooves
on that little buffalo.
Nobody tricks Rainbow Dash and gets away with it.
Boo!
Pinkie Pie!
Ah, you caught me! Looks like I tricked you
and didn't get away with it either.
You're good.
Shh! What do you think you're doing?
You gotta get outta here.
I do?
You're gonna blow my cover!
I am?
-I'm trying to save Spike!
-OH MY GOSH! So am I!
And the more of us there are out here,
the more chance is of us getting...
...caught.
Run, Pinkie. I'll hold them off. Save yourself!
STOP!!!
Dash, Pinkie, 'sup?
Hey, no worries, I know those guys.
They're cool.
If you say so, Spike. Catch ya later, bro.
Seems they took me by mistake.
And they feel awful about it too, poor guys.
Fortunately, they totally respect dragons...
...so they treat me like an honored guest.
Still don't like ponies much though,
but you're with me, so it's cool.
Huh. Why, I still don't trust them.
I say we turn tail and bail while we still...
Before we finish eating?
Are you a loco in the coco?
Can I please have more of that
mushy stuff, whatever it was?
Certainly. And, Mr. Spike,
you like gemstones, yes?
Turquoise, mmm...
This here's Little Strongheart.
And these are my friends,
Pinkie Pie and Rainbow Dash.
You!
That's it! We are outta here.
Wait!
Please, accept my apologies
for what happened on the train.
We didn't mean for anyone to be hurt.
Yeah, right.
We only wanted the tree.
The settler ponies have overtaken the land
and have planted an orchard all over it.
Because of their thoughtlessness, we can no longer
run over our traditional stampeding grounds.
Huh?
I think it's time they've met Chief Thunderhooves.
We have a long and winding stampeding trail...
...which we run upon for many generations.
My father stampeded upon these grounds...
...and his father before him...
-...and...
-I think they get the idea, Chief.
It is a sacred tradition to run the path every year.
But these year, these settler ponies, these...
Appleloosans!
They planted apple trees all over it
without asking our permission.
Well, that's not very nice. Right, Rainbow Dash?
The ponies refused to move their trees...
...so we are stuck here and it is not fair!
See, Rainbow Dash? They had a good reason to...
I'll say they had a good reason!
Come on! We have some apple-picking
Appleloosans to talk to!
Gently, please.
Sorry, Rarity. But our friends are out there...
...and we have to be ready for a long hike
into buffalo territory if we're gonna save them.
Let's go!
Hi, guys!
Pinkie!
We're so glad you're safe.
How did you escape from the buffalo?
We didn't.
We promised the buffalo a chance to talk.
Oh yeah? 'bout what?
We brought our new pal Little Strongheart
here to explain to the Appleloosans...
...why they should move
the apple trees off buffalo land.
That information would be quite help...
That's weird. Cause my cousin Braeburn
here wants to explain to the buffalo...
...why they should let the apple trees stay.
That would a useful thing to...
The land is theirs!
You planted the trees not knowing that. Honest mistake.
Now you just gotta move 'em, that's all.
Well, heh...
They busted their rumps here! And now
they're supposed to bust their rumps again...
...just cause some buffalo
won't stampede someplace else?
Plant the trees somewhere else.
Where?
It's the only flat land around these parts.
The buffalo had it FIRST!
The settler ponies need it to LIVE!
Look!
Both the settlers and the buffalo
have good reasons to use this land.
There must be something we can do.
Hey! I've got an idea!
We may be divided
But of you all I beg
To remember we're all hoofed
At the end of each leg
No matter what the issue
Come from wherever you please
All this fighting gets you nothing
But hoof-and-mouth disease
Arguing's not the way
Hey, come out and play!
It's a shiny new day
So what do you say?
You gotta shaaare
You gotta caaare
It's a right thing to do
You gotta shaaare
You gotta caaare
And there'll always be a way through!
Both our diets, I should mention
Are completely vegetarian
We all eat hay and oats
Why be at each other's throat?
You gotta shaaare
You gotta caaare
It's a right thing to do
And there'll always be a way throoough!
Alright, Pinkie Pie, that was FANTASTIC!
What a great song, you're right on!
It appears that Sheriff Silverstar
and I have come to...
...an agreement.
We have.
That was the worst performance we've ever seen.
Absotively.
The time for action is upon us.
Our stampede will start at high noon tomorrow.
And if the orchard is still there...
...we'll flatten it!
And the whole town!
But Chief...!
And we Appleloosans say you
better bring your best...
...cause we'll be ready and waitin'!
But Sheriff...!
Oh... That wasn't the message of my song at all.
I want my kin to have what they need to live...
...but a storm's a-brewin' here.
And I don't like the look of it.
We've just got to talk some sense into them
before somepony gets hurt.
Listen, maybe if you would just reconsider, we...
About the trees, now if you just...
If we could just sit down and talk, we could...
Why won't anybody be rational and reasonable?!
Sheriff! If we could only...
Isn't there some way to stop this?
Unless the settlers remove those trees...
...I do not think so.
I know you don't wanna do this.
But they have taken our land.
What would you have me do, Rainbow Dash?
I don't know. But it's never too late
to think of something.
At noon it will be too late.
Come on! Think!
Thinkthinkthinkthinkthinkthinkthink!
He's not gonna do it!
You gotta shaaare
You gotta caaare
It's a right thing to do
You gotta shaaare...
CHAAARGE!
Ready?
Aim...
FIRE!
Yum!
Hey! I've got a much better idea!
We will allow the apple orchard to stay
in exchange for a share of its fruit.
Those... delicious apple pies.
I'd rather eat turquoise any day of the week.
Bloomberg, this is your special day.
Mama's so proud of you.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"Friendship is a wondrous and powerful thing."
"Even the worst of enemies can become friends."
"You need understanding and compromise."
"You've got to share. You've got to care."
Hey! That's what I said!
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000