Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shines
And I know
For absolute certain
That everything
Is certainly fine
There's the mayor en route
To her office
There's the sofa clerk
Selling some quills
Morning, kid!
My Ponyville
Is so gentle and still
Can things ever go wrong?
I don't think that they will
Morning in Ponyville shimmers
Morning in Ponyville shines
And I know
For absolute certain
That everything is certainly...
Rainbow Dash! That's not funny!
Terribly sorry, darling.
I'm afraid I'm not good
with the thundery ones.
Something tells me
everything is not going to be fine!
Season 3 | Episode 13
Magical Mystery Cure
Subbed by GrayJeager
Fr.Jeager@gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
What are you doing?
What happened to your cutie mark?
Whatever do you mean, Twilight?
I'm simply doing what I've done
since the day it first appeared.
Does my sky look fabulous
or what?
Too last season?
Where is Rainbow Dash?
Why isn't she handling this?
I still don't know
what you had to wake me up for.
I love sleeping in the rain.
It's not about the weather, Spike.
Rarity had Rainbow Dash's cutie mark
and said this was Rainbow Dash's cottage.
Something strange is going on.
Hey, guys.
Rainbow Dash!
Why is Rarity doing your job?
And what in Equestria is going on in...
here?!
These animals don't listen
No, not one little bit
They run around out of control
And throw their hissy fits
It's up to me to stop them
'Cause plainly you can see
It's got to be my destiny
And it's what
My cutie mark is telling me
I try to keep them laughing
Put a smile upon their face
But no matter what I try
It seems a bit of a disgrace
I have to entertain them
It's there for all to see
It's got to be my destiny
And it's what
My cutie mark is telling me
I don't care much for pickin' fruit
And plowin' fields ain't such a hoot
No matter what I try
I cannot fix this busted water chute!
I've got so many chores to do
It's no fun being me
But it has to be my destiny
'Cause it's what
My cutie mark is telling me
Lookie here at what I made
I think that it's a dress
I know it doesn't look like much
I'm under some distress
Could y'all give me a hand here
And help me fix this mess?
My destiny is not pretty
But it's what
My cutie mark is tellin' me
I'm in love with weather patterns
But the others have concerns
For I just gave them frostbite
Over-top of their sunburns
I have to keep on trying
For everyone can see
It's got to be
My destiny
And it's what my cutie mark
It's what my cutie mark
Yes, it's what
My cutie mark is telling me!
This is bad.
This is very, very bad!
What's going on?
Why is this happening?!
Last night when you were taking
one of your seven-hour bubble baths,
I got a special delivery
from the princess.
Dear Twilight Sparkle,
The spell contained
on the last page of this book
is Star Swirl the Bearded's
secret unfinished masterpiece.
He was never able to get it right,
and thus abandoned it.
I believe you are the only pony
who can understand and rewrite it.
Princess Celestia.
From one to another,
another to one.
A mark of one's destiny
singled out alone, fulfilled.
That doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't even rhyme!
I cast the spell
so I could find out what it was.
But nothing seemed to happen.
But now I know something did happen.
The spell has changed
the Elements of Harmony!
That must be why
their cutie marks are all wrong!
So just cast a counter-spell
to switch them back!
There is no counter-spell!
What about that memory spell you used
to fix everypony when Discord was here?
It's not their memories, Spike.
It's their true selves
that have been altered!
- Zecora's cure for the Cutie Pox?
- That won't work either...
Well, maybe it won't be so bad.
Maybe our friends will grow
to like their new lives?
No Spike. They're not
who they are meant to be anymore.
Their destinies are now changed.
And it's all my fault...
I have to find a way
To make this all okay
I can't believe this small mistake
Could've caused so much heartache
Oh why
Losing promise
I don't know what to do
Seeking answers
I fear I won't get through to you
Oh why
Oh, Spike, what have I done?
Aw, come on, Twilight,
you'll figure out a way to fix this.
These are your friends.
You're right, Spike.
And they mean more to me
than anything.
My friends...
Twilight?
Are you alright?
I've got it! I know what to do!
You do?
I may not be able
to remind them of who they are,
but I can show them
what they mean to each other.
They'll find the part of themselves
that's been lost so they can
help the friend
they care about so much!
Come on, Spike!
Fluttershy, wait!
- Oh... Hey, Twilight...
- Where are you going?
I'm moving back to Cloudsdale.
I don't know what's wrong,
but I can't seem to make anypony laugh.
Before you go,
I was wondering if you might
be willing to help Rainbow Dash.
She's really struggling
with her animals.
But I don't really know
anything about animals...
But you do know something
about Rainbow Dash.
I know
that she's a true friend,
and I'll do
anything I can to help her!
Rainbow Dash!
I'm in here! Help!
I'm trapped!
Hurry, Twilight! Can't you do
some sort of spell to get her out?
No.
Fluttershy,
you're the only one who can help!
Rainbow Dash needs you!
Um... Hello?
Little... woodland creatures?
I know that
you're all very upset,
and feel like giving
Rainbow Dash a hard time,
but we'd all really appreciate it
if you'd calm down and, um,
maybe rest for a bit?
Oh! Uh... look!
Here's some nice, juicy leaves
for you to munch on.
And some crunchy,
munchy acorns too.
Uh, wouldn't you like to take a break
and have a little snack?
Aw, look at that. I guess you were
all just cranky because you were hungry.
Oh, you are very welcome,
little friends.
Goodness, it's like
I can understand them!
I... I feel strange, like...
like this is what I'm meant to do,
like this is who I am!
My destiny!
Wha... what happened?
Fluttershy, look!
Your cutie mark!
It worked!
Oh, I'm so happy
you're back to normal!
Now, we need your help!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
To see the light that shines
From a true, true friend
Um, hello! Friend trapped inside,
remember?
Rarity needs your help
She's trying hard doing
What she can
Would you try
Just give it a chance
You might find that
You'll start to understand
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help you see
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
To see the light that shines
From a true, true friend
Uh, what just happened?
There's no time to explain,
but we need your help.
Applejack's trying to make dresses!
Say no more!
Applejack needs your help
She's trying hard doing
What she can
Would you try
Just give it a chance
You might find that
You'll start to understand
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
To see the light that shines
From a true, true friend
Oh my, what a terrible dream I had.
Or, maybe I'm still having it.
Rarity, Pinkie Pie is about
to lose the apple farm.
We need Applejack's help!
Lose the apple farm?
Well we can't let that happen,
now can we?
Pinkie Pie is in trouble
We need to get there
By her side
We can try to do
What we can now
For together we can be
Her guide!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
To see the light that shines
From a true, true friend
Now that's more like it,
what's next?
The townspeople are furious,
we need the old Pinkie Pie back.
I'm on it, I know just the thing.
The townspeople need you
They've been sad for a while
They march around, faces frown
And never seem to smile
And if you feel like helping
We'd appreciate a lot
If you get up there and spread
Some cheer from here to Canterlot
Come on ponies,
I wanna see you smile!
Pinkie!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
To see the light
(to see the light)
That shines
(that shines)
From a true, true friend!
A mark of one's destiny,
singled out alone, fulfilled.
Wait a second, that's it!
I understand now,
I know how to fix the spell!
From all of us together,
together we are friends,
with the marks of our destinies made one,
there is magic without end!
What happened?
Hello? Where am I?
What is this place?
Congratulations, Twilight.
I knew you could do it.
Princess! I don't understand.
What did I do?
You did something today
that's never been done before.
Something even a great unicorn like
Star Swirl the Bearded was not able to do.
Because he did not understand
friendship like you do.
The lessons you've learned here in Ponyville
have taught you well.
You have proven that you're ready,
Twilight.
Ready? Ready for what?
You've come such a long, long way
And I've watched you
From that very first day
To see how you might grow
To see what you might do
To see what you've been through
And all the ways
You've made me proud of you
It's time now
For a new change to come
You've grown up
And your new life has begun
To go where you will go
To see what you will see
To find what you will be
For it's time for you
To fulfill your destiny
Twilight...? Is that you?
I... I've never seen
anything like it!
Twilight's got wings! Awesome!
A new flying buddy!
Why, you've become an alicorn.
I didn't even know that was possible.
Alicorn party!
Wow... you look just like a princess!
That's because she is a princess.
Hold on a second!
A princess?
Since you've come to Ponyville,
you've displayed the charity, compassion,
devotion, integrity, optimism,
and of course,
the leadership of a true princess.
But... does this mean
I won't be your student anymore?
Not in the same way as before.
I'll still be here to help and guide you,
but we're all your students now, too.
You are an inspiration to us all,
Twilight.
But... what do I do now?
Is there a book about
being a princess I should read?
There will be time
for all of that later.
We are gathered here today
in celebration of a momentous occasion.
My most faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle,
has done many extraordinary things
since she's lived in Ponyville.
She even helped reunite me
with my sister, Princess Luna.
But today, Twilight Sparkle
did something extraordinary.
She created new magic,
proving without a doubt
that she is ready
to be crowned
Equestria's newest princess.
Fillies and gentlecolts,
may I present for the very first time,
Princess Twilight Sparkle!
Thou Princess Twilight cometh
Behold, behold
A Princess here before us
Behold, behold, behold
Behold, behold
(behold, behold)
The Princess Twilight cometh
Behold, behold
(behold, behold)
The Princess is
(the Princess is)
Here!
Say something, Princess.
A little while ago,
my teacher and mentor Princess Celestia
sent me to live in Ponyville.
She sent me to study friendship,
which is something
I didn't really care much about.
But now, on a day like today,
I can honestly say
I wouldn't be standing here
if it weren't for the friendships
I've made with all of you.
Each one of you taught me something
about friendship, and for that,
I will always be grateful.
Today, I consider myself
the luckiest pony in Equestria.
Thank you, friends.
Thank you, everypony!
Twilight! I'm so proud of you!
Are you crying?
Of course not,
it's... it's liquid pride.
Totally different thing!
Way to go, Princess!
Best coronation day ever!
- We love you, Twilight.
- I love you too, girls!
The light in Equestria shimmers
Life in Equestria shines
And I know for absolute certain
That everything
Yes, everything
Yes, everything is going to
Be fine
Yes, fine
Yes!
Everything's gonna be just fine!
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
A friend will be there
To help them see
A true, true friend
Helps a friend in need
To see the light (to see the light)
That shines (that shines)
From a true, true friend