You gotta really
flap 'em hard.
Whoa!
Uh, maybe not quite that hard.
Looking good up there,
Princess Twilight.
Applejack, you know you
don't have to call me that.
Why do you protest so?
You've already given up
wearing your crown all the time,
the least you can do
is embrace your new title.
If other ponies want to
address me that way,
I suppose it's fine. But...
not my friends.
It just doesn't
feel right.
And neither does
all this flying business.
The Summer Sun Celebration
is only two days away
and I'm never going to be
ready to perform my part.
Not if you spend all your
time down here you won't.
Now get up there and show
everypony the big finish!
That's what
I'm talking about!
Waa-hoo!
Wow! That was a big finish!
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
You look amazing, darling.
They've really captured
your regality.
I suppose.
Oh, don't be so modest.
It's everypony's dream to
someday wear a crown
and have their coronation
ceremony preserved
in stained glass
for all to see.
I don't know if it's
everypony's dream.
Most of my dreams
are about frosting.
We'd better get going.
We don't want to
miss our train.
Fluttershy's
right.
Don't know about y'all
but I've still got bushels
to do to get ready.
The official celebration
may be here in Canterlot
but whoo-wee! has the
Mayor put us in charge
of one heck of a
party back home.
Aw, don't look like
that, sugarcube.
You get to be right there
with the other princesses
when Celestia
raises the sun.
And I'm honored.
Really I am.
It's just that the
Summer Sun Celebration
is what first brought
all of us together.
It just doesn't feel right
not getting to spend
such a special day with
my Ponyville friends.
It doesn't feel right
to us either, darling.
If the Mayor wasn't
so desperate for our assistance,
we'd most certainly
stay here in Canterlot.
And of course we
do understand
that your royal duties
must come first.
The Summer Sun
Celebration
may have brought
us together,
but it's something
much bigger
that'll always
keep us connected.
Exhibit A.
The six of us are
united by the
Elements of Harmony.
No amount of "royal duties"
is gonna change that.
Right everypony?
Right, Pinkie Pie?
Creamy, creamy frosting.
You should take
that as a "yes".
We're going to
write you
and give you so
many details,
it'll be like you're in
Ponyville with us!
Right, girls?
Cross my heart
and hope to fly.
Stick a cupcake in my eye.
And you will be
with us
right after the
celebration.
We already have an
appointment on the books
to discuss the royal
upgrades to your loft decor.
All aboard for
Ponyville!
Whee!
I can't help it, Spike.
They've only been
gone a minute
and I already feel like
I'm missing something.
For the Princess.
Dear Twilight, you
aren't missing anything.
Your friend, Pinkie Pie.
That's me!
Whoo whee!
But I am.
I just know it.
Check. Check. Check. Check.
And... check.
Huh. What do you know?
We're way ahead
of schedule.
I credit your extremely
competent assistant.
So do I.
The Celebration isn't
until the day
after tomorrow.
We could still fit in a
quick trip to Ponyville
and be back in
plenty of time
to finish off these last few
things before the main event.
That would be nice, Spike.
But what if something
else came up
while we were gone?
What if we were delayed
getting back
and I wasn't able to finish
everything on that list?
What if we lost the list
on the way to Ponyville
and then couldn't remember
which things we'd done
and which things
we hadn't done
and then spent so much
time trying to figure out
what we hadn't done
and what we had done
that we ruined the
entire celebration
by not doing the one
really important thing
that we were supposed to do?
Uh, so that's a "no", then?
These are the first royal
duties Princess Celestia
has given me.
I can't risk
letting her down.
And I'm sure
you won't.
Your Highness!
No need for that now,
Princess Twilight.
Sorry.
No need
to apologize.
Sorry.
I must admit that it is
wonderful to actually
be looking forward to the
Summer Sun Celebration.
What do you mean?
For my subjects it has
always been a celebration
of my defeat of Nightmare
Moon, but for me?
It was just a
terrible reminder
that I'd had to
banish my own sister.
I guess I'd never really
thought about it that way.
But now it has become a
wonderful reminder
of her transformation
back into Princess Luna
and our happy reunion.
I am so pleased that you
will be playing a role
in the festivities.
I know it must have
been difficult
to see your friends return
to Ponyville without you.
Maybe a little.
You may no longer
be my student,
Princess Twilight,
but I hope you know that
I will always be here
if you need me.
Just as I hope that you
will always be there
when I need you.
I think this guy
needs you.
A message for
Princess Twilight.
A letter from
Ponyville, I presume?
Never mind.
It's not important.
Spike, where were we?
About to call it a night?
We should probably go over
the checklist one more time.
I knew you were
gonna say that.
I'll leave you to it.
Huh?
Spike?
Check. Check. Check. Check.
Spike!
What time is it?
It's the middle
of the night.
But it could
be morning.
That's just it.
I can't tell.
Whoa. That is weird!
Come on, Spike.
We have to find out
what's going on.
What do you
think it means?
Princess Twilight
will know.
I'm sure it's just...
There's certainly a logical...
Your Highness, you
must come with us.
It's Princess Luna and
Princess Celestia.
They're gone!
But I don't understand.
Where are they?
We don't know.
It seems that Princess
Celestia and Princess Luna
have simply...
... vanished .
Vanished!
This is why we
have come to you.
We await your command.
My command?
We're officers of
the Royal Guard.
We take our orders
from royalty.
With Princess Luna and
Princess Celestia gone
and Princess Cadance
overseeing
the Crystal Empire now,
that means we take our
orders from you.
Princess Twilight, there
is no time to waste.
We need to know what
you want us to do.
I want you to continue the
search for Princess Luna
and Princess Celestia.
We have to find them
before ponies start to panic.
There must be some clue
that can tell us
what's happened to them.
If you find
something, anything,
let me know immediately.
Way to take
charge, Twilight.
Your Highness, news
from Ponyville.
The Everfree Forest
appears to be, well...
...invading!
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Are you all right?
My goodness, what is it
that has caused you all
such distress?
Whatever it is, I'm
sure it's nothing
you need to really
worry about.
No. You were right.
You should be worried.
Very, very worried.
Come on, y'all,
put your backs into it.
Eeyup.
Nnope.
Dagnabit! We ain't never
seen this kind of trouble
with weeds before.
Now that I think about it.
I've never even seen these
kind of weeds at all!
Have y'all?
Nnope.
Where the heck are these
things comin' from?
And what in tarnation is
going on with the sky?
Oh, no you don't.
This is Ponvyille
territory.
And we aren't due
for rain until
after the Summer Sun
Celebration.
You Everfree clouds need
to just head on back
to where you belong.
Whoa!
Gonna make me do this
the hard way, huh?
Hey!
Hm. Something strange
about the sky.
What in the name of calming
chamomile is going on?
Opal Essence,
darling, I'm so sorry.
I promise I'm not doing
this on purpose.
It wasn't me.
I swear.
Sweetie Belle, if this is
some sort of prank
you and your little Crusader
friends are pulling,
I find very little
humor in it.
Rarity! You have to
help me.
I think something's
wrong with my horn.
Where are we going?
The Everfree Forest
is ... invading.
Whatever is going on,
I'm sure we're going
to need our friends
and the Elements of
Harmony to stop it.
I just hope we haven't
missed the train.
Uh, Twilight, there
is another way for us
to get to Ponyville, remember?
There is?
You can fly.
Oh. Right.
Whoa!
Something very
strange is going on and--
I for one would
appreciate an explanation.
All I know is the
sky's split in two
and these clouds moving in
sure aren't from around here.
Neither are all
these crazy plants.
They're comin' from
the Everfree Forest.
And try as we might,
us Earth Ponies
can't do anything
to get rid of 'em.
Don't suppose you
know any magic
that might stop 'em
from spreadin'?
Alas, this whole "raging
forest" situation
seems to have left my
horn on the fritz.
We have to figure
out something.
I don't know how
much more of this
Ponyville can take.
I don't know how
much more I can take.
The Forest is
expandin', y'all.
And judgin' by how
fast it's movin',
it doesn't seem content just
takin' over Ponyville.
I reckon before long, it'll
cover half of Equestria.
Whoa!
I'm starting to wish
we'd taken the train!
Almost there.
Come on, Spike.
We need to get the
Elements of Harmony
and find the others.
Incoming!
Whoa!
Oh, thank goodness.
Oh, I hope you know we
wouldn't normally
go through your books
without permission.
Sweet ground.
Sweet, sweet,
wonderful ground.
OK, I get it!
I need to work
on my flying.
I don't know if
you've noticed,
but the Everfree Forest is
just a teeny-tiny bit
out of control.
Guess it turned out you
were missing something
here in Ponyville
after all.
But perhaps you
already know
what's causing all
of this calamity?
Has Princess Celestia
sent you to dispel it
post haste?
Not exactly.
You see, Princess
Celestia is,
well, she and Princess
Luna are both...
They're missing!
I don't know who
has taken them.
But I've got a hunch
we're going to need
the Elements of Harmony
to get them back.
Oh yeah.
Just like old times.
Aaa-boo-yah!
I told you we'd always be
connected by the Elements.
Now we just gotta
figure out who to aim
these bad boys at so we can
get Celestia and Luna back
and keep the rest of Equestria
from becoming plant food.
Any ideas?
Hmmm.
I haven't found squat
in any of the books
I've been looking through.
Oopies. Missed a spot.
Half-day. Half-night.
Strange weather patterns.
Out of control plants.
I think I'm starting to
get a pretty good idea
of who we're up against.
Winter wrap up.
Winter wrap up-- Ooooh!
Ho ho! Now Twilight,
you know Princess Celestia
said that you were to
give me a heads-up
before you summoned me with
that little spell she gave you.
In case you
haven't noticed,
I was in the middle of
a particularly
invigorating shower.
Enough!
Release Princess Celestia
and Princess Luna
and stop the Everfree
Forest from invading!
Why whatever are
you talking about?
Don't you play dumb
with us, Discord.
We know you're the one
behind all of this.
Don't get me wrong, I
absolutely LOVE
what you've done
with the place,
but I couldn't possibly
take responsibility.
I'm reformed.
Don't you remember?
Yeah. Right.
This has got your cloven
hoof-prints all over it.
I'll have you know that I
have only one cloven hoof.
Such accusations.
And here I thought
we were friends.
Drop the act, Buster!
We're onto you.
Ladies, ladie,
I'm innocent.
Would I lie to you?
Yes!
Um? Maybe?
Well, then, it seems
we've reached an impasse.
I'm telling the truth,
but you think I'm lying.
What do friends like us do
in a situation like this,
Princess Twilight?
Congrats by the way
on the promotion.
You totally deserve it.
I say we blast
him back to stone.
Works for me.
Here! Here!
Hey! We can't do that.
What if he really is
telling the truth?
Well, finally!
Somepony willing to give me
the benefit of the doubt.
The rest of you could
learn a lot about
friendship from my dear
friend, Shutterfly here.
Um, it's Fluttershy.
Oh, right. Whatever.
If you're not the
one responsible,
then help us
figure out who is.
I suppose I could,
but after all the hoof-pointing
and besmirching
of my good name, I just
don't know if I'm up to it.
Why don't you ask
your zebra friend
if she knows anything?
Why don't you ask
your zebra friend
if she knows anything?
Zecora!
From my home,
I've had to flee.
The forest has grown
too wild even for me.
Any idea why all
this is happenin'?
I'm afraid it is a
mystery to me as well.
But I may have
something that,
if combined with a spell...
I do not dare
to use it myself.
The results
would be tragic.
It only responds
to alicorn magic.
Princess Twilight, you
can turn the potion
from purple to white.
After a sip you may see
why the sky is day
and night.
Oooohhh!
Doesn't seem to be work--
Where am I?
Not another step.
Princess Luna!
I don't understand.
Where are we?
Why did you and
Celestia disappear?
Did you really expect me
to sit idly by
while they all basked in
your "precious light"?
"Precious light"?
There can only be one
Princess in Equestria.
And that Princess
will be me!