Princess Celestia! We came
as fast as we could.
I need you to wield the Elements
of Harmony once again and stop Discord.
The Elements! They're gone!
Everypony has to play
or the game is over.
And I win.
Our friendship... over?
Who were you talking to?
Nopony! Nopony whatsoever.
What?
Pinkie Pie! Are we glad to see you.
WHY? Need a good laugh?
What is happening to my friends?
Looks like we might be due
for a big old storm of chaos.
And what are YOU laughing at?!
You ponies are just
the most fun I've had in aeons.
Well, QUIT IT!!!
You better think
before you laugh at the Pink!
...kie Pie!
Oh, yeah?
Well, ha ha.
Quit it!
No. Ha ha.
QUIT IT!!!
No. Ha ha ha ha ha.
Uh, Rarity?
This here diamond o' yours?
Twilight said we should split it
six way, since we uh...
...found it together.
Try it, punk. He's mine. All mine!
Girls, why are you
all acting like this?
We need to stick together!
It's just too entertaining.
Stop it, Discord!
You're not playing fair.
I'm not playing fair?
Perhaps we haven't met.
I'm Discord. Spirit of chaos
and disharmony.
Hellooo!
How are we supposed to find
the Elements of Harmony...
...when you took away the labyrinth
before we could get to the end?!
Oh, wait! Did you...?
How funny!
You thought the Elements
were *in* the labyrinth?
Twists and turns are my master plan...
...then find the Elements
back where you began.
I never said they
were in the labyrinth.
But... But...
Keep trying, Twilight Sparkle.
♥ Maybe the magic of friendship ♥
can help you.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have some chaos to wreak.
Chocolate milk?! I hate chocolate milk!
Think, Twilight, think!
Find the Elements
back where you began...
Back where you began...
Don't touch my gem!
I'm touching your gem, Rarity. Ha ha.
What's you laughing at?!
Ugh, I just wanna go home.
Wait a minute...
Home! Back where you began!
The Elements must be in...
...Ponyville!
Come on, girls! I'm certain this is
what Discord's riddle really meant.
If we get back to the library...
...I have a book that I just know
can give us a clue.
Good boy, Angel! Mama's so proud.
Weeell, I can see so much better now.
I meant to do that.
Discord's turned our
dirt roads into soap!
Beautiful, isn't it?
This is the new and improved Ponyville.
And these are only my first changes.
This may look like fun, but it's not.
Picture it, the chaos
capital of the world.
I can't picture anything.
It's too dark.
Well, wait a few minutes and you'll
see it in the beautiful light of day.
Or not.
Ponyville the chaos
capital of the world?
Not if I have anything to say about it.
Don't worry. You won't.
Okay, we're here. Everyone please
please please just go inside, please?
I absolutely refuse.
With pleasure.
I hate libraries.
Pleeease, we gotta hurry!
Forget it, Twilight.
I know what you're up to.
The second I go in you'll have your
little minion Spike come and take Tom.
-Tom?
-Well, it's not going to work!
You're not going in
without him, are you?
Fine!
What'd you do that for, Fluttershy?
Cause you just look so peaceful.
I, uh...
Careful, Twilight!
You'll ruin his beautiful finish.
Oh, for the love of...
Twilight, what's going on?
Why's everybody look so...
...gray?
Don't ask. I need you
to help me find something.
Hey, Twilight? What's
soaking wet and clueless?
Fluttershy, I've had just about enou...
Your face!
What's happened to everypony?
I guess you just bring up
the worst in us, Spike.
No time to explain.
We've got to find the reference guide
to Elements of Harmony...
...before somepony does
something she'll regret!
The Elements of Harmony?
Oh! I know exactly where that book is!
Found it!
Ha!
Fluttershy... You better
give me that book!
Keep away!
Hey!
Applejack! Give me that book!
I don't have any book.
Pinkie!
You guys!
Stop it right now!
Mine!
Hey! Do you even know
what you just stole?
No, but if you want it, I want it.
GIVE ME THAT BOOK!!!
Where is she? Where is Rarity?
Beats me.
Lies!
Get back! All of you!
This is my book! AND I'M GONNA READ IT!
The Elements!
They were here all along!
This is great!
Now you guys can defeat Discord
and put everything back to normal.
See, girls? We did it! We've found
the Elements of Harmony!
Together!
You don't even care, do you?
No.
I never thought it would
happen. My friends...
...have turned into complete jerks!
Necklace... Necklace...
Aaand...
...big crown-thingy.
Come on, everypony! Let's go!
But, Twilight.
Aren't you missing somepony?
Nope. We've got the liar, the grump,
the hoarded and the brute.
That just about covers it.
What about Rainbow Dash?
Congratulations, Spike. You're
the new Rainbow Dash. Now let's go!
Me?!
B-b-but... what if she finds out
I've been impersonating her?
That won't end well.
Too bad. You're Rainbow Dash.
Now let's go defeat Discord so we don't
ever have to talk to each other again.
YEAH! WOOHOO!
Move!
Look out! Here comes Tom!
Well, well, well. I see you've
found the Elements of Harmony.
How terrifying!
Discord! I've figured out
your lame riddle.
You're in for it now!
I certainly am. You've
clearly outduelled me.
And now it's time to meet my fate.
I'm prepared to be
defeated now, ladies.
Fire when ready.
Formation! Now!
Rainbow Dash! Get over here!
All right. Let's get this over with.
What's going on?
Mine's workin'. There must be
somethin' wrong with yours.
I hate the Elements of Harmony!
Garbage.
MINE!
Sorry, Twilight. I guess I better get
back upstairs and clean up the library.
Good luck with all this... whoa!
Oops. Sorry, Rainbow Crash.
Bravo, ponies! Bravo!
Harmony in Equestria
is officially dead.
Discord rules, Celestia drools.
It's your fault it didn't work!
Who are you talking to?
Any of you! All of you!
I'm outta here!
I better go too. I got new, better
friends waitin' for me at the farm.
Yeah! I'm sick of you losers.
Fine! Leave! See if I care.
I don't need you guys either.
With friends like you, who needs...
...enemies.
My stomach!
Twilight, you've got to
see what I just did.
It's priceless!
Come now, Twilight Sparkle. You've
got to get into the spirit of things.
After all, this is your new home.
Not anymore.
YES!
Pack your things, Spike. We're leaving.
And don't ask where we're going,
'cause... I don't know yet.
Just not here.
Can't... move!
The Princess...
has been sending these...
...since I came back upstairs.
Make it stop!
These are all the letters
I've written to the Princess...
...since I've lived in Ponyville.
But why would she send them back?
"Real friends don't care
what your cover is..."
"Friendship is a wondrous
and powerful thing..."
"And like the path cut through the orchard,
there'll be always a way through."
"The best thing to do is
to stay true to yourself..."
"...special magical connection
with her friends..."
"...maybe even before she's met them."
Spike! Spike, it's all so clear!
Can't you see? Discord's trying to
distract us from what's important.
He knows how powerful
our friendships are...
...and he's trying to
keep us from seeing it.
Do you remember what I said
the first day we arrived in Ponyville?
I told you that the future of Equestria
didn't rest on me making friends.
But the opposite is true!
The friendships I've made
since I've been here...
...would save Equestria
from Nightmare Moon.
And now they need to
save it from Discord!
You're right, Spike.
I've got to fight for my friendships.
For them. For me. For Equestria!
Oh. Uh...
Why don't you just stay here and rest?
I'll take care of the whole fighting
for friendship thing myself.
And so I tried to defeat Discord...
...but none of my so-called friends
would lift a hoof to help me.
Applejack! I'm here to fight
for our friendship.
Oh. Now you wanna fight.
Where were you when
I was battlin' Discord?
Snap out of it!
This isn't you!
You're not a liar.
Wha... What happened?
Twilight!
I saw a vision of us
feudin' and fightin'.
I couldn't face the truth
so I started tellin' lies.
Can you ever forgive me?
I already have.
Come on!
Oh no!
Twilight! Applejack!
I just had the worst dream!
What do you think you're doing?
Get away from my gem! Get Away!
Let us never speak of this again.
Oh, and I... I turned gray!
Can you believe it?
She's not here.
Without Rainbow Dash
we can't use the Elements.
She could be anywhere by now.
We're never gonna find her.
Yeah, we will. Cause she's right there.
Rainbow Dash!
Hey, guys!
We've been looking everywhere for you.
That's nice.
Discord's still on the loose.
We need you to help us defeat him
with your element: loyalty.
Loyalty-schmoyalty.
Have you guys seen Ponyville?
It's a disaster!
I'm staying here in Cloudsdale
where everything is awesome.
How in Equestria could she think that
tiny patch of clouds is Cloudsdale?
The same way he got you to think that
cheap rock was a bona fide diamond?
I thought we agreed
never to speak of it again.
Time for Plan B.
Okay, Fluttershy.
You grab Rainbow Dash
and hold her down.
Applejack will lower me
down from this rope...
...so I can cast
the memory spell on her.
Got it!
Um... I'm just wondering
if it's okay...
...if I hold you down
against your will for a little bit?
Nice try. Ponyville's
your problem, not mine.
Come on, Fluttershy!
We've gotta catch her.
Applejack!
PinkiIEEE! You were supposed
to secure the roOOPE!
Oops.
Rarity! Pinkie! Hold on!
Y'all are slowin' 'er down!
Oh, Fluttershy. Would you
be a dear and FLY FASTER, please?
I can't!
If you can't catch her, Discord wins!
That... big... dumb... MEANIE!!!
Okay, Applejack! Last rope!
Make it count!
Lemme go! I don't need you guys!
Leave me alone!
Wha... What happened?
How's Ponyville?!
Where are the Elements?!
Did we stop Discord?
Maybe it's a little early
for a group hug.
Chaos is a wonderful, wonderful thing.
Not as wonderful...
...as friendship!
This again?
That's right! You couldn't break apart
our friendship for long.
Oh, Applejack. Don't lie to me.
I'm the one who made you a liar.
Will you ever learn?
I'll tell you what
we've learned, Discord.
We've learned that
friendship isn't always easy...
...but there's no doubt
it's worth fighting for.
Ugh, gag.
Fine. Go ahead.
Try and use your little Elements.
"Friend me". Just make it quick.
I'm missing some excellent chaos here.
All right, ladies! Let's show him
what friendship can do!
Wait, wait, wait!
What's this?
No...
Nooo!!!
We are gathered here today...
...to once again honor
the heroism of these six friends...
...who stood up
to the villain Discord...
...and saved Equestria
from eternal chaos.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000
Corrected for iTunes RIP by Yayponies.eu team !