Welcome to the Grand
Equestria Pony Summit!
You delegates have
traveled far and wide
to represent your cities
as we seek to
celebrate and learn
from all the unique places
that make up our wonderful
land of Equestria.
At tonight's welcome
reception, Princess Cadance
will dedicate this beautiful
friendship statue,
made up of gemstones from
each of your home cities.
Now I'd like to
turn things over
to the one who
organized the Summit,
Princess
Twilight Sparkle!
Thank you, everypony.
With delegates from
over fifty cities
attending three days of
conferences, receptions,
and meetings,
this is the largest Grand
Equestria Pony Summit yet.
And let me tell you,
putting it all together
has led to more than one
sleepless night.
We're so excited to have you
here and to learn more
about life all across this
great land of ours!
And now, my faithful
assistant Spike
would like to say
a few words.
Um, hello, everypony.
I'm here to help any way I can,
so if there's anything I
can do for any of you--
We love you,
Princess Twilight!
We love all the princesses!
I guess everypony
loves a princess.
Regular subtitles by YayPonies
We have muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
Agh!
Spike!
Spike?
Little help?
Spike, we need you!
Of course! What
can I do?
Spike: Whoa! What
happened to you?
Oh, I'm sorry, Spike, I just
need a quick nap...napkin.
Tell the delegates I'll...
She's been awake three straight
days preparing for the Summit.
We need to make sure she
gets some rest today.
She'll never be able to
attend the welcome reception
in this condition.
Can I count on you to see to
it that she isn't disturbed?
I promise I won't let you down.
Perfect.
Not on my watch.
Uh, excuse me?
Can you keep it
down a little?
Oh no!
I'll give you
birdseed...worms...
anything!
Just please stop singing
before you wake the Princess!
Huh. I can't believe
that worked.
Ah!
Uh, hi fellas. Sorry
to break up your game,
but there's sort
of an important
diplomatic summit
kinda thingy going on
and it involves a princess
needing to sleep and uh,...
maybe you could move
your game somewhere else?
The Princess thanks you
for your understanding!
Excuse me!
Do you have to do
this right now?
HA-CHEW!
Oh no!
Are those Dragonsneeze Trees?
These are too top heavy.
Wouldn't take much to
bring these beauties down.
Can't you just wait a few hours?
Sorry, it's a public hazard.
I've got my orders.
Well, I've got my
orders, too...
from Princess Twi-Twi-Twilight.
HA-CHEW!
Princess Twilight?
Oh! Why didn't you say so!
Gee, I reckon they'll
keep a few more hours.
Good thing I've got the
princesses on my side.
Aw, come on!
EXCUSE ME!
EXCUSE ME! SIR!
I REALLY NEED YOU TO--
--STOP RIGHT NOW!
Oops.
Let me guess, the noise?
Sorry, but we can't have
a broken water main.
What, you couldn't
do this yesterday?
Hey, pal, I'm just tryin'
to make sure everything
runs smooth for the Summit.
But there is no Summit
without Princess Twilight!
And she needs things to
be kept quiet around here.
So if you don't mind, I'd--
All right, all right, if that's
how she wants it.
But if something happens,
it ain't my fault.
Hm. Princess Twilight
will be rested;
Princess Cadance will be proud
and Princess Spike
deserves a little reward.
Princess Spike. Heh-heh!
All right, I worked
forever on this thing.
Uh, hi, can I help you?
My friend here, the
distinguished pony
from up Manehattan and I are
in a bit of a pickle,
and we need the Princess
Twilight to resolve it.
Can you talk a little quieter?
And maybe come back later?
Oh, sure now, gosh,
I wish we could,
but uh, we're both
supposed to give speeches
about our local economies
in five minutes.
And we've been booked
in the same hall.
I had the room first,
and let's be honest,
my speech is more important.
Point of order there, sir,
but I think you'll find
that my speech is the more
important one, dontcha know.
Look, youse is gonna have
a lot of unhappy delegates
on your hooves unless
we get a ruling
from Princess
Twilight right now.
Let me see what I can do.
Huh? Does something
need scheduling?
Oh, uh, yeah.
Two delegates have speeches
booked in the same hall.
What do I do?
OK, no problem.
Just put the hay in the
apple and eat the candle.
Huh?
I need an answer!
But Twilight can't
even think straight.
Oh my gosh! What am
I supposed to do?
Well? What did she say?
She picked me, right?
Hey hey hey!
Let's not be too
hasty there, good sir.
I got a feeling
she went with me.
Hey, hey if she
didn't pick me,
it ain't hard to see that as an
insult to all of Manehattan.
You know what I'm sayin'?
And it'd sure be a
shame to see something
like a scheduling issue
create a nasty old rift
between Whinnyapolis
and Ponyville.
So? What did the
Princess say?
Come on now,
spit it out!
Ummm, she said that,
well, she said, that she,
she wants you to ... share it?
If that's what the Princess
wants, what are you gonna do?
The Princess is always right.
No hard feelings; this
is not about you and me.
And now back to more
important things.
Combining those two
talks was a disaster!
The hall was overcrowded
and the speakers just
shouted over each other!
Huh? But--
Why would the Princess
have made such a decision?
Uh-oh.
Uh, by order of Princess
Twilight...be quiet!
I was really looking forward
to the "Don't Spend
All Your Bits" speech,
but when I went into the
hall, a pony had taken my seat.
A pony who used to be my friend!
Your friend took
your seat? Big deal.
Why don't you just--
No offense, but I don't need
some random dragon's opinion.
I want to hear what
Princess Twilight thinks.
Ugh. Fine.
Uh, the Princess says no
friendship should end
over a seat.
You should forgive your friend.
Of course! Oh, the
Princess is so wise!
I could tell these
delegates anything
as long as they think it
came from Twilight.
All right, who's next?
So how can Princess
Twilight be of service?
Well! As host city, the
Canterlot delegation
feels it's only right
that we should get passes
to every meeting
and party, yes?
Well, that's doesn't seem fair.
I mean, Princess Twilight
doesn't think that seems fair.
Yes, yes, very well.
It was worth a try,
though, wasn't it old chap?
This is great!
I just took care of a
whole bunch of stuff
that Twilight won't have to
worry about when she wakes up!
Wonder if anypony else
needs the Princess's help.
If I can check a few
of these meetings
off Twilight's schedule,
then when she wakes up,
she won't have to think about
anything but the reception.
Uh, says here you have a
meeting with Princess Twilight?
Yuppers. She wanted
me to prep her on all the
different gemstones in the
Citizens of Equestria statue
before the reception tonight.
OK. Go ahead.
Um, well, I'd rather um,
tell the Princess directly.
Well, if it helps, you can
call me Princess Spike.
No no no! It's all right!
The Princess asked me to take
care of a few things for her.
That's why I came to find you.
If you say so.
The Princess says so.
OK, let's start with topaze.
I'm here for your 2:00.
You?
But I'm supposed to be
briefing Princess Twilight
on the progress with
the water main.
I speak for the Princess.
Well, uh, can I start
fixing it again?
I'm gettin' a little
worried, to be honest.
Actually, Twilight still needs
her rest and her "no noise"
policy is still in effect
for a few more hours. Sorry!
Hey Spike, what's going on?
Oh, you know, just settin'
em up and knockin' em down.
What do you mean?
Not only have I kept things
quiet so Twilight could sleep,
I also took care of all her
afternoon meetings
so she won't have to worry
about them when she wakes up.
Are you sure she'd
want you doing that?
There are so many things to
keep track of at this Summit.
Ah, don't worry,
I got it covered.
I know Twilight so well, it's
easy to make decisions like her.
Oh. OK.
Well, thank you for keeping
Twilight's stress level down...
...as long as that's the
real reason you're doing it.
Well, why else
would I be doing it?
You're not enjoying speaking
for Twilight a little bit?
Enjoying it? Ha ha! No way!
The only things I'm doing
by order of the Princess
are for the good of the Summit.
Heh heh heh heh.
By order of the Princess.
Ah. Princess life is good.
It sure is. But it's also
hard work, isn't it?
Eh, it's not so bad.
Spike, I'm concerned you might
be abusing your relationship
with Twilight.
What are you talking about?
I'm a great princess!
I mean, Twilight's
a great princess
and I've been working
hard to help her!
When two delegates
had a falling out,
I'm the one who fixed
their friendship!
I listened to that pony
drone on about gems
for forty-five minutes so
Twilight wouldn't have to!
I moved a polo match away from
the tower so she could sleep!
And I didn't even eat that
delicious looking statue!
I'm a decision-making master!
OK, so maybe I did get a little
carried away making decisions.
But it's not like
anything bad happened.
Whooooaa!
This is unexpected.
I'll go shut off the main;
you get rid of the water!
At least the statue's OK.
Oh no.
Oh no!
Ah...Ah...HACHEW!
Aw, bless me.
Oh my!
What is the meaning of this?
Well, uh, ya see, there
was this polo game and--
How could you let
a water main burst
on Canterlot's most
important day?
Hey, don't look at me.
Princess Twilight said
to stop working on it.
Well, what about these trees?
I ordered them trimmed to
avoid just such a situation!
Well, the princess
told me to stop, bub.
Why would the Princess make
such horrible decisions?
This all could have
been prevented!
Please! Everypony, listen!
I'm so sorry all this happened!
What are you apologizing for?
These were Princess
Twilight's awful decisions!
I'm about to blow my stack
on Princess Twilight,
I'll tell you that for nothin!
Yeah, me too!
I'll not let Princess Twilight
give Canterlot a bad name
in the eyes of Equestria!
Come on, everypony, let's go
give her a piece of our mind!
Wait, you've got it all wrong!
WAIT!
I mean... wait.
What is it now?
There's an angry mob here
that demands satisfaction!
It's just that, uh,
we don't want to wake
the Princess, do we?
Wake her? What?
You're tellin' me
that she's asleep?
Princess! We must speak at once!
SHE... IS...SLEEPING!
I'm glad you're here, Spike.
We've got a lot to do.
Do you know if the
water main was fixed?
Uh, you seem well rested.
I haven't slept like
that since I was a filly.
You haven't?
Well, at least I
got one thing right.
And it was the one thing
Cadance asked of me.
Maybe I did do a good job today.
Fancy Pants. What's wrong?
Don't play games
with me, Princess.
You know why I'm here!
Is this about the special
privileges you wanted?
Because this seems
a little extreme.
Special privileges?
The last thing on my mind
is special privileges!
What's going on, Spike?
Um...you needed to sleep!
And Princess Cadance told me
you weren't to be disturbed!
And there was this bird,
and well...long story short,
I made a few decisions
on your behalf.
"A few decisions?"
Well, maybe more than a few.
But I had good
intentions. Honest!
Until I didn't anymore.
I'm sorry, Twilight.
I guess I got a
little carried away.
It just felt so good to have
ponies caring about my opinions
on such important matters.
I guess I was just enjoying
feeling like a princess.
Well, Spike, one of the most
important things a princess
can do is realize when she's
made a mistake and fix it.
How do I do that?
You could start with them.
Uh, hi there, everypony.
So I guess I owe you all
a pretty big apology.
It's funny, here we
are at a Summit
that brings together ponies
from all across Equestria
and all I could think
about was myself.
You all came here to celebrate
the things that make
each of our cities so
unique and special.
But instead of getting
into the spirit of things
like all of you...
I used my friend's position
to make myself feel good.
The Canterlot ruby
goes here, old sport.
And ours goes
here, dontcha know.
Does this mean you forgive me?
Sure!
You know the whole idea of the
statue is that when each of us
plays our own small part, it
adds up to somethin' grand.
Quite! Just like
how all our cities
make up the beautiful
land of Equestria.
I hereby dedicate the
Citizens of Equestria statue
to everypony who
plays their part,
no matter how big or
how small.
Aw, come on!
Ah...ah...ahhhh--