As you've
all probably noticed,
it's been quite some time
since the map has sent us
on a mission of friendship.
Yeah, ever since
Starlight messed with it
to go back in time and
tried to change history.
Yes. Since then. But
as part of her studies,
Starlight's been
assisting me
and together we think
we've come up with a spell
that will get it
working again.
Woo-hoo! Oooh!
Well done!
Now, without further ado...
Oooh!
Fluttershy and
Twilight in Appleoosa!
NO! Me and Rainbow
Dash in Las Pegasus!
NO! Rainbow Dash and
Twilight in Yakyakistan!
NO! TWILIGHT AND TWILIGHT IN
TWILIGHT'S CASTLE!?
ME! ME! OH! ME!
AND RARITY! Oooooh I hope
it's some faraway place
that nopony has
gone before!
Well.
Maybe not TOO far away.
An adventure somewhere that
has modern conveniences
would be preferable.
CANTERLOT!
This is wonderful!
I can check the boutique!
Perhaps there will
be some social events
that we can attend!
I'll have to
pack extra outfits!
What will I wear!
You know, some
ponies get excited
about the
silliest things.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
We have muffins!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Now then. As far as
finding a friendship problem,
I suggest we start
at the castle
and begin to
question the proper--
Oh, Rarity, you don't
find a friendship problem.
It finds you! We just
need to go with the flow
and eventually KABLAM! We
get friendship problem'd
right between
the eyes!
Well, this is a
team effort
so if you feel we
should go with the flow,
then with the flow
we shall go!
Where is the flow
saying we should go?
You know Canterlot! What
do you think we should do?
Oh! Take your pick!
Culture, couture, cuisine!
Oh my. Well, it sounds
like your stomach
is saying we should
flow towards some lunch?
I know JUST where to go!
Restaurant Row!
The absolute best
place for fine dining
in all of Equestria.
Ooooooh, so many choices!
Where should we go? This
one? That one? Those ones?
Any establishments
that have this.
The three-hoof rating.
Um... whose hooves?
Why, Zesty Gourmand,
the queen of cuisine.
When it comes to food, she
is the ultimate authority
in Canterlot and
thus all Equestria!
She judges a restaurant
on cuisine, décor
and presentation.
Without her approval,
a restaurant simply
cannot survive.
What's so important
about her approval?
Zesty grew up around
fine dining
and everypony hangs
on her every word
when it comes
to cuisine.
WOW. Then the food
here must be AMAZING!
Lead the way, partner!
Wheeeeee!
Oh my. Such
presentation!
Oh.
Ah, yes. Very nice.
Ugh. Maybe I'm not in the
mood for... whatever this is.
Can we try someplace else?
Ugh. Maybe
one more stop?
Nope.
Maybe instead of trusting
somepony else's hooves,
I should pick
the next place?
Ugh! Very well.
The Tasty Treat.
It's very... rustic.
It looks like it
hasn't even been rated!
Thank goodness!
Are we sure
they're open?
Mmmm! It
smells open!
Oh! Are you here for lunch?
Yes indeedy!
I'm Saffron Masala, the chef
here at the Tasty Treat!
The most exotic
cuisine in Canterlot.
Would you like to hear
about the specials?
We're actually in
a bit of a hu--
YES, PLEASE!
We have a curried oatcake--
We'll take one!
And a grass sandwich that
has been marinated overnight
in a mustard
Dijon dressing.
How can we say
no to that?
A-And for you?
Oh! Me? Oh, I'm
fine. Thank you.
No rating.
Anyway they won't come.
Hiya! What's your name?
Coriander Cumin.
Are you a chef here, too?
My daughter cooks. I host.
Then why are you
stacking chairs?
Without customers, I have no
pony to host for. So, I stack.
Father! STOP IT!
Don't close up the restaurant
around our guests!
What does it matter?
When they leave,
nopony else will
be coming in!
Well, your attitude isn't
going to bring anyone in!
Can't you at least
pretend to be positive?
Sooooooo
goooooood!
You are doing enough
pretending for the both of us.
Nopony here wants
to try anything new.
I know when to
throw in the towel!
Um. Pinkie, perhaps we
should excuse ourselves.
Oh Rarity,
try this!
Oooh!
Maybe if you would listen
to my ideas for once--
Oh yes, I did not move
halfway across Equestria
for my daughter that
I NEVER listen to!
Rarity. I think that
friendship problem
just KABLAMMED us
right between the eyes.
These two? Oh I
don't know, darling.
The food IS excellent, but
I'm not sure there's much
you and I can do
to help them.
What would you
have me do?
We can't even get
Zesty Gourmand
to come to our
restaurant!
She took one look
at how empty it was
and said it wasn't
even worth rating!
THAT'S IT!
YES! Uh, what's it?
The flow HAS led us here!
THIS is our mission!
We are going to get
you a Three Hoof rating
and save your restaurant! I
can get Zesty Gourmand here.
And I can pack
this place with ponies!
Hmph! And how do you
intend to do such a thing?
Just leave it to us!
Father, will you PLEASE
stop packing things?
When the lovely
pony comes back
and says she couldn't
convince Zesty Gourmand
to come visit us, we will
need to pack all this up.
I'm just getting
a head start.
You really don't
know Rarity.
I've done it!
See?
It took all of my
charm and cajoling,
but I was able to
convince Zesty Gourmand
to come and try the food!
What is the catch?
Ah, yes. Well, um, there
IS a bit of a challenge.
The only time she can make
herself available is tonight.
Pfft! Oh yeah, right.
What is it?
Zesty rates a restaurant
on cuisine, decor
AND presentation. And she
has very specific tastes.
If she's coming tonight,
there IS quite a bit of work
that needs to get done.
Like what?
Oh a tweak here, a tuck there.
Some slight modifications
to the menu.
We just need the place to
feel more cosmopolitan.
Father, after Rarity went to
all of this trouble for us,
can't we at least try?
Why don't I stay
behind with Coriander
to get the restaurant
ready for Zesty's arrival.
You and Saffron can try
and drum up some business.
One packed restaurant
coming right up.
Coriander, I understand
your trepidation.
But I promise you, we will
get those hooves by making
this place feel just like
all of the other restaurants
on Restaurant Row!
I hope my father
doesn't drive Rarity crazy.
It'll be fine. Rarity's
going to make sure that
The Tasty Treat is the
most unique and beautiful
restaurant in Canterlot!
Not like all those stuffy
places on Restaurant Row!
♪ Here's what I know ♪
♪ If you want to succeed ♪
♪ You must follow the
trends; That's the key. ♪
♪ If you want to show ♪
♪ That you've got
what it takes ♪
♪ You must be what
they want you to be ♪
♪ Here's what I know ♪
♪ Your food is so good ♪
♪ The flavors so fancy and
free ♪
♪ You just need to show ♪
♪ That unique sense of taste ♪
♪ Go on, be yourself,
let them see! ♪
♪ It's gonna work ♪
♪ I know it's gonna work ♪
♪ It's gonna work out
just fine; trust me. ♪
♪ It's gonna work ♪
♪ I swear it's gonna work ♪
♪ It's gonna work out
just fine you'll see. ♪
♪ You need to change ♪
♪ If you want to compete ♪
♪ But fear not, for
I know what to do. ♪
♪ I know it feels strange ♪
♪ But trust me when we're done ♪
♪ We'll make sure that
you're a hit too. ♪
♪ Don't ever change ♪
♪ Being different is good ♪
♪ Don't let what others
do be your cue! ♪
♪ Never rearrange ♪
♪ Cause somepony said
you should ♪
♪ Just trust your heart,
it will know what to do ♪
♪ It's gonna work ♪
♪ I know it's gonna work ♪
♪ It's gonna work out
just fine trust me. ♪
♪ It's gonna work ♪
♪ I swear it's gonna work ♪
♪ It's gonna work out
just fine you'll see. ♪
♪ Be unique! ♪
♪ Just be the same! ♪
♪ Trust your heart! ♪
♪ You'll make your name! ♪
♪ We'll help you every
step of the way! ♪
♪ Because we know
what you need to do ♪
♪ and you should know it too. ♪
♪ It's gonna work ♪
♪ I know it's gonna work ♪
♪ It's gonna work out
just fine trust me. ♪
♪ It's gonna work ♪
♪ I swear it's gonna work ♪
♪ It's gonna work out
just fine you'll see! ♪
The day is almost over
and we haven't found
anyponies! What will we do?
Try harder! FILLIES
AND GENTLECOLTS!
Check out the super stupendous
and amazing cuisine
of the Tasty Treat! GRAND
RE-OPENING TONIGHT!
How many Hooves
does it have?
No hooves yet, but
hopefully soon!
Well, when it gets
rated, let us know!
Ughh! Stupid hooves!
Oh, look at this, hon!
Oh, The Tasty Treat.
Do you think that's
a restaurant, Sugar?
Yes! Yes it IS!
We came to Canterlot
from Winnieapolis
to be adventurous!
But so far the food in all
these hoity- toity places
tastes like somepony cooked up
nuthin' with a side of nuthin!
Well, please, come
try The Tasty Treat.
I think it's going
to be exactly
what you're
looking for!
This is
going to be exactly
what Zesty is looking for!
Father, we're ba--
Rarity. What did
you do?
Welcome to The Tasty Treat.
You can eat here if you
want. Or not. Who cares?
I know! Isn't it perfect?
Zesty is sure to love it!
I thought we were trying to
make this the most unique
and beautiful
restaurant in Canterlot.
Not make it exactly like
every other restaurant!
We want
to help our friends
by getting them three hooves.
That will only happen
if this IS like every
other restaurant.
Father, what is this?
NOT THAT! ANYTHING BUT THAT!
This is what we must cook
if we want to succeed here!
This isn't what I wanted!
I wanted Canterlot
to like US for US!
Rarity, how could you
ruin the restaurant!
Ah! We've
helped SAVE the restaurant!
Now where are the
other guests?
How many other
ponies are coming?
Two.
Just TWO? I thought you
said you could pack a place
with ponies no matter what!
YOU said you would make
the restaurant better
so I guess we both didn't know
what we were talking about!
ZESTY GOURMAND!
Everypony! Places!
Welcome to the Tasty Treat.
What can I get you
this evening?
I hardly think it matters.
But by all means, try
your best to impress.
Well, we'll both try the
special this evening,
maybe with a little
kick to it, eh?
Yeah, we've been craving
some food with actual taste.
Saffron Masala!
What are you doing?
I'm trying to save
our reputations.
I've given it at least
a little bit of flavor.
No, no, no, no! But that's
not what Zesty wants!
What kind of food expert
DOESN'T want flavor?
That's insane!
I'm taking this out there.
No! Zesty will hate it!
You are going to
RUIN this for them!
No! I'm trying to fix
it after YOU ruined it!
Nooooooooooo!
I think we are done here.
Zesty! Please wait.
Allow me to explain.
Rarity. When it comes to
fashion, you are adequate.
But take some advice
from a friend.
Keep your opinions
out of restaurants.
Substandard food, laughable
service and I would think
even YOU could recognize
that the decor here
is trying desperately
while desperately failing.
Recommending a disreputable
place such as this
could do serious damage
to your social standing.
Disreputable?
You mean a place with food
that actually tastes good?
Anypony can throw
ingredients together
and create an obvious taste
that uncultured ponies
like those two can register.
Hey!
But it takes a TRUE
culinary artist
to create a subtle taste.
The barest hint
of a sensation.
That's what I bring to
Canterlot. That's art.
I'm so embarrassed.
I don't know that there are
words to adequately express
how truly sorry we are.
The worst has happened. No use
crying over spilled food now.
Here, this always cheered
me up when I was younger.
My spicy flat
noodle soup!
Mmm! Oh my, this is
truly delightful.
This is the best thing
you've made so far.
And I thought the food
before was the best!
That's all I've ever
wanted to do, Father.
Make food for the
ponies of Canterlot
like the food we made
together when I was younger.
It has been so long since
we've cooked together.
Remember how you used
to hide the ingredients
you did not like.
You know what?
Who cares what
some stuffy unicorn
thinks of the food
here. It's exquisite.
That's true.
And you don't need three
silly hooves in your window
to prove it.
That's double true!
You just need ponies in
here to give it a chance.
Ponies that will tell
everypony else in Canterlot
that the Tasty Treat is
the best food in the city!
THAT'S TRUE TIMES THREE!
But without Zesty's approval,
nopony will even try our food.
Oohoho, yes they will.
Pinkie! We ARE the
perfect team for this;
we were just doing
the wrong jobs.
I will go out and
bring the crowd.
You stay here and make sure
this place is every bit
as unique and rustic as it
was the moment we walked in.
And what about us?
You two? You are going to
cook. Make whatever you want.
And make a lot of it. I
intend to bring a crowd!
Would the owner of one of the
premier boutiques in Canterlot
put her stamp of
approval on something
that wasn't fabulous?
It's almost time.
Is everypony ready for
the grand re-re-opening?
Before we open, my father and
I just wanted to say thank you
for all of your help.
We've both been so stressed
about the restaurant
succeeding that we forgot
what it was we loved about it
in the first place.
Cooking is something we
used to love to do together.
No matter what happens next,
thank you for
reminding us of that.
Oh you guys! GROUP HUG!
Now come on! We've
got a party to throw!
Oooh! Wow! It
smells really good!
Welcome to the Tasty Treat!
Make yourselves comfortable!
Please, feel free
to sample the food!
What's this?
What is everypony doing here?
This place has no hooves.
It is not in keeping
with the level of cuisine
that I have set
for Canterlot.
Nopony told you this
place was acceptable.
Uh, Rarity and her friend said
it was good. They told us.
They told you? And who are
they to tell you anything?
Rarity can tell you what hats
to wear with which skirts.
Her friend can tell you how
to maintain a tragic look
for a frizzy mane.
They can't tell you
what food you can eat.
No, we can't. And
neither can you.
Nopony has the right to tell
these ponies what to think.
Zesty, you have very specific--
And very strange!
Yes and very strange
opinions about food.
And that's your right.
But just because you like
your food a certain way,
there is no reason
to tell these ponies
that they need to
do the same.
Rarity is right!
I for one think the
food here is delicious.
I own the Smoked Oat
on Restaurant Row!
I hate the food we make!
From now on, it's all
smoked, basted and grilled!
This food is an inspiration!
I own the Bake Shop!
I'm going to bake my
mother's Bundt cake
the way she made
it! Full of flavor!
Yes! Yeah!
Zesty, are you sure you
wouldn't like to try the food?
Ignoring a unique and fresh
establishment such as this
could do serious damage
to your social standing.
Thank you so much!
You are both truly amazing.
Nothing can stop the dynamic
duo of Pinkie and Rarity!