Elements of Harmony...
See: Mare in the Moon?
But that's just an old ponies' tale!
She will bring about nighttime eternal!
It's imperative that
the Princess is told right away.
See? I knew she would wanna
take immediate action.
My dear Twilight. There is more to
a young pony's life than studying.
Make some friends!
All the ponies in this town are CRAZY!
I hope the Princess was right.
She's gone!
Oh no. Nightmare Moon!
Seize her! Only she knows
where the Princess is!
Stand back, you foals!
Come back here!
Nighttime? Forever?
Where's she going?
We gotta stop Nightmare...!
You've been up all night, Spike.
You are a baby dragon after all.
Elements, elements, elements...
How can I stop Nightmare Moon
without the Elements of Harmony?!
And just what are the Elements of Harmony?!
And how did you know about
Nightmare Moon, huh?
Are you a spy?
Simmer down, Sally. She ain't no spy.
But she sure knows what's going on.
Don't you, Twilight?
I read all about the
prediction of Nightmare Moon.
Some mysterious objects called the Elements of
Harmony are the only things that can stop her.
But I don't know what they are. Where to
find them. I don't even know what they do!
The Elements of Harmony: A Reference Guide.
How did you find that?!
IT WAS UNDER "E"!
"There are six Elements of Harmony,
but only five are known..."
"Kindness, Laughter, Generosity,
Honesty and Loyalty."
"The sixth is a complete mystery."
"It is said, the last known
location of the five Elements..."
"...was in the ancient castle of the royal
pony sisters. It is located in what is now..."
The Everfree Forest!
Whee! Let's go!
Not so fast!
Look, I appreciate the offer, but I'd
really rather do this on my own.
No can do, sugar cube. We sure ain't lettin' any
friend of ours goin' to that creepy place alone.
We're stickin' to you like
caramel to candy apple.
Especially if there's candy apples in there.
What? Those things are good!
So none of you have been in here before?
Heavens no! Just look at it - it's dreadful!
And it ain't natural. Folk say
it don't work the same as Equestria.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nopony knows. You know why?
Rainbow! Quit it!
Cause everypony who's ever come in...
...has never... come... OUT!
Fluttershy! Quick!
Oh my goodness, oh my goodness...
Hold on! I'm a-comin'!
Applejack! What do I do?!
Let go.
-Are you crazy?!
-No, I ain't. I promise you'll be safe.
That's not true!
Now listen here. What I'm sayin'
to you is the honest truth.
Let go and you'll be safe.
Sorry girls. I'm not used to holding
anything more than a bunny or two.
And once Pinkie and Rarity
were saved, WHOA...
Me and Fluttershy loop-de-looped around and WHAM!
Got you right in a nick of time.
Yes, Rainbow, I was there.
And I'm very grateful, but we gotta...
A manticore!
We've gotta get past him!
Take that, you ruffian!
MY HAIR!
Wait...
YEEHAW! Get along, little doggie!
-All yours, partner.
-I'm on it!
Wait...!
Rainbow!
WAIT!!!
Shhh... It's okay.
Oh, you poor, poor little baby.
Little?
Now this might hurt for juuust a second.
Fluttershy!
Are you just a little baby kitty, aren't you?
Yesh you are, yesh you are.
How did you know about the thorn?
I didn't. Sometimes we all just
need to be shown a little kindness.
My eyes need a rest from all this icky muck.
Well, I didn't mean that literally.
That ancient ruin could be right in front
of our faces and we wouldn't even know it!
Oh wait. I think I stepped in somethin'.
It's just mud.
Pinkie, what are you doing?! Run!
Oh, girls. Don't you see...?
When I was a little filly and
the sun was going dooown...
Tell me she's not...
The darkness and the shadows, they
would always make me frooown...
She is.
I'd hide under my pillow
from what I thought I saw,
But Granny Pie said that wasn't the way
to deal with fears at aaall!
Then what is?
She said: Pinkie, you gotta stand up tall,
learn to face your fears.
You'll see that they can't hurt you,
just laugh to make them disappear.
Sooo, giggle at the ghostly!
Guffaw at the grossly!
Crack up at the creepy!
Whoop it up with the weepy!
Chortle at the cooky!
Snortle at the spooky!
And tell that big dumb scary face
to take a hike and leave you alone...
Andifhethinkshecanscareyouthenhesgotanotherthink
comingandtheveryideaofsuchathingjustmakesyouwanna...
LAAAUGH!
Where are we gonna cross *this*?
What a world, what a world...!
Excuse me, sir. Why are you crying?
Well, I don't know. I was just sitting
here, minding my own business...
...when this tacky little cloud of
purple smoke just whisked past me...
...and tore a half of my beloved mustache...
...CLEAN OFF!
And now I look simply horrid!
-Oh, gimme a break!
-That's what all the fuss is about?
Why, of course it is!
How can you be so insensitive?
Oh, just look at him.
Such lovely luminescent scales...!
I know.
...and your expertly coiffed mane...!
Oh, I know, I know.
...your fabulous manicure...!
It's so true!
All ruined without your beautiful mustache!
It's true, I'm hideous!
I simply cannot let such a crime
against fabulosity go uncorrected!
What did you do that for?!
Rarity, what are you...
My mustache! How wonderful!
You look smashing!
Oh, Rarity! Your beautiful tail!
Oh. It's fine, my dear. Short tails are
in the season.
Besides, it'll grow back.
So would the mustache...
We can cross now! Let's go...!
Allow me.
There it is! The ruin that holds
the Elements of Harmony! We made it!
Twilight! Wait for us!
We're almost there!
What's with you and falling off cliffs today?
Now what?!
-Duh!
-Oh yeah!
-Rainbow...! Rainbow...!
-Who's there?
I ain't scared of you! Show yourself!
We've been eagerly awaiting the arrival
of the best flyer in Equestria.
-Who?
-Why you, of course!
Really?! I mean... Oh yeah! Me!
Hey, uh, you wouldn't mind telling
the Wonderbolts that, would ya?
'Cos I've been trying to get
into that group for, like, ever!
No, Rainbow Dash. We want you to join us!
The Shadowbolts!
We're the greatest aerial
team in the Everfree Forest.
And soon we will be the greatest in all Equestria.
But first, we need a captain.
-The most magnificent...
-Yep!
-...swiftest...
-Yes!
-...bravest flyer in all the land!
-Yes! It's all true!
We need...
...you!
Sign me up!
Just let me tie this bridge real
quick and then we have a deal.
No! It's them or us!
Rainbow! What's taking so long?
Oh no.
Rainbow!
Don't listen to them!
Well...?
You...
Thank you! For the offer, I mean.
But... I'm afraid I have to say no.
See? I'd never leave my friends hanging!
Wow.
Come on, Twilight! Isn't this
what you've been waitin' for?
The Elements of Harmony! We've found them!
Careful... Careful...!
One, two, three, four...
There's only five!
Where's the sixth?
The book said: "When the five are present..."
"...a spark will cause
the sixth Element to be revealed."
What in the hay is that supposed to mean?
I'm not sure, but I have an idea.
Stand back. I don't know what will happen.
Come on now, y'all. She needs to concentrate.
Twilight!
The Elements!
-Twilight! Where are you?!
-Look!
Come on!
You're kidding. You're kidding, right?
Just one spark...
Come on, come on!
No! No!
But... where's the sixth Element?!
You little foal! Thinking you could defeat me!?
Now you will never see your Princess.
Or your sun!
THE NIGHT WILL LAST FOREVER!
You think you can destroy
the Elements of Harmony just like that?
Well, you're wrong.
Because the spirits of
the Elements of Harmony are right HERE!
What?
Applejack, who reassured me when I was
in doubt represents the spirit of...
Honesty!
Fluttershy, who tamed the manticore with
her compassion represents the spirit of...
Kindness!
Pinkie Pie, who banished fear by giggling in
the face of danger represents the spirit of...
Laughter!
Rarity, who calmed a sorrowful serpent with
a meaningful gift represents the spirit of...
Generosity!
And Rainbow Dash, who could not abandon
her friends for her own heart's desire
represents the spirit of...
Loyalty!
The spirits of these five ponies got us
through every challenge you threw at us!
You still don't have the sixth Element!
The spark didn't work!
But it did. A different kind of spark.
I felt it the very moment I realized how
happy I was to hear you... To see you...
How much I cared about you!
The spark ignited inside me
when I realized that you all...
...are my friends!
You see, Nightmare Moon, when those
Elements are ignited by the...
...the spark that resides in the heart of us all...
...it creates the sixth Element: The Element of...
Magic!
NOOOOOO!!!
My head...
Everypony okay?
Oh, thank goodness!
Why Rarity, it's so lovely!
I know! I'll never part with it again!
No. Your necklace. It looks
just like your cutie mark.
So does yours!
Look at mine! Look at mine!
Oooh yeah!
Gee, Twilight! I though you were
just spoutin' a lot of hooey.
But I reckon we really do represent
the elements of friendship.
Indeed you do.
Princess Celestia!
Twilight Sparkle, my faithful student.
I knew you could do it.
But... you told me it was all an old pony tale.
I told you that you needed to
make some friends. Nothing more.
I saw the signs of Nightmare Moon's return...
...and I knew it was you who had
the magic inside to defeat her.
But you could not unleash it until you
let true friendship into your heart.
Now if only another will as well.
Princess Luna...
It is been a thousand years since
I have seen you like this.
Time to put our differences behind us.
We were meant to rule together, little sister.
Sister?!
Will you accept my friendship?
I'm so sorry! I missed you so much, big sister!
I've missed you, too.
...Hey! You know what this calls for?
A PARTY!
Why so glum, my faithful student?
Are you not happy that Equestria is complete?
And you can return to your studies in Canterlot?
That's just it. Just when I learned how wonderful
it is to have friends, I have to leave them.
Spike! Take a note, please.
I, Princess Celestia, hereby decree...
...that the unicorn Twilight Sparkle shall
take on a new mission for Equestria.
She must continue to study
the magic of friendship.
She must report to me her findings
from her new home in Ponyville.
Oh thank you, Princess Celestia!
I'll study harder than ever before!
Isn't this exciting? AreyouexcitedcauseImexcited
Iveneverbeensoexcitedwellexceptforthetime
whenIGASPbutImeanreally...
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000