Yeah!
Who?
Oh. It's you, Owloysius.
Come on! Try and keep up.
Winona? I mean...
Winona's head?
Um... Is this weird or is it just me?
Angel?! Gummy?!
Okay. This is officially beyond weird now
and moved right on down to freakytown.
Sincerest apologies, Rainbow,
if our pets were bothering you.
Say you're sorry, Opal.
She's sorry.
What are you all doing out here?
Why, we always round up our critters for
our regular pony pet playdate in this park.
Uh... You do?
Same time every week.
I thought you knew.
You didn't know? She didn't know?
Well, we initially planned on inviting
Rainbow, of course, except...
We were totally gonna
invite you, Rainbow.
Then Twilight remembered that
you don't even have a pet.
And Rarity remembered that you really
like taking naps in the afternoon.
So Applejack figured you wouldn't
missing out on anything anyway.
And Fluttershy and I nodded
our heads in agreement like this.
Oh... Please don't be mad at us.
Oh... I'm not mad.
You all are right. Not much point
of a pony pet playdate for me...
...if I'm a pony without a pet, right?
Exactly.
So, if'n you'll excuse us...
Hey! Now wait a minute.
Just because I don't have a pet now
doesn't mean I never want a pet.
Oh! Oh, really?
You really want a pet? Really?
Cause I've got so many
wonderful choices at my house.
Oh, and I know you'll just love them.
And they'll love you! Oh!
And you'll be best friends
forever and ever!
Now, Rainbow, my dear,
I cannot express my delight.
It's abundantly clear
That somewhere round here
Is the pet that will suit you just right.
I can't wait to get started,
but first let me set a few rules.
It's of utmost importance
the pet that I get
Is something that's awesome and cool.
Awesome and cool. Got it!
I have so many wonderful choices,
just wait, you will see.
I need something real fast like a bullet
to keep up with me.
Sure! How 'bout a bunny?
They're cutesy and wootsy and quick as can be.
"Cutesy"? "Wootsy"?
Have you even met me?
Rainbow, have faith!
You see, I will bet you.
Somewhere round here
is the pet that will get you.
Come on, the sky is the limit.
Sky is good. I'd like it to fly.
Really? Because I think this wittle puddy
tat has your name written all over it.
Yes, he does! Aw, look, he likes you.
Pass.
I have so many wonderful choices
for you to decide.
There are otters and seals
with massive appeal...
Otters and seals do not fly.
Maybe not, but I've seen
this particular seal...
...catch ten feet of air
when he breaches the water.
That's it. I'm outta here.
Wait! There must be a pet here,
that will fit that ticket.
How 'bout a ladybug or a cute cricket?
Bigger! And cooler!
Bigger. Cooler. Right.
I've got just the thing in that tree. Dash...
Meet your new fabulous pet squirrelee!
It's just a squirrel.
Not just any squirrel. A flying squirrel!
Yeah... So, like I was saying...
Fluttershy, pal, this won't cut it.
I need a pet to keep up with me.
Something awesome, something flying...
...with coolness that defies gravity!
I'm sensing you want
an animal that can fly.
You think?
I have plenty of wonderful
creatures who soar in the sky.
Like a sweet hummingbird
or a giant monarch butterfly.
Better. But cooler.
I see. How 'bout an owl?
Or a wasp, or a toucan?
There's so many wonderful
creatures the likes of that.
There are falcons and eagles.
They are both quite regal.
Or perhaps what you need
is a dark and mysterious bat?
Now you're talking!
But instead of just one standout
now that's too many.
So many choices
and such riches a plenty.
Not a bad problem to have,
if you ask me.
The bat would be awesome,
but the wasp I'm digging too.
You have something
in a yellow striped bat?
No.
I've got a hot pink flamingo
Just dying to meet you.
What to do? What to do?
A prize! That's it!
There's really just one way...
...to find out which animal's best.
Hold a contest of speed,
agility and guts...
...that will put each pet to the test!
Don't forget style,
that should be considered.
Then we'll know for sure
who's best of the litter.
-The one who's as awesome as cool...
-...just like me!
Can't settle for less, cause I'm the best,
so a contest we will see!
Who's the number one greatest,
perfectest pet in the world for me!
May the race begin!
And may the best pet win!
Shh...!
So, you all think you've got what
it takes to be my pet, do ya?
Well, we'll just see about that.
If any of you don't think
you can handle it...
...bow out now before you humiliate
yourself in front of your peers.
This competition isn't for the weak.
You'd better be prepared
to step up your game!
YOU CALL THAT FLAPPING?!
That's better.
There's only room on team
just for one of you...
...and my future pet needs to
be able to take it to the extreme.
Any questions?
I got one. Does she understand
what a pet really needs?
Yeah. Like care and attention.
Love and affection.
Ugh! And breath mints!
Now you just pay attention
and try your best and...
Seriously, Fluttershy. The turtle?
What did you bring that thing here for?
Technically he's a tortoise.
And he's always dreamed
of being somepony's pet.
He just wants a chance to compete.
He won't get in the way.
You won't even know he's here.
No.
Oh. Just let him try.
But there's no way
he can possibly keep up.
Look at 'im.
-It won't hurt to let him try.
-But...
Just let him try!
Uh. Fine.
But don't say I didn't warn you!
This isn't a game, you know.
All right. Now these games
will determine which one of you...
...has the most important qualities
I'm looking for in a pet.
Speed!
Agility!
Guts!
Style!
Coolness!
Awesomeness!
And radicalness!
Aren't those all the same thing?
You would think that, Twilight.
And that's why you would
never qualify to be my pet.
Speed!
On your marks...
Get set...
Sorta speedy.
Not speedy.
Pretty speedy.
Could be more speedy.
Yeah! That's speed!
That's just sad.
Agility!
Sorta agile.
Not agile.
Pretty agile.
Could be more agile.
Wanna know the opposite
of agility? That.
Yeah, baby! Now that's
what I call agility!
Don't leave me hangin'!
I'm gonna have to shave a point
off your score for that.
Okay! Which of you has the guts to try and
get Opal's favorite toy away from her?
Now that takes guts!
Style.
Any pet of mine's gotta look good.
'Cause you gotta make me look good.
Coolness.
Sorta cool.
Not cool.
Pretty cool.
Could be cooler.
Not what I had in mind.
I can't hear you!
Now that's a cool sound!
Sorta awesome.
Not awesome.
Could be more awesome.
Hohoho yeah! That is awesome!
Uh... You did that already.
That's pretty much all you can do, huh?
Whoa...
That was truly awesome!
But I'm afraid this is
the radicalness competition, so...
...I'm gonna have to
take some points off.
Listen, turtle...
-Tortoise!
-Whatever!
You had your fun, but I think
you and I both know...
...who made the cut and who didn't.
You didn't.
I mean... A for effort and everything...
You gave it your best shot.
Maybe I've got a gold star sticker
around here somewhere you can have.
But seriously, go home.
You're starting to creep me out.
So... Anyway...
You're all outstanding competitors.
But there can be only one of you,
who's number one.
So the final, tie-breaking
contest is going to be...
(Pause for dramatic effect)
A race against...
...ME!
...through Ghastly Gorge!
DUN DUN DUUUN!
Gesundheit.
Actually, Ghastly Gorge isn't scary.
It's fun!
I've flown though it
a million times myself...
...so obviously I'll be
at the front of the pack.
But whichever of you make it
across the finish line with me...
...will have proven
he can keep up with me...
...and will have earned the honor
(and glory) of getting to be my pet.
Ready?
...setgo!
Try to keep up!
Can't catch me!
♪♪♪♪♪
Come on, slowpokes!
You wanna win, doncha?
;-P
Oh! I forgot to tell you!
Watch out for the quarray eels.
They don't like you when
you get too close to their nests.
Like this.
:-O
Easy-peasy, one too greasy.
Right, guys?
AVALANCHE!
Hey!
Come on...
No! Wait! Come back! Don't leave me!
I'm the one who's supposed to win!
I don't wanna end up stuck here...
...forever.
Oh no. Nonono. Thi...
This can't be happening.
Forever is way too long
to be trapped in Ghastly Gorge.
I mean... it's like...
...forever!
SOMEPONY! ANYPONY! HELP ME!!!
Woohoo!
My prayers have been answered!
Oh, thankyouthankyouthank...
YOU?!
Oh no!
Now I'm not only gonna
be stuck here forever...
...I'm gonna be stuck here forever with
the most annoying turtle in the world!
I'm doomed. DOOMED, I tell you!
Something's not right here.
Where's Rainbow Dash?
Great gallopin' galoshes!
There's been an avalanche in there!
Rainbow!
Wait! Look!
It's the turtle!
-Tortoise!
-Whatever.
And he's carrying something on his back.
It's Rainbow Dash!
It's her! It's Rainbow!
Maybe we'd better go meet them halfway.
Way to go, little guy.
Oh, thank goodness
you're not hurt, Rainbow.
Just my pride.
I certainly hope all of this
dreadful dust was worth it...
It sure was if'n it means
Rainbow gets to have...
...her own little critter, just like
the rest of us, from now on.
Uh... thanks.
What you did... I owe you one.
Rainbow! Your new pet is
over here waiting for you!
Oh. Right. Yeah. That.
What's the matter?
You got your perfect pet, right?
The best of the best,
like you wanted, remember?
It can fly and it's not a squirrel.
Should we sing about it again?
A falcon sure looks
good on you, Rainbow.
Easy, fella. Nothing to be afraid of.
A falcon sure does look cool.
He's absolutely everything
I wanted in a pet.
Yay?
But I said whoever crosses the finish
line *with me* gets to be my pet.
You did! You did say that!
She did say that! That was the rule!
And the only racer, who crossed
the finish line with me...
...was the one, who stopped
to save me when I needed help.
The tortoise!
But what about the...?
Would you look at that.
He even smiles slow.
Spike, take a letter.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"I used to think that the most important
traits to look for in a pet..."
"...or any best friend, were all
physical, competitive abilities."
"But now I can see how short-sighted
and shallow that was."
"Today I learned what the most
important quality really is."
"A certain kind of spirit.
A stick-to-it-iveness."
"A never-give-up, can-do attitude,
that's the mark of a real winner."
"And this tortoise has it."
Tenacity.
Gesundheit.
"You just can't stop that little guy."
He's like a... like a...
...tank!
But Rainbow. You didn't want
a pet that couldn't fly...
...because it would keep you grounded
and hold you back, remember?
Come on, Tank! We're gonna be late
for our very first pony pet playdate!
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000