I love it when Princess Celestia
comes to Ponyville!
I got my hooves shined
just like Rarity for the occasion.
- Ya like?
- I certainly do!
I'm surprised she's not here yet.
I wonder what's taking so long?
And where are
Applejack and Fluttershy?
Fluttershy's detained helping Applejack
with a mishap at Sweet Apple Acres.
They'll be along.
I still don't get why
the Princess would be so late.
She's bringing
an important visitor.
That could be part of it.
A visitor who's important and slow.
Maybe it's somepony
so terribly important,
she still had many more terribly important
things to do before she got here.
Maybe the visitor has a deer antler,
a goat leg, a bat wing, and a snake tail!
Yeah, right. That's Discord.
Why in the
wide-wide world of Equestria
would Princess Celestia
bring along someone like that?
Maybe you should ask her!
Season 3 | Episode 10
Keep Calm and Flutter On
Subbed by GrayJeager
Fr.Jeager@gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
With all due respect,
Princess Celestia,
how could you bring Discord here?!
Your majesty.
I'm fully aware that
the last time Discord was here,
he created serious havoc.
If by "serious havoc"
you mean
"turning Ponyville into
the chaos capital of the world".
And tricking us all into being
the opposite of our true selves.
And making yummy delicious
chocolate milk rain all over the place,
without a single dollop of whipped cream
to go with it anywhere in sight!
Not a single dollop!
Yes, I understand.
But I have use for Discord's magic,
if it can be reformed
to serve good instead of evil.
This is why
I've brought Discord here,
because I believe you are the ponies
who can help him do just that.
This will never work!
This is a disaster!
How will we control him?!
We're doomed!
Need I remind you
that you are the ponies
who turned him back into stone
like this in the first place?
I suppose we can just use
the Elements of Harmony
against him again
if he gets out of hand...
We probably need a volunteer
to run away from here
right away to get them.
- I'll do it!
- No need, Spike.
I have them right here.
And I've cast a spell so Discord
can't take them and hide them again.
Now where is Fluttershy?
I believe she may know best
how to begin reforming Discord.
Fluttershy? Really?
- What's he goin' on about now?
- Good news.
Mr. Beaverton Beaverteeth has agreed
to take his dam apart and move it.
Well, it's about time.
My apple trees are so waterlogged
I can practically hear 'em gargle!
But he says first you'll have
to apologize for calling him...
"a nuisance".
Apologize?!
He's lucky I didn't call him a varmint!
Mr. Beaverton Beaverteeth!
Such a language!
Fine, fine.
I apologize.
Thanks, Fluttershy.
Don't know what
I would've done without ya.
Glad I could help.
Hey, slackers!
Double time it over to Ponyville,
would ya?
We're all waiting on you!
I realize that this is a tall order,
but I wouldn't ask
if I weren't confident
you could get him to use magic
obediently of his own free will.
And you really think
I'll know best how to do that?
I do.
Now, I must return to Canterlot
for Equestria's royal summit.
You may release Discord when ready.
Okay, ponies,
guess it's time to get started.
Let's just hope
this releasing spell works.
Or... let's not.
We'd best keep our elements on
at all times until further notice.
Check!
Well, it's about time somepony
got me out of that prison block.
What a relief!
What do you think you're doing?!
Why, stretching of course.
When you're a creature of chaos,
stone bodysuits aren't
your typical go-to fashion choice.
Make that bunny cute again! Now!
He is adorable the way he is.
You know what else is adorable?
You ponies truly believe
that you can reform me,
and that you're putting your faith
in this one here to make it happen.
Makes me wanna pinch
your little horsey cheeks...
How'd you know about that?!
Being turned to stone doesn't keep me
from hearing every word Celestia says.
Although I admit
it makes rolling my eyes a challenge.
Well, unless you want us
to turn you back to stone,
you'll zap those animals back
the way they were pronto!
Oh, you wouldn't dare
turn me back to stone
and risk disappointing
your precious princess.
Try us, "Dip-cord"!
You think you can treat
poor defenseless animals like that
and get away with it?!
You go, Fluttershy!
You'd best watch your step, buster,
or I'll give you the Stare!
The Stare?
Oh no, please, not that!
Anything but
your disapproving eyeballs!
Oh no! No no no, stop!
Stop! I can't take it any more!
I'll do whatever you say!
Because...
You are hilarious!
If it turns out we need to use
our elements against you,
I'm sure we can convince Princess Celestia
it was for a good reason!
I suppose that's correct.
Oopsie!
Well, it looks like I know
where I'll be crashing
while I'm being "reformed"...
With you, Fluttershy.
Oh, dear.
He may be horrible,
but that doesn't mean
we have to act the same way.
We should at least
try to be hospitable.
You don't mind giving up
your favorite spot on the couch,
do you, Angel Bunny?
Oh, I'm sorry about Angel.
Are you alright?
Oh, yes. Thank you,
Fluttershy, for your concern.
If only your pony friends
could be as considerate...
Don't listen to him, Fluttershy!
He's just trying to drive a wedge
between us, like he always does.
Now why in the world would
I ever try to do a thing like that?
So we can't unite and use the Elements
of Harmony against you, that's why!
I never thought of that...
You big liar!
Now, look who's a liar.
Anyone can plainly see
that I'm not big at all.
Oops.
There, all better.
I can't watch...
We'll be outside.
You sure you're okay with this?
I know it's not gonna be easy,
but Princess Celestia's counting on me.
And I think
I actually know what to do.
You do?
I think the key is to befriend him.
Being kind to him and letting him
be my house guest
is probably
the best way to do that.
- And you really think that'll work?
- I think it's worth a try.
Okay, but if you need us,
all you need to do is whisper "help",
and we'll be back here
with our Elements.
So watch that
goat-legged step of yours, pal!
What?! Look at me!
I'm practically reformed already.
She's really alright
with him staying there?
That's what she said.
Personally, I think we should
come up with a backup plan,
in case this whole "befriending"
business doesn't work out.
Rainbow Dash is right.
This is Discord we're talking about,
girls.
It wouldn't be a bad idea
to have another trick up our sleeves.
And I think I know just the trick.
Discord? Oh, there you are.
Listen, Discord, I just want
to make sure you know that
if there's anything I can do to--
Are you eating... paper?
Am I? How odd of me.
Well, um...
I'm just heading out, so,
make yourself at home while I'm gone.
Bye-bye, have a nice time!
Everything is fine here, bye bye...
You like carrots, Angel?
I'm playing your owner for a fool!
How d'ya like them carrots?
That's weird.
The spell I had in mind isn't in here.
Spike, where are the other books
I asked you to pull?
Right here, Twilight.
I really want to have a
reforming spell up and running pronto.
But what if he makes the
Elements of Harmony disappear
like he did last time?
Princess Celestia cast a spell
protecting them, remember?
What's wrong?
Princess Celestia didn't cast a spell
protecting our books!
Everywhere I thought
I'd find the reforming spell...
Are you sure
this isn't overdoing?
You said to make myself at home
while you were gone,
but I wouldn't want
to overstep my bounds.
I did say that, so...
if this makes you more comfortable,
by all means, please feel free.
Well, it does, very much so.
You're so very kind,
my dear Fluttershy.
I always knew that you were
the understanding one,
not like those nasty friends of yours.
My friends aren't nasty!
Of course you'd say that,
it just goes to show
how understanding you truly are.
You know,
I think Princess Celestia is right
when she singles you out
as the one who could reform me.
You're off to such a good start
I'm seriously considering actually
being reformed.
Fluttershy!
Fluttershy, can you hear me?!
Goodness! I hear Twilight!
Fluttershy, what's going on?
Are you okay?!
We're fine, everything's going great.
Isn't it, Angel?
We've come to get you away
from Discord!
He's just terrible and,
from the looks of it,
completely out of control!
Oh, but you're wrong!
We're making great progress!
Seriously?!
I'm earning his trust by giving him
a little space to be himself.
Hate to break it to you,
but he used that "space to be himself"
to tear out all the reforming spells
from the library!
That does explain the paper eating...
He ate them?!
But we aren't gonna need a spell.
He's already really
considering being reformed!
He said so.
And you believed him?!
If I'm going to be his friend,
I have to start by giving him
the benefit of the doubt!
Tell you what. Bring all the ponies over
for a dinner party this evening,
and I bet his manners
will have really improved by then.
I'll even get him to put the cottage
back on the ground first.
Alright. Dinner it is...
I can't believe we're having
a dinner party with Discord!
This evening
is sure to be a disaster.
Glad I didn't bother wearing
my fanciest outfit.
Fluttershy thinks this is the way
to reform Discord
and asked us
to give it a chance.
Oh, our pony guests!
We're so delighted
that you've come.
Please, do come in.
See what a beautiful job
he did helping?
Discord set the entire table himself.
I'm so proud.
May I take your...
hats, ladies?
Hang on to your elements, girls.
It's gonna be a bumpy night.
As you all know,
Princess Celestia hoped
we'd help Discord use his magic
for good, instead of evil.
Pinkie Pie, care for some gravy?
You bet!
Allow me.
Oh, what a cute little
gravy boat you are!
Yes you are! Yes you are!
That's one creepy little
gravy boat if you ask me.
Oh, come on now, Dashie,
you're not even giving this a chance.
Hey! That's hot!
Whoops! I'm so sorry!
He did that on purpose!
I don't know about that.
Mistakes happen.
Oh, look, everypony,
dancing candles!
I'm not falling for that!
Discord's just trying
to distract us from--
Hey! Knock it off!
I suppose that's another "mistake"?
No, I think you just made them mad.
There's something fishy going on.
Discord!
Well it's hardly my fault
if the soup tureen
finds the term "something fishy"
to be offensive.
Not the dress. Not the dress!
That tureen's only doin'
what you're makin' it do!
Now let's not jump
to any conclusions.
Fluttershy,
can't you see what he's doing?
He's playing innocent with you
so you'll never agree to use
the Elements of Harmony
against him!
Well, that's a bit harsh,
isn't it?
You see what I'm saying,
right, Fluttershy?
Fluttershy!
You know what I see?
I see that
Discord's far from perfect,
but I also see none of you
giving him a chance!
What's gotten into you?!
Why do you keep cutting him
so much slack?!
Because that's what friends do.
We're friends?
Why, of course!
I can't ever remember my house being
this lively before you came along.
Oh. Well, I've...
never really had a friend before.
Well now you do!
Now is not a good time, Angel.
We're having a dinner party.
Hold up! I think he's tryin'
to tell us somethin'!
Apple!
Applejack!
Sweet Apple Acres?
Flooding at Sweet Apple Acres!
And we all know who's
behind that now, don't we?!
Who, me?
Oh, give it a rest!
What do you think of your
"friend" now, Fluttershy?
I've never seen
the floodin' this bad!
They've built dams round here before,
but never like this!
What's goin' on?
Such language!
It's no use.
They won't listen to a word I say!
You see Discord's
behind all this, right?
Oh, of course I do!
Do you all think I'm a silly,
gullible fool?!
I've just been trying to gain
his friendship any way I can,
so he'd come to trust
and listen to me!
Hey there, Fluttershy, you want a turn?
The water's great!
Time to see if it worked.
Fluttershy, there you are.
A sight for sore eyes.
As you can see, there's a big mess
down here at Sweet Apple Acres.
Oh, yes. Awful business, that.
It is awful.
This is Applejack's home,
and it's being destroyed
by innocent creatures
who would never be acting this way
if it weren't for
your reckless behavior.
You need to fix this.
Very well, I will fix it.
I only ask one thing in return.
Yes?
I ask that you never use
your Element of Harmony against me.
As a sign of our friendship.
I will never use
my Element of Harmony against you.
Excellent!
There, much better!
I do prefer ice skating
to water skiing! Don't you?
Discord!
That's not fixing it!
Why, I oughta...
Where are you going?
- What's wrong, pal?
- Don't call me your pal!
Come skating with me,
and we'll let bygones be bygones.
Here you go, Fluttershy!
Game on!
He fixes this or
he goes back to being stone!
Princess Celestia will understand!
I made a promise not to use
my element against him
and I'm going to keep it.
You see?
She wants to have fun with me
because we're friends.
She can't use the elements against me
I'm free forever!
Not. Your. Friend!
Who cares?
I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want.
I'm Discord, the master of chaos!
You think
you can boss Discord around?
You think I'm just going to
turn all this back because you say so?
Because if I don't
I'll lose the one friend I ever had?
Well played, Fluttershy.
Well played.
I liked it better my way, but...
I guess when you're friends,
you can't always have things
exactly your way all the time, eh?
Yes, Princess,
I'm ready to use my magic
for good instead of evil.
Most of the time.
Congratulations on your success,
ponies.
I definitely sense
a big change in Discord.
I'll leave the Elements of Harmony
with you, Twilight.
Just in case.
You were right
when you said Fluttershy
would be the one to find
the way to reform Discord.
By treating Discord as a friend,
she got him to realize
that friendship
was actually important to him.
And something that, once he had,
he didn't want to lose.
Go on. Say it...
Alright...
Friendship is magic!
See?
He can be a real sweetheart
once you get to know him.