We're getting closer.
I can hardly wait!
I'm so excited I...
I feel like shouting.
Woohoo.
Whoo wee! Canterlot, here we come!
Oh, I do hope I look festive enough.
There it is! Canterlot!
Ooh!
Oh, isn't Canterlot wonderful
this time of year?
Yeah. I wish it was Hearth's
Warming Eve every day.
There's so much to look at here.
I feel like my durn eyes are gonna
pop right outta my head.
I have an idea.
Let's play "I spy with my little eye"
as we walk. I'll go first.
I spy...
...an eight foot candy cane.
I spy a snowpony.
I spy somepony eating
a gingerbread house.
And it's me!
I can't believe that
Princess Celestia chose us...
...to put on the most
important play of the season.
Do you guys know what
an honor this is? For all of us?
Oh. I wish she hadn't
honored me quite so much.
I can't go on stage. I don't want
everypony looking at me!
Fluttershy, darling, there is
nothing to feel nervous about.
No?
Of course not. All across
Equestria ponies are preparing...
...their own pageants for Hearth's
Warming Eve in their own towns.
It's tradition.
So you're saying they'll be
too busy to come to our play?
Well, no. We're in
the Canterlot pageant...
...the biggest, most important
production in all of Equestria.
A lot of ponies will come to watch us.
A lot?
Hundreds.
Hundreds?
Maybe even thousands!
Oh! My hair!
Applejack, be a dear and
shut those windows, will you?
Rainbow Dash! Rainbow Dash!
Thank you! Thank you!
It's a reenactment
of the founding of Equestria.
It's not "The Rainbow Dash Show".
Well, it should be "The Rainbow
Dash Show". I'm the star.
Fluttershy! You've got to
come out of there!
Curtain in two minutes.
Twilight, let me handle this.
My hair!
PIIINKIEEE...
The Hearth's Warming Eve pageant
is about harmony and friendship...
SHUT THE WINDOW!
Once upon a time, long before
the peaceful rule of Celestia...
...and before ponies discovered
our beautiful land of Equestria...
...ponies did not know harmony.
It was a strange and dark time...
...a time when ponies
were torn apart...
...by hatred.
I know. Can you believe it?
During this frightful age
each of the three tribes...
...the pegasi, the unicorns
and the earth ponies...
...cared not for what befell the other
tribes, but only for their own welfare.
In those troubled times, as now...
...the pegasi were
the stewards of the weather...
...but they demanded
something in return...
...food that could only
be grown by the earth ponies.
The unicorns demanded the same...
...in return for magically
bringing forth day and night.
And so mistrust between
the tribes festered...
...until one fateful day
it came to a boil.
And what prompted the ponies to clash?
'Twas a mysterious blizzard,
that overtook the land...
...and toppled the tribes'
precarious peace.
The normally industrious earth ponies
were unable to farm their land.
The earth ponies were freezing.
Home of the pegasi fared no better.
The pegasi were hungry.
And the unicorns were
freezing *and* hungry.
Even the unicorns' magic was
powerless against the storm.
Each tribe blamed the others
for their suffering...
...and the angrier everypony grew,
the worse the blizzard became.
And so it was decided, that
a grand summit will be held...
...to figure out a way
to cope with the blizzard.
Each tribe sent their leaders.
Daughter of the unicorn
king: Princess Platinum.
Ruler of the pegasi:
Commander Hurricane.
And lastly leader of the earth
ponies: Chancellor Puddinghead.
Perhaps the three tribes could
finally settle their differences...
...and agree on a way
to get through this disaster.
All I wanna know is why the earth
ponies are hogging all the food.
US?! We're not hogging
all the food. You are!
Oh, wait. You're right. It's us.
Well, it's only cause you mean old
pegasuseseses are making it snow like crazy!
For the hundredth time, it's not us!
We're not making it snow.
It must be the unicorns!
They're doing it with
their freaky magic.
How dare you?!
Unlike you pegasi ruffians, we unicorns
would never stoop to such a thing.
Ha-Me-Ph.
Hmph.
Well, if you non-earths aren't gonna
stop using your weirdo powers...
...to freeze us all, then
I'm just plum out of ideas.
What a shocker!
An earth pony with no ideas.
Commander Hurricane!
Please cease with the insults!
You're not the boss of me,
your royal snootiness!
I BEG YOUR PARDON!
I am a princess!
I won't be spoken to that way!
Well, I'm leaving first!
No, I'm first!
And the blizzard raged on.
So the summit of the tribes did not
turn out as well as hoped...
...and the three leaders returned
home to lick their wounds...
...and basically complain.
ATTEN-TION!
Well? Aren't you curious
about how it went?
Oh! Uh... Commander Hurricane, sir!
How did it go, sir?
Horribly! Those other tribe
leaders are so disrespectful.
Don't they realize that we are
a mighty tribe of warriors...
...and should not be crossed?
We have got to break ranks
with those weak foals.
Clover the Clever! I need you!
Yes, your majesty.
Did the other pony tribes
see reason as I predicted?
Those other tribes are impossible.
I, for one, can no longer bear to be
anywhere near the lowly creatures.
The unicorns are noble and majestic.
We will no longer consort
with the likes of them.
Wouldn't it have been easier
to use the door, Chancellor?
Maybe for you, Smart Cookie.
But I am a chancellor.
I was elected, because I know
how to think outside the box.
Which means...
...I can also think inside the chimney.
Can you think inside the chimney?
-I...
-I didn't think so.
Oh my gosh. Hold on to your hooves...
I am just about to be brilliant!
That'd be a first.
I have decided that the earth
ponies are gonna go it alone.
Aw, so you mean the other
tribes didn't come around?
Shoot. I really thought we could
get through to them if we...
Don't worry about them.
We're the ones with
all the food, right?
Uh, actually we're all out.
Fine. Then we'll have to go somewhere
near where we can grow some new food.
And with me as our fearless
leader, what could go wrong?
Where should I start?
The point is...
We must find a new land!
Come on, Private Pansy.
Let's get a move on.
Hup one, hup two...
Get a hold of yourself, private!
We cannot let anything distract us
from the mission at hand.
To find (and if necessary
to conquer) a new land.
Conquer, sir?
Never know where enemies
might be lurking.
I don't see any enemies, commander.
Just snow.
Aha! Who's that?
Okay, this is getting old.
Mm, this is simply taking forever.
My hooves are killing me.
How long have we been walking for?
About five minutes, Your Highness.
I never imagined finding
a new land would be so hard.
But it'll all be worth it.
Don't you agree?
I actually think that the three
tribes could have tried harder.
STOOOP!
-What's wrong?
-That is what's wrong.
Your Highness, it's just a stream.
We can cross it easily.
I refuse to get my gown wet.
I have no intention
of arriving at my new land...
...looking like
a bedraggled earth pony.
Or worse yet,
a rough-and-tumble pegasus.
I, for one, have no intention
of stooping down to their level.
On the other hand, I have no trouble
watching *you* stoop down.
And do watch the gown, darling.
It's worth more than all
of the books in your library.
Yes, yes.
This is definitely the right direction.
It feels like we're going in circles.
But that's impossible! Are you suggesting
that I'm reading the map wrong?
Absolutely not, your chancellorness.
It's just that there are
holes in the map and...
Of course! How else could I
see where I was going!?
Yeah, uh...
Or talk? I need to be able to talk.
I mean, how would we survive
if I just only shut up?
Heaven forbid that should happen,
your chancellorship.
It's just that the map
is also upside down.
I got a news flash for you, Cookie.
The earth is round.
There is no up or down.
You're right!
It's such a relief to me, that
you're in charge of this map.
Relief?!
You don't need relief! If anypony
needs relief around here, it's me!
I'm a chancellor! I'm a big shot.
You're just my, uh...
...my...
Secretary.
Whatever.
You take the map, while
I enjoy some relief.
Yes, chancellor Puddinghead.
And so each leader encountered
obstacles along the way.
But eventually they all arrived
in the new and wondrous land.
Nopony ever seen paradise before.
This is the new land
we've been searching for!
What a view. I can see
my future house from here.
I proclaim this new land to be...
Pegasopolis!
I've never seen such jewels.
This ruby is dazzling.
This whole land is dazzling!
I'm double-dazzled!
In the name of the unicorns
I hereby dub this land Unicornia.
The air! The trees!
The dirt. This dirt is the dirtiest
dirt in the whole dirt world!
And fertile too.
Perfect to grow on food.
In the name of the earth ponies,
I think I'm gonna call this new place...
Uh...
Dirtville!
How about Earth?
Earth!
Congratulations to me
for thinking of it.
We've found our new home!
I planted my flag first.
-Did not!
-Did too!
I planted mine earlier than first.
All of you riffraff
are trespassing in Unicornia.
The name is Pegasopolis.
-Earth!
-Pegasopolis!
Unicornia!
I say we fight for the land.
May the best pony win.
That's barbaric.
Clover the Clever, throw
that brute into the dungeon.
What dungeon?! Look.
Perhaps if we all calm down...
I agree. Let's all calm down.
I vote for calm.
I'll have you court-martialled
for insubordination, private!
We settle this on the battlefield.
Who dares throw a snowball at royalty?!
Wait a minute. Where'd all this
snow come from anyway?
Oh no. Not again.
And so the paradise that the ponies
had found was soon lost...
...buried beneath a thick blanket
of snow and hard feelings.
Instead of beautiful, it was blizzardy.
Instead of wonderful, it was wintery.
Instead of spectacular,
it was snowtacular!
-Instead of...
-We get it! Move on!
Everypony was forced to seek shelter.
They searched high and low...
...but the only shelter for miles
was a cold and desolate cave.
And, of course, the three
tribes had to share it.
And nopony was too happy about that.
Please, Commander Hothead...
It's Commander Hurricane!
Please, Commander, could you just
stand back and give me my royal space?
You mean like this, Your Highness?
Indeed not.
You see this invisible line?
Private, outline our territory
for everypony to see.
See this real, non-invisible line?
No unicorns or earth ponies
are allowed to cross it.
This is the sovereign
territory of Pegasopolis.
-Clover the Clever!
-Smart Cookie!
I know, I know.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
Don't go around the rock. Go over it.
I'm not giving up an inch
of territory to the enemy.
That rock is clearly on the Unicornia's
side of the cave and it belongs to us.
Who knows? There could be jewels inside.
I claim this rock for Pegasopolis.
Unhand that rock this
instant, you scoundrel!
Oh, lookie, found my rock.
I've been looking for it everywhere.
Hey!
You invaded our territory!
Finders keepers, losers weepers.
That's the last straw!
Give me my rock!
Look, everypony! The entrance!
Great. Now there's
no way out. We're trapped.
You two deserve this horrible fate.
You've done nothing but argue
and fight with each other.
You've been fighting too,
"Your Highness".
Yeah! Worse!
I haven't been fighting
nearly as much as you!
How ridiculous!
A unicorn never stoops to fighting.
That's just cause you wimpy
unicorns know you never win.
Earth ponies are numbskul...!
Pegasi are brut...!
Unicorns are snob...!
What is that thing?
They must be... windigos.
Windigos?
My mentor, Star Swirl the Bearded,
taught me about them.
They're winter spirits that feed
on fighting and hatred.
The more hate the spirit feels,
the colder things become.
Then this is our fault.
We, three tribes. We brought
this blizzard to our home...
...by fightin' and
not trustin' each other.
Now it's destroyin' this land too.
And now our bodies will
become as cold as our hearts.
All because we were
foolish enough to hate.
Well, I don't hate you.
I actually hate Commander Hurricane
a lot more than I hate you guys.
Actually, I don't really hate her.
I just really, really,
really, really, really...
...really, really, really,
really, really dislike her.
-Well, I don't hate you guys either.
-Nor do I.
No matter what our differences,
we're all ponies.
What was that?!
I didn't know unicorns could do that.
I didn't either.
Nothing like this has
ever happened before.
But I know it couldn't
have been just me.
It came from all three of us
join together in friendship.
All through the night the three ponies
kept the fire of friendship alive...
...by telling stories to one another
and by singing songs...
...which of course became the winter
carols that we all still sing today.
Eventually the warmth of the
fire and singing and laughing...
...reached the leaders and
their bodies began to thaw.
And it even began to melt their hearts.
The three leaders agreed to
share the beautiful land...
...and with it harmony,
ever afterwards...
...and together they
named their new land...
Equestria!
The fire of friendship
lives in our hearts
As long as it burns,
we cannot drift apart
Though quarrels arise,
their numbers are few
Laughter and singing will see us through
(Will see us through)
We are a circle of pony friends
A circle of friends
we'll be to the very end
We should be so honored that
Princess Celestia chose us.
She must really think we exemplify
what good friends are.
Applejack, I thought you
closed all the windows.
Don't blame me.
Rainbow Dash should have flown up there
and shut it. After all, she's got wings.
Why do I always have to do
all the high-up chores?
Why can't Twilight use
her magic for a change?
You know what? I've got it.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000