Any minute now.
Yee-haw!
It's officially
apple bucking day!
Look at all those apples!
Ripe and juicy.
Perfect for bucking!
What the heck is going on?
They're back!
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
Attention!
This is a Sweet
Apple Acres code red.
I need all hooves
and claws on deck.
Calm down, Applejack.
Calm down?
How can I calm down
at a time like this?
Vampire fruit bats
are attacking
Sweet Apple Acres!
But I thought the fruit
bats usually stayed put
in the West Orchard.
The fruit bats do,
but these aren't just your
everyday ordinary fruit bats.
They're vampire
fruit bats.
I'll be durned if they
think they're gonna sink
their fangs into my
blue ribbon apple.
Ooooh! Wow!
Awesome!
This here's our
entry into the
Appaloosa State Fair's
Produce Competition.
You know how much TLC goes
into gettin' an apple
to grow like this?
Applejack, when you go
big, you really go big.
Them Vampire Bats
want to shrivel it up
like a raisin.
Ooh,I'm sure if we
just let them know
how special that particular
apple is to you,
they'll leave it alone.
Yeah, right.
Be my guest.
Um, excuse me,
Mr. Vampire Bat.
We were just wondering if,
maybe, you wouldn't mind
leaving that really
big apple alone?
Well, what did he say?
Um, "yes".
Huh?
But it could
have been a "no".
Oh.
This is the first Vampire
Fruit Bat I've ever met
and well, it might
take some time for me
to really understand
their language.
Uh-huh.
And in the meantime, this
pest and his vermin friends
are gonna go
after my prized apple,
and while they're at it, every
other apple in the orchard.
These Vampire Bats are
nothin' but a bunch of monsters.
Monsters?
Oh! That's a bit harsh,
don't you think?
No, I do not.
♪ Those vampire bats will
give you a fright ♪
♪ Eating apples
both day and night ♪
♪ They rest for a
minute, maybe three ♪
♪ Then they're eatin' every
apple in your apple tree ♪
♪ They don't care about nada,
not zilch no, nothin' ♪
♪ 'cept bringin' about an
orchard's destruction. ♪
♪ Now just wait a minute
there's another side to this. ♪
♪ And if I did not defend them
then I would be remiss. ♪
♪ These bats are
mamas and papas, too. ♪
♪ They care for their
young just like we ponies do. ♪
♪ Oh give me a break.
You're being too kind. ♪
♪ These creatures
have a one track mind. ♪
♪ The orchard is not
their restaurant. ♪
♪ But do they ever think
what others may want? ♪
♪ No, they don't.
And that is just a fact. ♪
♪ These bats they simply
don't know how to act. ♪
♪ That's where I
have to disagree. ♪
♪ They're loyal
to their family. ♪
♪ Spreading seeds
both far and wide. ♪
♪ You see one comin' you'd
better run and hide. ♪
♪ They're big and ugly
and mean as sin. ♪
♪ Will ya look at the
state my trees are in? ♪
♪ They help your trees
they'll grow stronger faster. ♪
♪ They've turned my life
to a total disaster. ♪
♪ Well, I, for one,
don't have a doubt. ♪
♪ These vermin must be
stamped right out. ♪
♪ I second that;
they've got to go. ♪
♪ These bats they've
got to hit the road. ♪
♪ It comes down to
just one simple fact. ♪
♪ They crossed the line
it's time to fight them. ♪
♪ Stop the bats
Stop the bats. ♪
♪ Make them go and
not come back. ♪
♪ Stop the bats
Stop the bats. ♪
♪ Make them go and
not come back. ♪
♪ Stop the bats
Stop the bats. ♪
♪ Make them go and
not come back. ♪
♪ Yes, it comes down to
just one simple fact. ♪
♪ They crossed the line;
it's time that we attack. ♪
I'm sorry, Fluttershy,
but I believe Applejack
has made the
better argument.
These vampire fruit bats
sound downright dreadful.
So let's get to
roundin' 'em up
so that they don't destroy
the rest of my orchard.
Fruit bat round up!
Um, excuse me, but what if
instead of rounding them up,
we let them have part
of the orchard.
Have you lost your
pest-lovin' mind?
They're only here
because they're hungry.
If we built a
sanctuary for them,
they could have their
own apples to enjoy.
After a while, they
could even help
the rest of your orchard.
The Vampire bats don't eat
the seeds of the apples
and when they
spit them out,
they grow into even more
productive apple trees.
Listen, Fluttershy, that
sounds real nice and all,
but every second we spend
buildin' this
so-called "sanctuary"
is a second they'll spend
destroyin' orchard.
You don't know
what it was like
the last time there
was an infestation,
but Granny Smith has told
me enough stories about it
that just the thought of
it gives me nightmares.
Granny says we lost a huge
section of orchard that year.
They had to ration
out apples all winter.
What about the cider?
There was still
cider, right?
Not
a
drop!
No cider?
No cider!
We need to round up
these monsters
and we need to do
it now!
If Granny Smith wasn't
with Apple Bloom and Big Mac
checkin' out our produce
competition in Appaloosa,
she'd be here tellin'
us to do just that.
I'm sorry, Fluttershy, but
I think Applejack is right.
I just wish there was another
way we could convince them
not to eat them in
the first place.
Maybe there is.
So there's good news
and bad news.
The good news is that
I've found a spell
that can get the
vampire fruit bats
to stop wanting to suck
the juice from the apples.
But in order for
the spell to work,
I need the bats' full
and complete attention.
Oh, no.
Fluttershy, I need you to
do your stare on the bats.
Oh, gosh, I don't know.
What's the problem?
You've used the stare
plenty of times before.
Yes, but it's not
something I take lightly;
I've made a vow not to use it
except in dire circumstances.
This circumstance is
plenty dire to me.
Me, too!
Think of the cider!
Won't somepony please
think of the cider!
I'm sorry, I just don't like
the idea of taking away
the thing that really
makes the vampire fruit bats
vampire fruit bats.
It just feels wrong.
But if we don't do this,
there won't be any apples
left for anypony
here in Ponyville.
Doesn't that
feel wrong, too?
So what's it going
to be, Fluttershy?
Will you do your stare
on the bats or not?
Um, um...
...OK, I'll do it.
Good choice.
I knew you wouldn't side
with those icky bats.
Ewwww!
They're not icky.
First round of
cider's on me!
Hold it right there.
We gotta round up these
beasts with wings first.
Time's a-wastin'!
Got you!
Good work, everypony.
I think we got them all.
Now all we need is for
you to do your stare.
Um, are you sure I
really need...
OK.
I really, really, really
hate to do this to you.
I just hope you
can forgive me.
Good.
Now you go, Twilight.
All right.
You can stop
staring, Fluttershy.
Did it work?
Only one way to
find out for sure.
Whoo-ee!
My crop is saved.
Yee-haw!
We'll be drinking
cider all winter long!
I want to thank
you for your help.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Don't mention
it, Applejack.
It was my
pleasure, really.
Now all we gotta do is
sweep up these cores
so I can start bucking
fresh tomorrow morning.
Apple bucking day, take 2.
YEEHAW!
Time to collect those
juicy sweet apples.
The spell didn't work.
You're durn tootin', the
spell didn't work.
I think we're going to have to
take more extreme measures.
I hear ya', Applejack.
Come on, everypony, let's
track down those Vampire Bats!
Wait a minute.
I don't think these bats
are the ones that sucked
my apples dry.
But if the vampire bats
aren't eating your apples,
who is?
Fluttershy, you're
our animal expert.
Do you know of any other
creature that might be
capable of this?
I'm sorry.
I don't.
Well, there's only
one way to find out.
We'll have to catch
whoever it is in the act.
And how do you
propose we do that?
A stake-out.
The witching hour.
Maybe we should
just call this off.
I'm not sure about the
rest of you guys
but I'm really hungry.
Oh, Fluttershy, it'll be OK.
Don't forget, darling,
we're all in this together.
That's right.
Nopony leaves this orchard
until we solve this mystery.
Agreed?
Agreed!
Does everypony have
their pony signal?
Now remember Pinkie Pie,
only use the signal
if you see something
suspicious.
I got it.
Something suspicious.
Whatcha doin?
All right, now
everypony split up.
We'll each patrol our
own row of the orchard.
Whoever or whatever is
destroying my apples
has got to be
here somewhere.
I have a bad
feeling about this,
a really bad
feeling about this.
That apple, it looks
so juicy and sweet.
What was that?
Suspicious! Hee hee!
It's pony signal time!
Who's there?
Oh, well, there's
obviously no need to worry
about that shadowy
figure overhead.
Or maybe there is.
I think I'll just go see
how Rainbow Dash is doing.
Uh...
Who's there?
Answer me, or
you'll regret it!
Fine. Have it your own way.
Take that, you,
you, you...
You scarecrow.
Applejack, what is it?
Suspicious!
Fluttershy?
Yooo-hoo!
Fluttershy!
That's not Flutter-shy.
That's Flutter-bat.
We've got to get
her down from there.
Fluttershy sweetness,
please come down.
And do stop being
a vampire bat.
Fluttershy!
It's me, Rainbow Dash.
Why don't you cut the
bat act and come on down?
Whoa!
Maybe we should just let
her come down when she's ready.
Flutterbat on the loose!
Run for your lives!
Pinkie Pie, calm down.
See, she's back
on her...branch.
She's just biding her time.
Waiting for the
right moment to pounce!
Pinkie Pie, bats
don't eat ponies.
Not even vampire bats.
But maybe vampire
ponies eat other ponies.
I'm not taking
any chances.
How did this happen?
That's what I
don't understand.
I think this was
actually our fault.
Our fault?
And how do you
figure that?
OK, so this is me;
these are the bats
and this is Fluttershy
doing her stare.
The spell was supposed to go
right onto the bats like this.
But somehow the spell
must have backfired.
It took the vampire fruit bats'
desire to be vampire fruit bats,
and transferred that
desire into Fluttershy.
C'mon! We'll reverse the
spell and make it right.
Then what are
we waiting for?
Let's save Fluttershy before
that thing eats us all!
Hit the deck!
Whoa!
Follow that bat!
I can't believe
we lost her.
Oh Fluttershy,
where are you?
Look out!
If she keeps this up, your whole
crop will be gone in no time.
That's the least
of my worries.
I just want my
friend back.
We'll never get her back
unless we corner her
and catch her so I can
reverse the spell.
There she is.
There she goes!
Oh, this is no use.
I think the only way we're
going to catch her
is if we find a way to
lure her closer to us.
But even if we can
lure her to us,
how are we going to get
her to stay still long enough
for you to do
your reverse spell?
Oooh! If only we had
Fluttershy to do her stare
on the Flutterbat.
That's it!
OK, let's get
our friend back.
Action stations!
So much for having
the winning apple
in the Appaloosa
State Fair, huh?
She's coming!
Uh, where am I?
Thank goodness you're OK!
But what happened to me?
You turned into
a vampire pony!
I tried to eat ponies?
Of course not.
So I wasn't a vampire?
Yes!
"Yes," I was?
Or "Yes," I wasn't?
Yes, you were!
But I didn't try
to eat ponies?
Yes!
I did?
No.
I'm confused.
Me too, and I was there.
Fluttershy, I'm real sorry I
didn't take your suggestion
in the first place.
And don't forget; now
you'll get seeds that will
grow into even bigger
and better apple trees.
Does that mean what
I think it means?
Yep. More cider, too.
Ha ha! Wow!
OK. Got the part
about the spell.
Fluttershy turning
into a bat.
Building the sanctuary.
Be sure to put in there
that I came to see that my
short-term solution was
a little short-sighted.
And that you shouldn't let
anypony pressure you
into doing something you
don't think is right.
Sometimes you have to tell
even your closest friends, "no".
Now how 'bout
we celebrate our
stronger-than-ever friendship
with a nice, ripe juicy apple?
Stand back!
I vant to suck its juice!