Hey! Rainbow Dash!
Hiya, Scootaloo! What's up?
The Rainbow Dash fan
club just decided
everypony's coming to see you
when the Wonderbolts' new tour
comes through Ponyville!
Well, it's great that you guys
are going to the show, Scoot,
but I won't actually
be performing in it.
Reservists aren't
in the show
unless one of the real
Wonderbolts can't fly.
I'll probably be working
crowd control or something.
You're still gonna be
wearing a Wonderbolts uniform
though, right?
A Reservist one, yeah.
Hmm. That's good
enough for me!
Whoa!
Rainbow Dash! Glad
we found you.
We need you in the show when
we get to Ponyville. Flying.
But she's only
in the Reserves!
Not anymore, kid.
You mean...
Rainbow Dash! You're finally
a full-fledged Wonderbolt!
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Rainbow Dash! Woo!
What
she said.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu/
Uh, anypony see my wing
balm? I don't wanna be stiff
when I show up at
Wonderbolt headquarters.
Got it.
Do you have time to tell us
what happened, Rainbow Dash?
Ooo yes, we must
know every detail!
Start from when you were
a foal and you first knew
your destiny was to
become a Wonderbolt!
Well, not
much to tell, really.
Spitfire told me the
Wonderbolts need me
to go on tour with them.
That's really great.
I know how long you've been
waiting for a spot to open up.
Yeah, Fire Streak decided to
retire and teach full-time.
Cloudsdale Flight School will
probably be churning out
Wonderbolts with him there.
But guess who was at the
top of the Reserve list?
Ooh ooh! I know! Pick me!
So what do you
do now, Dashie?
I have to report to
Wonderbolts Headquarters
this afternoon. It's only
two days till tour starts
and I need to learn
the routine.
You're leaving already?
But we barely started your
congratulation party!
I haven't even thought about
your going away party yet.
Pinkie, I'm not
leaving Ponyville.
I just have to
train for this show.
I hope everything
goes well.
It sounds like an
awful lot of pressure,
having to learn
everything so quickly.
Yeah, good luck, Dash!
Luck? Save that
for the rest of the team.
Now that my awesomeness has
finally been recognized,
the other Wonderbolts
will have to keep up
or eat my cloud-trail.
Everypony knows you're a
great flier, Rainbow Dash,
but so are the rest
of the Wonderbolts.
It might be more
challenging than you think.
You're right.
I mean, do I show up
wearing sunglasses or not?
Sunglasses are
automatically cool,
but anypony can
put them on.
Maybe I'd stand out
more if I didn't.
Team briefings are
every morning at--
--oh seven twenty.
Because there were twenty
ponies in the original
EUP Guard that became
the Wonderbolts.
Right. And I know you've
seen the Academy bunks,
but these are the official
Wonderbolts' barracks--
--built by Admiral
Fairweather himself!
Don't forget rule
number one, newbie:
always check both ways
before crossing the runway.
Uh sure, but nopony
else is here!
They will be. And most
of the Wonderbolts
like to make a flashy
entrance, so stay alert.
Right. No problem.
Whoa! Is that
General Flash's cap?
And the original crest with
the Wonderbolts motto on it.
"Altius volantis."
"Soaring higher!"
WOW! I mean... cool.
OK, newbie, we've got
a show in two days,
which means you've gotta
hustle your haunches
to learn this routine.
You've got five minutes to
get dressed and get outside
to meet the rest of the team.
Yes, ma'am! I'll have
all the moves down
by the end of the day.
Let's hope so. We're
all expecting you
to make quite
an impression.
Lookin' good! OK, you're about
to take your first flight
as an actual Wonderbolt.
No pressure.
Just gotta go out there and
knock 'em off their hooves.
OK, Wonderbolts, get
ready to meet your most
awesome member ever!
Hey! Look out!
Huh?
Whoa!
Whoa! Most awesome
entrance by a newbie ever!
Are you OK, Rainbow Dash?
More like Rainbow Crash!
OK, flight school. Get
ready for Rainbow Dash!
Whooooooooa!
More like Rainbow Crash!
Rainbow Crash, Rainbow Crash,
Rainbow Crash, Rainbow Crash!
Hey! You guys buzzed
me on purpose!
Not quite. You forgot
rule number one, newbie.
"Always check both ways
before crossing the runway."
Yeah, well, I was just...
testing you guys.
Yeah, right.
All right, nopony got hurt
and we've got a lot to do,
so let's forget about
this and get flying.
Classic rookie move, Rainbow
Crash. That was amazing.
Higher, Crash! You're
breaking formation!
Check your nine, Crash!
Tighter, Crash! Get in there!
My name's not Crash!
Whoah!
Huh! Coulda fooled me!
Hey Crash, I know it
was a tough day today,
but don't worry, you'll
get the hang of it.
Tough day? Please. If I can
pull off a Sonic Rainboom,
I can learn this routine. I'll
have it down cold tomorrow.
Probably even come up with
a couple of improvements.
Rainbow Dash, over here.
Yes, ma'am?
I'm glad you're
still here.
Oh yeah? Did you want
some ideas on how
to make the show
extra awesome?
Not quite. I know you've
been a Reservist for a while,
but the Bolts have a
few of their own rules
you might not know about.
Like worst flier
of the day
has to clean up the
whole compound.
Better get to it, Crash.
My name's not Crash.
Surprise!
What?
Hooray, Rainbow Dash!
Our favorite Wonderbolt!
We know you're probably
tired, Rainbow Dash,
but Pinkie wanted to
throw you a real party.
Your Best Day EVER party!
Yeah. It was
something, all right.
Well, we can't wait
to hear all about it.
And I'd love to
tell you. I really would.
But I'm pretty beat.
You know, from all the
excitement of my big day.
Um, is something
wrong, Rainbow Dash?
What could be wrong? I'm
finally a Wonderbolt,
which means everything has to
be totally perfectly awesome.
Oh no, something is wrong.
What happened, darling?
I told you, it's nothing.
I mean, maybe some of the
Wonderbolts started calling me
"Rainbow Crash".
Oh no! Isn't that the
same terrible nickname
those bullies in flight
school used to call you?
Why would they call you that?
Well, I, kinda, sorta
fell into a garbage can.
Ugh!
Well, look at the
bright side!
At least they didn't
call you Rainbow Trash!
So you started off
on the wrong hoof.
I bet every new Wonderbolt
has a tough first day.
Um-hum!
What you need is to find a
positive way to stand out.
As soon as you're known
for something else,
that nasty old nickname
will be forgotten.
Rarity's right.
Why don't you think of the
Wonderbolts like us?
We're a team, but we all stand
out in different ways.
That's it! I'm gonna stand out
in a different way.
Just like you guys!
Goodbye, Rainbow Crash,
hello, Captain Awesome!
Good morning, everypony!
Who's ready for a fantastic day
of flying? I know I am!
I just couldn't be more excited
for the big show tomorrow. Are
you guys excited? I'm excited!
Actually, I'm always excited!
Some ponies even call
me "Dynamic Dash"
because I'm so full of
energy all the time!
Uh, Wonderbolts don't
get excited, Crash.
You gotta keep a level
head to fly the way we do.
Well, of course I know that!
But the truth of the matter is,
you should be excited.
It's the dream of near every
little Pegasus pony
to grow up and fly
with the Wonderbolts
and here you all are doing it.
So are you.
True. Go ahead and call me
"Forthright Filly"
if you want, but she-ucks, I
like to tell it like it is.
And I believe a pony oughta
appreciate hard work
paying off like this because
being a Wonderbolt
is somethin' special.
We know.
You know, I was just reading
about how dihedral wing angles
can help increase stability
in banking turns.
It made me think that
pre-flight checklists
could really help
increase our efficiency,
so I went ahead and made
them for everypony.
I'm always finding so much
interesting information
in books. In fact, a lot of
ponies call me
"Reading Rainboom."
We all know how
wings work, newbie
and we already have checklists!
Now get off the runway!
I'm so sorry.
I was just trying to help
because I care about all of the
Wonderbolts oh so much.
Yesiree, just call
me "Care Mare."
Um, but if you're busy now, I
can just come back later.
Or, you know, not at all.
OK.
I must tell you how much I
just love these uniforms!
Why, ever since I was a foal,
I've admired the mixture
of bold lines and
classic contours.
They don't call me "Rainbow
Fash" for nothing!
Uh...
The "Fash" is for fashion.
Crash!
I'm not sure why you're
acting like this,
but you need to stop.
I was just, you know,
trying to show everypony
all the awesome ways I can
contribute to the Bolts.
I know you're excited to find
your place on the team,
but just focus on the
routine for now, OK?
Yes, ma'am.
Maybe this will
help motivate you.
"Crash?"
Couldn't you just put
my regular name on it?
That's not how it
works around here.
We all have our nicknames on our
jackets. Right, Clipper?
Clipper?
Right, boss!
Now it's official. Welcome to
the Wonderbolts, Crash!
If I don't come up with
something unforgettable
to add to the routine,
I'm gonna be Rainbow Crash
for the rest of my life.
This is gonna be so amazing!
I know! I'm almost as
excited as Pinkie Pie!
I can't wait to see Rainbow
Dash's first performance
as an honest to
goodness Wonderbolt!
I hope there's
cotton candy!
We should all remember
to be extra supportive
for Rainbow Dash, too.
Excellent point. It's simply
dreadful that she's had
such a rough start after
finally achieving her dream.
Rainbow Dash is a pretty
resilient pony.
I'm sure she's shaken
off her tough first day
and turned it around by now.
Speaking of - hey Dash!
Oh, perfect! Hey, can
I borrow Scootaloo?
Me? What for?
Oh, I just
needed some help
and figured the president of
the Rainbow Dash fan club
was the right pony for the job.
I thought the Wonderbolt
Reserves were here to help.
Oh, yeah, they're all busy doing
official Reserves stuff.
But don't worry, with
Scootaloo's help,
everything's gonna be awesome.
Better than awesome.
Does-does that mean practice
went well yesterday?
Gotta go!
What are we doing up here,
Rainbow Dash?
I just need a small
favor from you
that's really gonna make this
show something special.
Now, the Wonderbolts are going
to fly over this ridge
right before the
finale of the show.
I'll fly by last and
when I signal you,
you zip up the ramp
on your scooter
and kick the storm
cloud into my path.
What?
That kick will shoot
off a lightning bolt
right behind me, making
me look totally awesome!
And then I'll do some
incredible Rainbow Dash flying
with it, to create the
coolest, show-stoppingest,
lightning-tastic light show
anypony has ever seen!
Are you sure about this?
It's gonna
be so awesome!
And no pony will ever call me
"Rainbow Crash" after this.
Oh, gotta go! Be ready for
me, OK, Scootaloo?
Um, OK?
Mares and gentlecolts, fillies
and foals of all ages,
look to the skies and
prepare to be awestruck
by the incredible flying
prowess of the Wonderbolts!
I hope Spike and Pinkie Pie
are done getting their snacks
or they're going to
miss Rainbow Dash!
Oh don't worry, Fluttershy.
Nothing could keep Pinkie
Pie from missing this.
Except
maybe cotton candy.
C'mon, Pinkie, the
show's starting!
One second! Just a little bit
bigger, please, but hurry!
Bigger!
That was amazing!
She's doing great!
Bigger!
I hope this works!
Ahhhh!
Ahhh!
Whoahh!
Ahhhh!
Whoah!
Hope I'm not too late!
Pfft! I don't know what
took that pony so long.
Ahhh!
That was amazing!
Way to go, Rainbow Crash.
You gonna tell us what
just happened, newbie?
I am so sorry.
I should hope so.
You changed the routine
without consulting me
and put other
ponies at risk.
I've drummed flyers out
of the Bolts for less.
I know and I'm ready for
whatever punishment you want.
You guys were right to
call me Rainbow Crash.
I've always been
a standout flier,
but since I joined
the Wonderbolts,
I've only stood out
for making mistakes.
It's been my
dream my whole life,
but I guess maybe I'm not
Wonderbolt material after all.
Are you serious?
You're the most talented
flier we've ever had.
And you've saved all of
Equestria like, a dozen times!
I-I--
Of course you're supposed
to be a Wonderbolt!
We've been waiting
for a spot to open up
ever since you
joined the Reserves.
But... you guys... all
called me Rainbow Crash.
Yeah, so? My
nickname's Clipper.
You know why they
call me that?
Uh, cause you're as
fast as a ship?
Because I clipped my
wing on a flagpole
as I was landing on
my first day. Huh.
Huh.
Flatfoot. My first day I
misjudged my landing
and came down right on
Spitfire's hoof.
Daisy.
Slowpoke.
Hoof 'n' Mouth.
You don't want to know
what they call me.
Whoa, that is
so much worse than Crash.
Right?
So, does this mean I'm
still on the team?
You think you can be
part of this team
and not constantly
try to showboat?
I promise. I spent my
whole life trying to be
a standout flier, but now
that I'm a Wonderbolt,
it's time to be OK
with fitting in.
Good. Because I really didn't
want to miss the chance
to tease you for years about
this catastrophe!
I mean, that crash was epic!
But you're on
probation for a month!
Got a problem with that?
No, ma'am.
Hey Rainbow Dash, we just
wanted to check on you.
Are you doing OK?
I'm doing great, thanks!
Sure you don't need any help?
Nah. This mess is my
responsibility
and I've gotta clean it up
myself. And after this,
Spitfire's got me cleaning
the Wonderbolts compound
for the next month.
So why are you in
such a good mood?
Duh! Because I'm a Wonderbolt!