OK! Let's see how
your still-life's
comin' along, Kettle Corn.
Well, that certainly
is... round.
I can make it rounder.
I'm afraid that's all
the time we have today.
We'll try something
else tomorrow.
But I like circle-painting.
And on the way to figuring
out what you're meant to do,
you'll find a ton
more stuff you like.
That's what makes looking for
your cutie mark so great.
Mmmhmmm!
Sorry everypony,
we're closin' up shop.
Glad to help you out tomorrow.
Awwww!
I don't know if we can
help them tomorrow.
Working with blank flanks
one at a time takes forever.
If only there was a
way we could help
a whole herd of
'em at once.
That would be perfect!
We'd save time and they
could help each other.
Just like we used to!
Aw, but it'd have to be
somewhere big enough
to handle all those
blank flanks.
Somewhere outside...
with tons of
activities to try!
Are you two thinking
what I'm thinking?
CUTIE MARK DAY CAMP!
And I know just the place.
Applejack used to go there
when she was little!
CAMP FRIENDSHIP!
Oh.
Sorry.
I thought we were all
gonna yell that one too.
Attention all blank flanks!
And blank flank affiliates!
Come to our Cutie
Mark Day Camp
to find out what
you're truly good at.
Bond with other blank flanks
and find out what you're
meant to do together!
Hey Rumble!
Oh, hey, Crusaders.
Look, I can't stop.
Gotta meet my brother for...
...something.
No problem! Just wanted
to make sure you heard
about our Cutie
Mark Day Camp!
The first session's
tomorrow!
Uh whatchya got
there, little brother?
What? Oh. Nothing.
Come on. I wanna show you a
new dive roll I'm trying.
Scootaloo: Come one, come all!
Cutie Mark Day Camp is for
blank flanks of all kinds!
Hmm...
Welcome Cutie Mark Campers!
Who's excited to be here?
We are!
Whoo hoo!
Well, we're excited too!
At Cutie Mark Day Camp,
you'll be able to try
all kinds of things.
Kayaking!
Scootaloo: Horseshoe tossing!
Circle painting!
You can try 'em all, but
the most important thing
is that you'll be
trying them together.
That's what worked for us!
Thunderlane: Then I bet it'll
work for these little guys too!
I thought you said we
were gonna go practice
for the Wonderbolt's
Ponyville extravaganza show.
I'm going to
Wonderbolt practice.
You're going to
cutie mark practice.
And we're glad to have you!
I can't believe your own
brother is a Wonderbolt.
Uh, Rainbow Dash is
practically my sister
and she's a Wonder Bolt too.
Do you know Spitfire?
I know she'll be
mad if I'm late!
Now you have a good
time and try some stuff.
Who knows what
you'll be good at?
Wow!
My goodness!
All right! Looks like we found
the first activity of the day...
the horseshoe toss!
Whoo hoo!
Well, wish I could stay and
play, but it's time to fly!
Have fun!
Whoa!
C'mon, Rumble!
Step on up and show
us how it's done.
No way he's as good
as his brother.
Eh. Whoops.
Aw, guess I won't be
getting my cutie mark
in the horseshoe toss...
Don't worry about
it, Rumble.
Hardly anypony finds their
calling on the first try.
Eh. I wasn't worried.
Good! 'Cause there's a ton
of other stuff to try!
We'll find you something
you're good at!
Whoops!
Whoopsie.
Whoops.
The first and last lines
have five syllables,
but the middle has seven.
It's called a haiku.
Whoops. I've tried it all.
Time to tell my brother
this.. camp isn't for me.
Come on, Rumble.
Isn't it fun just trying stuff?
Not really.
Yeah!
All right!
Haiku cutie mark!
And I never would have
tried without Skeedaddle.
That's what Cutie Mark
Day Camp is all about.
Working together and
helping each other!
But I can still
come back, right?
And maybe paint some circles?
Of course!
Let's all meet right
back here tomorrow.
Hooray!
Wow. I can't believe we got a
cutie mark on the first day!
Yep. This camp was a
pretty swell idea.
Everypony's really enjoyed it.
Everypony except Rumble.
He didn't have much
luck with anything.
Trying to find out what you're
meant to do can be frustrating.
You remember how long it took
us to get our cutie marks?
I remember the nightmares.
Well, we can't let Rumble
quit camp just because
he didn't find something
he's good at yet.
We'll just have to convince him
to come back and try harder.
Mm hmm!
Hey. Rumble!
What are you all
doing here?
We just wanted to apologize
for not finding anything
you liked today.
Oh. Whatever. It's fine.
It's not fine! It's frustrating
and we know what it's like.
I'm not frustrated!
It's OK. We've
all been there.
But we won't give
up on helping you.
We know you'll get
your cutie mark.
Everypony does!
Actually, I don't
need your help
because I don't want
to get my cutie mark!
What!?
I-I must have
hay in my ears
because I thought I
just heard Rumble say--
You heard right! I don't
want my cutie mark!
[gasp] He said it again!
Not wanting a cutie mark is
like not wanting to breathe.
Everypony wants to know
what they're meant to do.
Hmph! Not this pony.
WHY?
Because Cutie Marks
are silly and...
and they just force you into
one thing your whole life!
That's silly.
Having a cutie mark doesn't
mean you can't do other things.
Yeah! Our cutie marks
are in helping ponies
with their cutie marks,
but I still like making
potions with Zecora.
And when was the last
time you did that?
Um...I-I-I think it was... uh...
Well, we've been pretty busy
helping other ponies lately--
Oh. You mean doing the thing
you got your cutie mark for?
The thing you're stuck doing
for the rest of your life?
OK, maybe we will be doing
that more than anything else,
but we love being
Cutie Mark Crusaders!
Well, that's fine for you, but
I'm not gonna be put in a box!
A blank flank who doesn't
want a cutie mark?
That's gotta be the strangest
thing I've ever heard.
Granny always says, some ponies
have to find their own hay.
Are you sure she didn't
mean "find their own way?"
Huh. That would
make more sense.
I can't believe Rumble isn't
interested in getting
his cutie mark either, but
we can't force him.
And we've got a whole
camp full of ponies
who are interested
in cutie marks.
Mmm hmmm!
Yeah!
Here he comes, the fastest, most
elite flyer in Equestria...
THUNDERLANE!
Uh! Whoa!
Eh.. I was gonna say me.
You're not the only pegasus
in the family, you know.
Aw sorry, little
brother. You're right.
You might be the most elite
flyer in Equestria someday,
but for now, you should
try other things too.
Speaking of which, aren't
you supposed to be at camp?
Pfft.
That camp is for losers
who can't do anything.
Great. So there's no pressure.
You can try everything and not
be worried about looking bad.
I'm not worried about that!
I just don't want
to get a cutie mark
in any of their
ridiculous activities.
Well, you're still
going back tomorrow.
You can't be a
blank flank forever.
Ahhh!
All righty, Cutie Mark Campers,
that's it for jam making.
But this is fun and I didn't
get my cutie mark yet.
What if I'm not good
at anything else?
You don't get a cutie mark
just because you're
good at something,
or even because
you like it.
There's more to
it than that.
I'm real good at
painting circles,
but I got my cutie
mark in haikus.
Which is what I like, but uh I'm
still a blank flank like you.
So, you can't get a cutie
mark in something you like?
Now, we didn't say that.
Rumble: You don't have to.
Rumble, you came back!
Say buh-bye to
painting circles.
You'll be too busy
haikuing from now on!
But... I like circles.
Come on, Rumble, that's
not how cutie marks work.
So that's how cutie marks work?
Am I speaking Olde Ponish?
Apple Bloom: I just said it wasn't!
♪♪
♪ Cutie Marks are great,
they say ♪
♪ Yeah right! ♪
♪ They make you
special in your way ♪
♪ But that special mark
that's just for you ♪
♪ Will erase the stuff
you like to do. ♪
♪ So no more painting?
No more Haiku? ♪
♪ Rumble, stop.
That's just not true! ♪
♪ So you're good at
charming snakes; too bad! ♪
♪ Or you bake delicious
cakes; oh, well! ♪
♪ Maybe there are lots of
things that you like to do! ♪
♪ Well, your options
get pretty stark ♪
♪ once you got
that cutie mark! ♪
♪ Blank Flanks are better ♪
♪ Nopony can tell you
who you have to be ♪
♪ Blank Flanks are better ♪
♪ Keep your spirits
soaring free! ♪
♪ So listen up cause
I ain't lying ♪
♪ Don't need no marks
so why keep trying? ♪
♪ If you like just being you ♪
♪ Then keeping that
blank flank blank ♪
♪ is the thiiiing to do. ♪
♪ Blank Flanks ♪
Cutie marks don't
limit you!
They only show
what you can do!
♪ Blank Flanks! ♪
But what if you
can't do a thing?
♪ Blank Flanks! ♪
These cutie marks
are frustrating!
♪ You say there's
nothing you can do? ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Exactly! ♪
♪ A blank flank is
the way for you ♪
♪ It's no work to just
be who you are ♪
♪ No hunt to be
some cutie star ♪
♪ You're perfect
just being you ♪
♪ Don't bother with
what you cannot do! ♪
♪ Blank Flanks are better ♪
♪ Nopony can tell you
who you have to be ♪
♪ Blank Flanks are better ♪
♪ Keep your spirits
soaring free! ♪
♪ So listen up
cause I ain't lying ♪
♪ Don't need no marks ♪
♪ so why keep trying? ♪
♪ If you like just being you ♪
♪ Then keeping that blank flank
blank is the thiiiiing to do. ♪
♪ Blank Flanks forever! ♪
That's it, Blank Flanks!
Be proud of who you are.
You don't need some phony pony
telling you you're
just ONE thing!
Blank Flanks ... FOREVER!
♪ Forever and ever! ♪
BLANK FLANKS!
Whoopee!
Now wait just an
apple-pickin' minute, Rumble.
Where do you think you're
leading our campers?
They're not your
campers anymore.
I'm starting a new camp.
Everypony on this
side of the line
is in Camp Blank
Flanks Forever!
But you can't be a
blank flank forever!
That's just the kind of
talk I'd expect to hear
from "Camp Cutie Mark."
Which is why blank flanks
need a camp where we can enjoy
being blank flanks and
appreciate our blank-flankiness
without feeling pressured
to get a cutie mark.
Now, hold on, everypony.
Blank flanks forever!
Blank flanks forever! [cheering]
What just happened?
Has everypony gone mad?
In a word, "yes."
I just can't see
what we did wrong.
I thought everypony
was having fun.
They were until that Rumble
came and made a mess of things.
What are they doing now?
It looks like
whatever they want.
Honestly, it's not
all that different
from what they
were doing here.
Then, what was the point?
The point is that Rumble is a
mad pony who must be stopped!
Sweetie Belle: Now calm
down, Crusaders.
We just need to
talk to him again.
The key is to
remain calm.
[shrill] Cutie Marks
make you SPECIAL!
By putting you in a
special little box!
Special!
Box!
Come on, Sweetie Belle.
I think you've remained
calm long enough.
Kettle Corn, you
covered your cutie mark?
I'm blank flank again.
Keeping
my options open.
I'm more than haikus.
You just
haikued right then!
Don't let them
get in your head.
You're an open-ended
question.
Blank Flanks forever!
Blank Flanks
Forever!
Blank Flanks Forever!
Wow, you're
cracking great!
Thanks!
[gasp] Oh, no!
What if I get a
cutie mark in it?
Then you'll be stuck
doing it forever!
Blank Flanks, no more potential
cutie mark activities!
Well, Cutie Mark
Day Camp is a bust.
No it isn't. It's
a swell idea.
We just can't seem to talk
any sense into that...
that Rumble.
Maybe we can't, but I bet
I know somepony who can.
Let me get this straight.
My little brother
upended your entire camp?
How in Equestria
did he do that?
Well, it started when he
couldn't toss a horseshoe,
or paddle a kayak,
or shoot an arrow,
or use a pencil and we felt bad
that he wasn't good at anything,
but now he doesn't want a cutie
mark at all because he's afraid
he'll get stuck doing something
he doesn't like forever. Y'know?
No. I don't.
Rumble's good at
all that stuff.
Well, that doesn't make
a lick of sense...
unless he was being bad
at stuff on purpose!
Oh. I was afraid of this.
Afraid of what?
Ever since I became
a Wonderbolt,
Rumble's either watching me
or trying to fly like me.
He won't do anything else.
That's why I thought your
camp was such a good idea.
Scootaloo: I don't understand.
If Rumble wants to be
a Wonderbolt someday,
what's wrong with that?
Not a thing, but right
now he isn't even giving
anything else a chance.
Sounds to me like
Rumble isn't afraid
of being "put in
a box" at all.
It doesn't?
Nope. I think Rumble's
already picked out a box.
He's afraid he'll get a cutie
mark that'll keep him from it.
I don't know how to
say this Rumble
but, Blank Flank Forever
Camp is kinda...
Boring?
If we want to stay blank flanks,
we can't risk doing stuff.
What if I get a cutie
mark in being bored?
Scootaloo: Attention blank
flanks of Cutie Mark Day Camp!
The Cutie Mark Crusaders
are pleased to announce
today's special guest--
Thunderlane!
Hey, everypony! It's me!
Ahh!
Anypony who's interested,
gather round for a day
of camp activities with
a genuine Wonderbolt!
Er.. s-s-sorry, Rumble, but
cutie mark or not,
I'm not missing
out on this!
Whoa!
Apple Bloom: All right campers, it's time for
our last activity of the day.
A Wonderbolt obstacle course!
Just like the one they'll fly
through in their upcoming show!
But on the ground, since
not everypony has wings.
Thunderlane? Aren't you
going to run the course?
Nope! I know I'm a Wonderbolt
and my cutie mark is
all about moving fast,
but I really like to cook!
Since when?
We take turns making the
meals at Wonderbolt HQ.
I didn't want to at
first, but now I love it.
I just wish I tried it sooner.
You do?
Of course!
There's more to me
than just flying.
And I bet there's
more to you too.
Obstacles are fun
Running free
through mud and dirt
Beats circle painting!
That haiku pretty
well sums it up.
Looks like Thunderlane was
right about the obstacle course
getting Rumble to
come back over.
Hey, Rumble.
Aren't you gonna do
our Wonderbolt course?
I'm cooking today.
Maybe I'll do the
course tomorrow.
So, you're coming back tomorrow?
You're not worried about
getting your cutie mark?
Nah. I already know
I'm a good flyer.
It kinda runs in the family.
I guess it's time to see
what other stuff I can do.
Hm hm.