Good morning, Miss Cheerilee!
Good morning, everypony!
I hope you brought
your thinking caps
because today we're going
to learn about physics!
Physics?
Mm-hm. Specifically, the use of
force in energy conversions.
In this case, using mechanical
work to convert potential energy
into kinetic energy.
The what, now?
Um. Mrs. Cheerilee, that
sounds a bit over our heads.
Yeah. Why would we even
need to know that stuff?
Oh, it's very important.
In fact, you'll most likely
end up using it tomorrow.
Tomorrow? What for?
Why, for participating in the ...
APPLEWOOD DERBY!
Oh, WHEW! For a second I
thought we were gonna have to
You know... learn stuff.
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
Derpy is Best Muffin!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
We get to race in the Applewood
Derby tomorrow? That's so cool!
My family's talked
about it for years
and now I'm finally
old enough to race!
Now hold onto your
horseshoes, everypony.
You've got a lot of work to do
before you're ready to race.
Yeah, but not
school work, right?
There'll be a block of
applewood just like this one
waiting for you at Sweet
Apple Acres tomorrow
and you've got one day to turn
it into a race-ready cart.
Awwwwww!
Oh, yeah. That is
a lot of work.
Mm-hmm. Luckily, you'll each
get to pick an older pony
to help you. But
choose wisely
because they'll also
have to ride in the cart
with you during the race.
Hmm, I think I know
just the pony to ask!
Me too!
Me three!
Just remember everypony,
your cart has to be able
to finish the race if you want
to win one of the awards.
Fastest, for winning
the race, naturally.
Most Traditional, for
the best working replica
of an original Applewood cart.
And Most Creative, for the cart
with the best overall design.
Hoo-eee! Those ribbons
are the bees' knees.
Uh-huh!
All right then, class.
You've got a lot to learn
if you want to
build a race cart.
Oh. I knew there was
gonna be a catch.
Wow, have you seen what the
carts used to look like
in the olden days?
Yeah. I know all about them.
When Ponyville
started the derby,
they decided to
use the wood
from our apple trees
for the carts.
The race has been a part of
Sweet Apple Acres ever since.
I just think these old
carts look so cool.
But I guess you and Applejack
will probably win the award
for most traditional, huh?
The Apples usually
do, but honestly,
I'd rather build the fastest
cart there is and win the race!
But I'm pretty sure
Scoot and Rainbow Dash
will take that award.
You know, I race around
so much on my scooter,
being the fastest isn't such
a big deal. Maybe I'll try
to make the wildest-looking
cart I can think of.
Really?
Sure. If I win
Most Creative,
you can totally win
the award for Fastest.
And I can win the award
for Most Traditional!
Sounds like we're all going
to try something different.
I can't wait to
tell Applejack!
Let's get to it!
GOOOOO CRUSADERS!
Are you kidding! Of course I'll
help with the Applewood Derby!
I want you to have as much fun
as I did when I was a filly.
Wait, Cloudsdale
has a derby too?
Sure! Practically every
town in Equestria has one.
I still remember
racing my cloud cart.
THIS. IS. SO. AWESOME!
WHOOHOOOOO!
And let me guess...
You won Fastest Cart.
Obviously!
So what do you say? Will you
help me make my race cart?
Help you? I'm ALL OVER IT.
I've got tons of ideas.
Don't worry, I've got a
lot of ideas of my own.
Um, what are you looking for?
The blueprint for my
Derby cart, of course.
I'll have to change it a little
cause this race is on roads,
not on clouds, but trust me,
your cart is gonna be AMAZING!
Um, OK, Rainbow Dash, thanks!
How awesome is THIS?
With Dash on my team, how
could anything go wrong?
Heh, well I'm mighty
flattered you wanna work
with your big sis on your cart.
I mean, the "Applewood
Derby" did...
...start on our farm. I know.
Well, I couldn't be more proud
to help my little sister
take the prize for
"Most Traditional!"
Actually I was kinda thinkin' of
somethin' else. Like fastest?
"Fastest?" Apple Bloom,
things aren't like they were
in the old days.
The fastest cart now has gotta
be slick and modern and...
Exactly!
...not Apple at all. The
Apples win Most Traditional.
We have since the Derby started!
Why would anypony want
to win anything else?
Now, why don't you head off
and get some chamomile vines,
some hickory sticks,
and some apple barrels
and I'll show you what an Apple
Family cart should look like.
I guess I do have a family
tradition to uphold.
THE APPLEWOOD DERBY?
Of course I'll help!
Wow, uh, Rarity, I didn't
know you'd be this excited!
Me? Oh why, I'm just itching
to right an old wrong
from long, long ago.
I designed my own cart
when I was just a filly.
And I was positive I was
going to win the prize for
"Most Creative," hooves down.
But I came in second. Second!
You? Second for Most
Creative? To whom?
But I learned a valuable lesson.
I learned to know my audience.
And the race cart audience
wants big! They want bold!
Chop, chop, everypony
out! We've got work to do!
This will take all of
my considerable skills,
but I will fashion the biggest
and boldest derby cart
to ever win the prize
for Most Creative!
Actually, I was sort of
thinking of something more...
traditional?
Oh, ha ha! Oh please, darling,
leave tradition to the Apples.
We're doing big and bold!
Soon the prize for Most Creative
will finally be in my hooves!
You mean MY hooves.
Yes, that's what I
said "my hooves."
Darling, I hope you're ready to
get an early start tomorrow.
Uh, how early?
Rarity, the sun's not even up yet!
Oh, Apples, quit complaining. In
my day, we were up even earlier!
Hey, I'd get up in the
middle of the night
if it means my cart crosses
that finish line first
and wins Fastest!
And my cart wins Most Creative!
And my cart wins
Most Traditional!
Hoo-eee!, it's
gonna be a good day!
You mean "our" carts, right?
Yes, that what we said, darling!
Yep!
Our carts!
"Their" carts? It almost
sounds like they're planning
on building them without us.
I'm sure they meant "our" carts,
like the team cart. Right?
Of course! I mean they're
all our older sisters...
practically.
Plus they've all done this
before. I'm sure they know best.
Let's just buckle
down and get to work.
Scootaloo,
where have you been?
I've only got till noon to
make the fastest cart ever.
Uh, about that.
I was really thinking of going
for the Most Creative prize.
I mean, I know all about
speed already so...
Exactly! It's all about speed.
We've gotta get across the
finish line to win a prize,
so we might as well
get there first, right?
Hey, I left a bunch of
paint cans by the road.
Bring them up here, would ya?
Nothing as fun as
painting racing stripes
on the winning cart!
Right. Fun.
Spendin' time building a
cart with my big sister,
why this is just tee-riffic!
Um, how can I help?
You can feast your
eyes on... this!
I mean, it ain't
quite finished yet.
Oh, good.
But don't it have the makings of
the best cart you ever did see?
Uh, is somethin'
wrong, Apple Bloom?
Actually, I was kinda
thinking of something
a little more modern.
And less rickety.
With maybe a chance of winning.
Bless my hooves, I
thought we covered this!
Tradition is all that counts
and who knows tradition better
than Apples? Nopony! That's who!
So are you an Apple
or are you an Apple?
I'm an Apple. But, what if I
just take off this fringe.
NO! NOT THE FRINGE!
Why, shoot, now I've gotta
start all over from scratch!
And it's almost race time.
Oh! So maybe we can redesign
it then... just a little.
No time! And who'd want
to redesign something
that's already perfect?
Right. Perfect.
OK, so I sketched
out some of my ideas.
How about a nice
yellow fringe on top?
Oh-ho, darling, the
fringe is not exactly big.
And that yellow is the least
bold color I can imagine.
Well, it doesn't
have to be yellow.
But I really do love the
old-timey style. Like this!
Sweetie Belle, precious face.
"Old-Timey" is just
another word for passé!
Remember, BIG and BOLD! I do
have a reputation to uphold!
It was one thing
to lose as a filly,
but can you imagine if I didn't
win the Most Creative now?
Ponies might stop
buying my couture!
But we're supposed to
be doing this together!
Yes, of course we are, darling.
In fact, we just
finished! Voila!
I know. You're speechless.
But if that isn't big and
bold, I don't know what is.
Isn't it wonderful?
Right. Wonderful.
Hey, Crusader.
How's it goin'?
Rarity's definitely made
the biggest, boldest cart
anypony's ever seen.
Wow. Well, Applejack's built
something so traditional
it's practically an antique.
No matter what I say, there's
no talking Rainbow Dash
out of making the fastest
cart in Equestria.
Doesn't look like any of us
ended up with what we wanted.
But I'm sure our older sisters
know what they're doing, right?
Right.
And even if our carts aren't
exactly what we had in mind,
it'll still be fun to drive
them to the finish line.
Sure. The race is
the best part!
Yeah. CMCs behind the wheels!
Yeah!
Derby Racers, to
the starting line!
The race is about
to start, Scootaloo.
You better shake a leg if you
want a ride in the winning cart.
You too, Sweetie Belle. There's
only one seat left aboard
this creative masterpiece and
it's just for you. Woo-hoo!
Whoa, ponies! Wait for me!
This traditional cart handles at
the exact perfect pace. Slow!
And I got the passenger seat all
warmed up for you, Apple Bloom!
Passenger seat?
Ugh. They're the only
older ponies driving!
First they built the carts;
now they're gonna drive them?
I know they were
all excited to help,
but I don't think they're
really helping any more.
We better hurry if we want to
be a part of this race at all!
Um, aren't you all
missing somepony?
They'll be along.
And uh, usually the younger
ponies drive the carts.
Darling, do these look
like "usual" carts to you?
Racers, on your marks.
Get set... GO!
AAAAH!
AAAAHHHH!
AAAHHH... can't
we go any faster?
Faster? Don't be
silly; this is perfect!
Ugh.
♪ GO GO GO! ♪
♪ Check me out: racin' the
Derby! ♪
♪ Check out my old-fashioned
cart! ♪
♪ Check me out: racing
the Derby ♪
♪ in my original work of art! ♪
♪ Check me out:
faster than ever
There's nopony can
catch me now! ♪
♪ Let me out! I'd do it over ♪
♪ if I only knew how! ♪
♪ Giddy-up,
Derby Racers! ♪
Derby Racers ♪
♪ GO GO GO! ♪
♪ My cart's the most original! ♪
♪ Designed with imagination. ♪
♪ My cart's the most
traditional! ♪
♪ Just plain no complications. ♪
♪ Look at me I am the Ace! ♪
♪ Might as well give
up the chase. ♪
♪ Wish we could stop this race,
start again and do it our way. ♪
Having any fun yet?
Nope! Maybe if we could
go a little faster.
♪ Giddy-up,
Derby Racers! ♪
Derby Racers ♪
♪ GO GO GO! ♪
♪ Gotta get some attention
if I want that ribbon! ♪
♪ Gotta push the limits further,
blow away the competition! ♪
♪ Gotta coast on through, just
relax we're gonna cruise it. ♪
♪ Guess I don't really care ♪
♪ since we're clearly
gonna lose it. ♪
♪ See everypony's watching,
presentation is our glory. ♪
♪ Just passed you even faster,
speed is king end of story! ♪
♪ Bigger, Bolder
down the track ♪
♪ Love the view from
the back of the pack. ♪
♪ Won't stop, we're
on the attack! ♪
♪ Too late to take it
all back! ♪
♪ Giddy-up,
Derby Racers! ♪
Derby Racers ♪
♪ GO GO ♪
LOOK OUT!
Oh! My beautiful swan
cart is an ugly duckling!
And my old time cart is
a rootin'-tootin' wreck!
It still counts as a win if I
push my cart across, right?
THEY'RE NOT YOUR CARTS!
HUH?
We were supposed
to design them.
And we were supposed
to drive them.
The Derby was supposed to be
for us, not the three of you!
Now you've ruined
it for everypony!
Yes. Well, I suppose
we might have gotten
a teensy bit carried away.
But I thought you
all wanted our help.
We did. We wanted your
help to build our carts,
but we all ended
up with carts
that are what each
of you wanted.
Umm-hmm.
Well, why didn't
you say anything?
You've all done the race before.
I just figured you knew best.
Plus it's hard to speak
up to older ponies.
Oh, I certainly
understand that,
but you mustn't think older
ponies automatically know best.
And we probably could
have done a better job
of listening to you.
I guess we owe all
three of you an apology.
Maybe not just us.
Um. How do you feel
about a do over?
I think that's a
wonderful idea.
But maybe the older ponies
should sit this one out.
Thanks for helping us fix up our
carts. Pretty creative, right?
I know it's not traditional, but
it sure looks fast, don't it?
You know, darling, I can't
believe I'm saying this,
but that yellow fringe
is rather bold after all!
Thanks, everypony! We couldn't
have done it without you.
Yup, I sure am glad
Ms. Cheerilee agreed
to run the race over again.
Well, it isn't every year I
get to say this twice, but...
Derby Racers, to
the starting line!
Racers, on your
marks, get set, go!
Whoo-hoo!
And it's probably best
keeping all the grownups
on the sidelines, but what
are we supposed to do now?
I think I have an idea.
Ah! Much better. Honestly,
I'm not sure why we wanted
to race those carts
in the first place.
Seriously! This is the most
relaxed I've been all day.
GO SCOOTALOO! GO!
WHOO-WHOO-WHOO-WHOO!
Er, I mean... this is the
life. Right, ponies?
Ah!