Thank you, little squirrel.
But remember, these flowers
are for Princess Celestia.
Only the prettiest ones will do.
Hellooo, little guy.
I've never seen anything like you before.
Oh! Are you hungry?
Here you go.
I guess you *were* hungry.
You're the cuuutest thing ever!
I can't wait to show you to my friends.
Oh! Hurry up, Spike!
This place isn't gonna clean itself!
It also didn't mess itself up.
Princess Celestia will be here tomorrow!
I thought this was just an unofficial, casual visit.
There's nothing casual about a visit from royalty!
I want this place to be spotless.
And you've barely made a dent in the clutter!
Maybe you should...
start reading them... one at a time!
Everything's got to be perfect.
No time for fooling around!
You know, this would be an awful lot easier...
...if there weren't two of us here
getting under each other's feet.
Great idea. You clean, I'll go see how
everyone else's preparations are coming.
Or maybe I should...?
What happened to the rest of her name?
We couldn't fit it all in.
You can't hang a banner that says
"Welcome Princess Celest".
Take it down and try again.
That looks perfect. Keep up the good work.
Hello, Mr. and Mrs. Cake.
How's the banquet coming?
It would be coming a little better if...
Pinkie! What are you doing?!
Those sweets are supposed to be for the Princess!
I-I know. That's why I'm tasting them.
Somepony needs to make sure that everything
is tasty enough to touch the royal tongue.
And I, Pinkie Pie, declare that
these treats are fit for a king!
Or a queen! Or a princess!
Twilight! Pinkie! You won't believe...!
Oh. I'm sorry. Uh... Am I interrupting?
No, not at all. Come on in
and make yourself at home.
What's going on, Fluttershy?
You won't believe what I found
at the edge of the Everfree Forest.
Come on out, little guy. It's okay.
Three?
They're amazing! What are they?
I'm not sure. I'm also not sure
where these other two came from.
I'll take one off your hoofs.
I've never seen anything so...
...ADORABLE!
Besides, it'll be nice to have
a companion for Spike...
...so won't bother me so much
while I'm studying.
Pinkie, do you want the other one?
Ugh! A parasprite? Are you kidding?
-Ugh?
-A para-what?
How could you not like...
Now I gotta go find a trombone!
A what?
A trombone. You know...
Typical Pinkie.
[Stand still, Rainbow Dash.]
I can't! I need to fly!
This is way too boring for me.
Do you want to look nice
for Princess Celestia or not?
Wow! Rarity, those outfits are gorgeous!
Hm, thank you, Twilight.
Nice to know *someone* appreciates my talents.
Sooo boooring.
Huh?
What's that sound, Twilight?
Wow! What are they?
The better question is: where did they come from?
I only had one a minute ago.
Uh, I'll take one!
Me too. Oh, they're perfect!
Does anypony know where I can find an accordion?
Girls! Hello! This is important!
Durgh! Thanks a lot!
Oh, the decorations... the banquet...
I really hope everything comes
together in time for tomorrow.
What's there to worry about?
Spike!
Wake up! What happened?!
What's going on?
Where did they come from?
I don't know. The little guy got hungry
in the night, so I gave him a snack, but...
...I have no idea where these others came from.
Oh no! They're messing up all my hard work!
The Princess will be here in a few hours!
Spike! Help me round up these little guys!
What does it... look like I'm... doing?
I know, I know. "Stop fooling around."
Get off me!
Not only are you adorable...
...but you're also quite useful.
Oh! Are you okay?
Eeew!
Gross, gross, gross!
No creature that behaves so revoltingly
is allowed in my boutique!
Look, Rarity! Applejack lent me a harmonica!
Isn't that great?
And not a moment too soon.
Pinkie, I'm a little busy right now.
And I'm not?! You know how many
more instruments I've gotta find?
A lot! That's how many.
Now if we split the list between us,
we might just make it in time.
Please, Pinkie! I don't have time
for some silly scavenger hunt.
I've got a real problem.
You've got a real problem, all right.
And a banjo is the only answer!
I see we've having the same problem.
Get out!
Fluttershy knows everything about animals.
I'm sure she can tell us how to
stop them from multiplying.
Or not.
Do something, Fluttershy! Can't you control them?
I've tried everything I know.
I've tried begging and pleading
and beseeching and asking politely and...
If we can't get them under control
before the Princess arrives...
...it'll be a total disaster!
EEEW!
If you ask me, it's already a total disaster!
Here's all those apples you wanted, Fluttershy!
But I still can't figure why ya need so many.
Hey!
What do we do?
I got it!
Nopony can herd like Applejack!
Yeah! We can drive them back into the forest!
I'll rustle 'em up, but I need
everypony's help to do it.
Twilight, you and Rarity wait over there.
I'll herd the little critters
straight at ya like a funnel.
Rainbow Dash, you and Fluttershy
stay on top of 'em.
Don't let 'em fly away.
Aye, aye!
YEEHAW!
All right, y'all. Here goes nothin'!
Look out, Rarity!
That one's fixin' on gettin' away!
Keep a lean on 'em, Rainbow Dash!
Hold on, girls. We're almost there!
Pinkie!
Twilight! We don't have much time.
You're telling me? The Princess
could arrive at any moment.
Exactly! That's why I need you, girls,
to drop what you're doing...
...and help me find some maracas!
Maracas?
Pinkie, we've got much bigger problems than missing maracas!
You're right!
Getting a tuba has to be our number one goal.
Follow me!
I said: follow me!
Pinkie Pie...
...you are so random.
Ugh, you are also stubborn!
Forget her, ladies.
Focus! Head 'em up and move 'em out.
Alright!
Ouch.
We did it! Nice work, Applejack.
Couldn't have done it without y'all.
Now let's get back and clean up the mess
they made before the Princess arrives.
Okay. Everyone knows what to do, right?
We gotta work extra hard to make up for lost time.
Where did *they* come from?
Well... I may have kept just one.
I couldn't help myself. They're just...
...so cute.
We don't have time to
keep rounding up these things!
What do we do now?
We call in the weather patrol!
Time to take out the adorable trash.
YAAA!!!
Way to go, Rainbow Dash!
Looks like our problems are solved.
They will be with these cymbals!
Hey! Gimme those back!
I can't hold it! She's breaking up!
Pinkie Pie! What have you done!?
I've lost a brand new pair of cymbals,
that's what I've done!
Will you forget about your
silly instruments for one second?
You're ruining our efforts to save Ponyville!
Me?! Ruin?!
I'm not the ruiner. I am the ruinee!
Or is it ruiness?
Ruinette?
Come on, girls!
There's no reasonin' with that one.
She's a few apples short of a bushel.
Hey! I'm trying to tell you all
that the ruining is on the other hoof!
If you just slowed down and LISTENED TO ME...!
What do we do?
They're eating all the food in town.
My apples!
We've gotta do something!
I got it! I'll cast a spell to make them
stop eating all the food.
Look! Tambourines! If you could all just...!
Hey! It worked. They're not
eating the food anymore.
Oh no. If they get inside my store...
EVERYPONY FOR HERSELF!
MY OUTFITS!
Go on! Shoo! Get out! Naughty, naughty!
I'll save you!
No woodland creature's gonna
eat the Apple family's crop!
Brace yourself, y'all!
Here they come!
Didn't see that one comin'.
Help!
They're eating the words!
Help.
Have you gone mad?
Zecora! These little guys
are devouring Ponyville!
And the Princess is on her way!
Can you help us? Please?
Oh, monster of so little size.
Is that a parasprite before my eyes?
I don't know! Is it?
Tales of crops and harvests consumed.
If these creatures are in Ponyville...
...you're doomed.
Oh no! Here she comes!
Okay. Here's the plan.
Rainbow Dash, you distract them.
Good! Everyone else, we need to build
an exact copy of Ponyville right over there.
We've got less than a minute.
Zecora was right. We're doomed.
Oh no. The Princess's procession
is here. It's all over!
Pinkie? We're in the middle of a crisis here.
This is no time for your...
...nonsense?
Look!
Twilight Sparkle, my prized pupil!
Hello, Princess!
So lovely to see you again, as well as your friends.
So... How was the trip? Hit much traffic?
What is this?
These creatures are adorable!
They're not *that* adorable.
I'm terribly honored that you
and the good citizens of Ponyville...
...have organized a parade in honor of my visit.
Parade? Oh! Yes! The parade!
Unfortunately that visit is going to
have to wait for another time.
I'm afraid an emergency has
come up in Fillydelphia.
Apparently there's been some sort of infestation.
An... infestation?
Yes. A swarm of incredibly bothersome
creatures has invaded the poor town.
I'm sorry, Twilight, to have to
put you all through so much trouble.
Trouble? Oh... What trouble?
Before I have to go...
...would you care to give me your latest report
on the magic of friendship in person?
My... report?
Haven't you learned anything about friendship?
Actually, I have.
I've learned that sometimes the solution to your
problems can come from where you least expect it.
It's a good idea to stop and listen to
your friends' opinions and perspectives.
Even when they don't always seem to make sense.
I'm so proud of you, Twilight Sparkle.
And I'm very impressed with your friends as well.
It sounds like you're all learning
so much from each other.
Thank you, Princess.
Hey! What happened to the Princess?
Emergency in Fillydelphia.
Some sort of "infestation".
Oh no! Have they got parasprites too?!
Well, have tuba, will travel.
I think the Princess can handle it.
So you knew what those critters
were all along, huh, Pinkie Pie?
Well, duh! Why do you think I was so frantic
to get my hooves on all these instruments?
I tried to tell you.
We know, Pinkie Pie.
And we're sorry we didn't listen.
You're a great friend.
Even if we don't always understand you.
Thanks, guys. You're all great friends too.
Even when I don't understand me.
You saved my reputation with Princess Celestia!
And more importantly, you saved Ponyville!
Or not.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000