Whoa!
Twilight! Mail's here!
Are you all right?
We just had a really
heavy delivery today.
Is it a deluxe set of Special
Edition Ogres & Oubliettes
figurines that I'm
totally surprised by
and haven't been hinting
that I need forever!?
Well... it's
for Twilight.
Awww.
Thank you!
You're welcome!
Huh, it's from
Princess Celestia.
So's this. Really?
She couldn't have
put it into the box?
"My Dearest Twilight.
I have been conducting
a thorough cleaning
of the castle,
and I came across a few items
of yours in your old room.
I thought you might
want them back."
I didn't even know
I'd left anything!
Aw, look!
Remember this? It's the
macaroni picture frame
Cadance helped me make
when I was a filly!
Who could forget a
masterpiece like that?
My G1 Starswirl figure!
And some of my favorite
school scrolls!
And here's my extra,
extra credit report
on "The Impediments of Using
Magic in Everyday Chores"!
Ha! Still so true!
Is my Smash Fortune
comic in there?
I've been looking
for that for years!
Agh!
Hold this.
Oh, no, oh no, oh no!
What's wrong? It just looks
like an old library book.
Exactly! It belongs to
the Canterlot Library.
That means it's...
... OVERDUE!
You don't understand, Spike!
I have a perfect library
book-return record!
Ahem. Had a perfect record.
[groan] I've never turned in a
book even a minute late!
And this one...
has been overdue since
I left for Ponyville!
Make sure you bring
this one back on time.
We've got a long
waiting list of ponies
who can't wait to read it!
I promise I won't
let you down!
Oh. Of course you
won't, dear.
If there's anypony I can
trust to take care of a book,
it's you, Twilight Sparkle!
After all, you still hold the
"Best Book Borrower" title.
Ooh! I hope I do forever!
Spike! Quick! Find
me that old copy of
"Predictions and Prophecies".
What's that for?
Well, it was a gift
for Moondancer but...
Oh, Spike.
You know we don't have time
for that sort of thing.
And then Celestia
sent me to Ponyville
and I forgot
all about this!
Dusty Pages prided herself
that no books were damaged
or lost on her watch.
And I failed her!
I've failed MYSELF!
I take it we're
going to Canterlot?
[sigh] The sooner the
better, I guess.
Uh, why are we hiding?
Don't you want to
return your book?
Yes, but what if somepony
sees me in there?
I'm the Princess
of Friendship.
Everywhere I go,
ponies recognize me.
I'll stick out
like a sore hoof!
Princess Twilight Sparkle in
a library? Stop the presses!
A late book is a
big deal, Spike!
What if Dusty Pages
revokes my library card?
Or bans me from ever
entering the building again!?
Don't you already have
most of those books
in your collection at home?
Yes, but the ones in
there have a special
Canterlot Library-y smell!
You sniff books?
You don't?
I used to LIVE in a library!
If I'm not a good example
of proper book-borrowing
behavior,
then what kind of
princess am I?
One that makes mistakes
like everypony else.
Trust me, once you return that
book, you'll feel way better.
Thanks, Spike.
Let's go.
Agh!
[disguised voice]
Ahem. I have a book to return.
Princess Twilight!
So good to see you!
Need some recommendations
from the new release section?
[gasp] Is that the
new edition of
"Mooncurve's Seven
Theories on Bending Time"?
I have been waiting
for the release since--
Uhh I mean, uh, no
books today, thanks.
But I do need to speak with
Dusty Pages about a... [ahem]
sensitive matter.
Dusty who?
Dusty Pages! The head librarian?
She's worked here forever.
I'm sorry, Princess.
I don't know her.
Now, was there some
other way I can help
the Library's Best
Book Borrower?
Just ask her where to
return an overdue book.
It's no big deal. It
happens all the time!
Not to me, it doesn't!
[sigh] Fine.
Fine! Oh, no. I didn't even
think about the late fine!
A book out this long
will probably cost
a thousand bits!
She--I mean we, have
an overdue book.
Oh! Well, that's no
problem at all.
In fact, it happens
all the time!
See?
I'll just find it
in the card catalog.
Er.. Number one-eight-nine-oh-five. Got it!
Ohhhhh, wow. Eeeesh.
I haven't seen a book
this late in, well, ever.
Ahem. You need to go and
see First Folio
in the "Grossly Overdue
Book Return Office
for Ponies Who
Should Know Better."
Don't pull any punches
with those names, do ya?
And that office would be...?
In the basement.
[whispers] Because of the SHAME.
Whoa. Ugh. Looks like nopony
ever goes down here.
Nopony except
undependable rule breakers
who deserve all the
horrors this hallway holds.
And their faithful
dragon companions.
Uh. Hey, looks like First Folio
left a note on the door.
Abandon hope all
ye who enter?
"Out to lunch on
Restaurant Row."
Guess we'll have
to try back later.
Oh, no! I can't wait another
minute to return this book!
In the time it took
us to get there,
I racked up another--
Seventeen bits in late fees!
We're going to lunch!
Good, cause I'm starving!
Oh. You mean to
find First Folio.
Can we at least
get take-out?
Tell me if you see any
librarian-type ponies.
Twilight, we've
tried this
at three other
restaurants already.
And my late fines
are already up
another 26 more bits!
Waiter, we're
ready to order.
Oh, I'm not actually a---
Three samosas, two
curry specials...
Do you think that's
enough for the two of us?
Hm. I would probably order some
Naan as well? For the table.
Sounds great!
Twilight? Is that you?
Moondancer! How
have you been?
I'm just visiting.
No real reason. Heh.
Well, it's good to see you!
I'm just meeting my friend,
First Folio, for lunch.
Do you want to join us?
First Folio!? YES!
I mean, thank you.
Princess Twilight!
Good to meet you!
Did you know your picture
is still up in our library
as the Best Book Borrower.
Yeeeeah.
I was hoping I could talk
to Dusty Pages about that.
Oh, Dusty Pages left
the library moons ago.
Didn't you know?
Mm mm.
Oh, I heard she was
forced to leave.
It's so sad. She
loved the library.
Wait. Forced to leave?
Uh huh, yeah. She had a
perfect librarian record,
until one careless pony
didn't return a book.
Ruined it all.
Are you OK, Twilight?
Uh huh... Would...
you excuse me?
That's why you only order
spicy if you can take it.
Twilight, what's wrong?
Dusty Pages isn't working
at the library anymore
because I didn't
return this book!
Spike! I think I got her FIRED!
Twilight! The
library is that way!
Change of plans! We're
going to Dusty's house.
She used to invite me
over for tea all the time.
But what about your late fees?
They're not as important
as making things right.
Wait, so you're not
going to return the book?
No. Dusty Pages is! It's
my fault she lost her job.
So if I give her the book,
she can get her old job back!
It'll fix everything!
Didn't ya see the sign?
"No Salesponies"!
Oh, I'm not
selling anything!
No carolers either.
No surveys, no petitions,
no free literature--
No problem!
I'm just looking for somepony
who used to live here.
I'm pretty sure
this was her house.
Dusty Pages?
Yes!
Hold on.
She moved to Silver somethin'.
Shoals? Seas? Surfer? Whatever.
When you find her,
give her this.
It's been stackin' up
for years.
And tell her to
CHANGE. HER. ADDRESS!
"Silverstable Community..
for the best Golden Years."
This HAS to be it!
I hope so.
It's the last "Silver" spot
on the map we haven't looked.
Whoa! This place is--
Terrible, I know!
There's not a single
bookshelf in sight.
Poor Dusty.
Excuse me.
Yes. How may I help you?
Do you have a resident
named Dusty Pages?
Oh, yes! Her apartment
is in the next complex.
Ground floor.
Thank you!
I can't believe that my
carelessness sent her here
when she could be
happily surrounded
by millions of
wonderful-smelling books!
You realize that might just
be a "you" thing, right?
[gasp]
There she is! Here we go.
Aarrgghh!
She's bound to
be back soon.
Maybe we should just wait here.
No. We are
fixing this... NOW!
This place isn't that
big. We can find her!
Sorry to interrupt your
plein air painting,
but we're looking for Dusty
Pages. Have you seen her?
Sure have.
And...?
She had to leave
early to get to her
fengbi de ti session.
Which is right
before she leads
the woodworking
class with me.
Then she's on
to windsurfing!
Ooh! And don't forget theatre rehearsal!
Dusty's playing the
lead role... again.
Then there's her
band practice later.
Thank you!
Wow, Dusty sounds
like one busy pony.
Oooh! She's just filling her
days with distractions
to cover the pain of
losing the best job ever!
But not for long!
DUSTY PAGES! Finally!
C'mon, Spike.
Wait! She looks
pretty happy up there.
Trust me, it's
all an act.
She'll be a lot happier
when I deliver the good news
that she can go back to
working at the library!
Care to take five, everypony?
Oh! Twilight Sparkle? My stars!
It's so wonderful to see you!
What are you
doing here?
I've been looking all
over Equestria for you!
I need to tell
you something.
You brought my
mail! Oh, thank you!
No. I mean, yes, we did, but
that's not why we're here.
I let you down.
And I can't forgive myself
until I set things right.
I don't remember you
doing anything wrong.
You told me to take special
care of a book I checked out
from the Canterlot library.
And I never brought it back!
[gasp] It was YOU that
had that book out?
The one that broke
my perfect record?
But now you can bring
it to Canterlot Library
and get your job back!
No thank you!
I don't ever need to
see that library again.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have somewhere to be!
Do you mind?
I don't understand.
If Dusty Pages won't go
back to Canterlot Library
and explain everything,
then she won't be able
to get her job back.
Even worse, her record
will remain... imperfect!
And yours will, too?
Well. Yeah! But that
doesn't matter anymore.
Really?
Well, maybe a little
bit. Oh, no... BITS!
The late fines! How
much do I owe now?
Uh... You don't want to know.
It would have been worth
all the bits in Equestria
if I'd made things
right with Dusty.
I wish I knew why
she won't go back.
Why don't you ask her?
She didn't seem
to want to talk.
You surprised her.
And she probably had something
else on her schedule.
That thing is PACKED. C'mon,
what've you got to lose?
Now that I've messed
up this much. Nothing.
You're right, Spike.
It's worth a try.
Where do you think she
went? Crochet, bingo...
A squishy fruit
foodfight tournament!?
Hey, everypony! We come in--
...er pieces.
Stop! We just wanna talk to
Dusty Pages for a moment!
Please?
TIME OUT!
Oof!
Next time, you should rent gear!
We're not actually
here for the game.
I.. was hoping you'd
give me another chance
to talk to you about
the library book.
This really means a
lot to you, doesn't it?
Mm hm. I know I
ruined your life
by not returning
my book on time.
And I will do anything I
can to make it up to you.
Even promise to never take a
book out of the library again,
if that's what it takes.
That.. is not the
reaction we expected.
Twilight, dear. You've
got it all backwards!
I'm not upset with you.
You're not?
No! If I'm mad at
anypony, it's me.
All those years I spent
hiding away in that library,
trying to be perfect...
When your book never came in,
I felt something.. exhilarating!
What was it?
Freedom!
From books?
From perfection!
I was too stubborn to know
when to call it quits.
It took your mistake
to make me realize
that I wasn't living
the life I wanted!
You mean you weren't fired?
You left the library
because you wanted to?
Twilight, your late
book was the best thing
that ever happened to me!
Now, I'm not afraid to try
things I might fail at.
In fact, sometimes messing up
teaches me more than
getting it right!
You're sure you don't
want to return it
and get that
perfect record back?
Agh!
Oh, good. It was
a yellow one.
You can still
see the words!
But it'll have a stain!
That doesn't change
the truth inside it.
Wait. Did you even
read that thing?
Actually, er... no.
I guess I didn't.
"PERFECTION."
And the next part...
"The Impossible Pursuit."
Oh. That might've been
useful to look at earlier...
Hm. Your total late fees come to...
However much it
is, I'll cover it!
Uh, do you have a
monthly payment plan?
...twenty-eight bits.
That's it!?
Yeah. Most ponies don't
know it caps at a month.
Probably because
we don't tell them.
Thank you! Your
account is back to normal.
Although we will be taking down
your Best Book Borrower picture...
Um, is that really necessary?
It just seems so.. permanent.
I mean, I did return
the book, after all.
Ahem.
OK. Letting the perfection go...
You want me to
reshelf this for you?
Nope. It's an old edition.
We've already replaced
it with a new copy.
In that case, can we keep it?
It might be a good
reminder to have around.
You're sure? It's got a stain...
That's what makes it perfect.