All right, ponies.
Listen up!
We're all ears!
Right, Bulk Biceps?
Nu-uh, I'm all muscles.
Yeah!
I like your attitude,
Bulk Biceps,
but it's gonna take more
than muscles and "yeah"s
to get us to the
Equestria Games.
We are the aerial relay team,
and it's up to the three of us
to make sure that we
qualify at the tryouts.
And do I need to remind
you how much I...
I mean, Ponyville
wants to qualify
and make it to the games?
I remember!
I really, really, really want to
qualify for you AND Ponyville!
Bring it on!
Gimme a "P" for Ponyville!
"P" Ponyville!
"P"!
Oh. Thanks, Pinkie Pie!
That was a scary, I
mean great, cheer.
Just make sure you
have one ready
for when we qualify for
the Aerial Relay.
And after that, for
when we win gold medals
at the Equestria Games!
Not so fast!
If yer gonna be good,
yer gonna be better
with some a' my Apple
Brown Betty's in ya!
They're perfect.
"P" is for perfect!
All right, team!
Show me what you've got!
Put some bend into those knees!
Flap those wings!
And I want to see all four
hooves off the ground
on the count of three!
One, two, three!
Don't forget to breathe
while you're up there!
"P" is for...
uh... pain?
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
Good luck, Rainbow Dash!
Sorry we couldn't fly with
you on the aerial relay,
but the air sprinters
needed us, too.
Too bad we can only
compete in one event.
But, rules are rules!
Good luck!
It was nice of you to
be part of a team
that doesn't have uh....
the strongest flyers.
Nothing nice about it!
I know that I can pick
up the slack for anypony.
With me on the
team, we'll qualify.
I'm sure of it!
Ponyville is very
lucky to have you.
Yeah, I'm pretty awesome!
I am so proud to be
representing Ponyville!
It's such an honor to even
try out for the games.
I just hope I don't
let anypony down.
We'll make them proud.
"P" is for PROUD!
We're going to be the best
fans anypony has ever seen!
Can't wait to see what
everypony else is wearing,
even though I am absolutely
sure they won't be better
than the Ponyville
uniforms I'm designing
for the Equestria games.
And we WILL make it
to the games
once everypony carbo loads
on my Apple Brown Bettys.
I can't wait!
That's Rainbow Dash.
She's an awesome flyer!
I heard that she's flying the
last third of the relay,
which means everypony
else is gonna have to be
way ahead to beat her.
The Wonderbolts!
I hear they're
flying for Cloudsdale.
Then Cloudsdale
will definitely qualify.
They're the best
flyers ever!
And the game is on!
Nice to see there's some
real competition here.
Two more days of practice,
then we'll see you in the air,
Rainbow Dash!
If you're lucky!
The Wonderbolts know a
winner when they see one!
And we'll be winners just as
soon as we practice.
Right, team?
Right!
YEAH!
Hooray!
And um...
I'm with her.
Hooray!
Give us some Clouds!
Give us some Dale!
And what do you get?
Cloudsdale!
Whooooo!
Where can I get pom
poms like those?
So, do I need to remind you
of what our goal is here?
Uh, maybe?
We want to qualify. We need to
be one of the first four teams
to cross the finish line.
Bulk Biceps, you're
the first flyer,
so let me see you flap it!
What the?
Sorry!
Got the idea
from them, but...
Hooves down, cakes up!
It looks like they've
got better aim.
OK, the passing of the
baton needs to be seamless.
You shouldn't miss a wing beat
or drop a hair in altitude
and whatever you do,
don't let go of it!
Are you really, really,
really, sure you're ready?
I mean, I don't want to take
it if you're not super sure.
Ready!
Ponyville can do
so much better!
I'll be back with a freshly
painted one in no time!
We were using that!
And it's not like anypony else
has color-coordinated horseshoes
or anything!
I guess someponies do!
Someponies do what?
Have a better chance
of qualifying
and going to the Equestria
Games than others.
Watch and learn.
The Cloudsdales are Wonderbolts
and Wonderbolts are the best
fliers there are.
And my personal heroes.
So maybe you can
learn something.
PLEASE learn something!
Come on, Soarin'!
Pick up the pace!
You can do better than that!
I sure hope so.
Practice! Practice!
YAY Practice!
Whoa!
Help!
Gotcha!
Awesome!
As good as any Wonderbolt!
Oh, Rainbow Dash, I'm
just so proud of you!
You scooped Soarin'
out of the sky
and brought him down to
the ground, and now?
Now he's OK.
At least, I hope he's OK.
Are you OK?
Uh, my wing hurts...
But, I'm sure it'll be
OK by the competition.
You're the best, Rainbow Dash!
Aw, it was nothing!
But if you feel like talking
about how great I am,
don't let me stop you!
"P" is for Rainbow Dash!
Um, Rainbow Dash actually
starts with an 'R.'
Never mind!
Tough break to lose a teammate
right before the tryouts.
You know...
you grew up in Cloudsdale.
So, that means you
could fly with us.
Fly?
We mean practice.
You could practice with us
until Soarin' is better.
What do you say?
Want to be our third?
I don't know.
My team really needs me to be
at my best in order to qualify.
Don't want to be too worn out by
the time the race comes around.
We put you through some
pretty intense workouts
at the Wonderbolt Academy and
you handled those just fine.
I did kick some major
tail at the Academy.
But I don't know how my
teammates will feel
about me practicing
with the competition.
Who says they
need to know?
Think about it, Rainbow Dash;
this is your chance to
fly with the winners.
All right, I'll do it!
Wise decision,
Rainbow Dash.
Awesome!
Whinny, Ponies, Whinny!
Fly on! Fly on! Fly on!
Come on, Bulk Biceps!
You can do it!
And I'm ready to
take the horseshoe...
if you want me to!
You, uh, keep doing
your wing-ups.
I'm just gonna go get
some, uh, water.
Yeah!
Too much?
It's not easy practicing
with two teams is it?
You know?
Does anypony else?
No, they're too
busy practicing
to wonder why you
keep disappearing.
Well, I've seen the
other teams practicing,
and we're still
going to qualify!
I can fly fast enough
to make up the distance.
It just seems like one of the
teams you're practicing with
needs a little more
help than the other one.
But, it's so much more fun
working out with the winners
than... um, the non-winners.
Besides, Ponyville
will still qualify!
Rainbow Dash, you
got a minute?
Uh, sure.
You could really be an
asset to our team so,
we want you to join
the Cloudsdale team...
permanently.
It looks like Soarin's
wings won't heal in time
for the trials. We want
you to fly with us.
Of course, this means you won't
be able to fly for Ponyville.
But let's face it, even
with you on their team,
their chances of qualifying
for the Games are pretty slim.
So... what's it going to be?
Well, I...
Take some time to
think about it.
They want me to fly with them!
It's like a dream come true!
If you fly for Cloudsdale,
Pinkie Pie won't have
anypony to cheer for.
Rarity's uniforms
will never be seen.
And Applejack will have slaved
over those Apple Brown Bettys
for nothing.
But I really want to fly
with the BEST team!
What would you do?
I think this is a decision you
have to make on your own.
The race is tomorrow, so
you better make it soon.
Woe is me!
What's happened?
I've hurt my hoof!
All of them?
I, uh, tripped, on a, uh, foam
hoof, and landed on a, uh, "..."
Oooh, if I get my hooves
on that "...",
It'll be in big trouble!
There is no way
I can fly now.
Do you think you'll
be better by tryouts?
I'll be lucky
if I ever fly again.
I just need a little rest.
Oh, don't worry, Rainbow Dash,
we'll take care of you or,
at least somepony will, like a
medic or a doctor or a nurse.
So the Medic Pony isn't
sure what's wrong with you.
Everything! Absolutely
everything!
This'll cure everything
that ails ya.
Thank you.
I couldn't have done
that on my own.
Nothing says get better like
a little medical pizazz.
Silk slings and a
glitter bandage?
That might help.
And how is our patient doing?
I've been better.
We just wanted to let you know
that we're so sorry you're hurt
but you shouldn't worry a
bit about not being able
to be in the tryouts.
We'll be all right.
We even have a replacement.
We're so, so sorry
that you can't compete.
We all know how much you
love to fly and we promise...
Cross our hearts!
... that if we qualify and make
it to the Equestria Games
and all win gold medals,
you can have ours...
because we know how much
a gold medal means to you.
Thanks.
I think Rainbow Dash might
need to rest some more...
Don't forget your bettys!
You know, choosing not to
choose isn't really a decision.
You sure have nice friends.
Nopony's been by to visit me.
Too busy practicing, I guess.
Well, hopefully your
wing will be better soon.
Oh, it's fine.
I'm just keeping it warm in
case my team wants me back.
What do you mean,
wants you back?
Spitfire and Fleetfoot told
me that you were still
too injured to fly.
And they told me that they
were worried I wouldn't be
one hundred percent
by the tryouts,
so they were going with
somepony else.
That somepony else was me!
Until, well, until I
got hurt, that is.
So, I guess
we're all out of luck.
Cloudsdale won't qualify
without three flyers and...
Ponyville won't
qualify without you!
Too bad.
Even with Rainbow
Dash's replacement,
I don't think we're going to
qualify; no offense.
Agh! What am I going to do
with all of these now?
Uh, What were you going to
do with them before?
Maybe my Equestria
Games uniforms
will still be in
style next year.
I mean, I am pretty
fashion-forward!
Is that Rainbow
Dash... walking?
Does this mean you're
feeling better?
I feel great because I was
never hurt in the first place.
I faked my injury so that
I wouldn't have to choose
between flying for
Ponyville or Cloudsdale.
I wanted to fly with you both
and the decision was too hard.
Oh, Rainbow Dash, you
don't have to choose us.
I know you love to win,
and you should go with the
team that surely will!
I know now who I should
have been loyal to.
Good choice. Always
stick with the winners.
Ponyville!
Because it's not
just where I live,
but it's where my
friends are,
the ponies who really
care about me,
whether I can help
them win a race or not.
Are you sure that's
the right decision?
You lied to me about
Soarin's wing
just so you could
get a better flyer.
You may be a winning team,
but you're still not the kind
of team I want to be a part of.
Huh.
Rainbow Dash, you are something.
Saw it at the Academy.
Seeing it again here.
We could learn a lot from
a competitor like you.
Think we already have.
Ready to fly?
Really?
Never should have lied and tried
to replace you to begin with.
Go, Cloudsdale!
Come on, Ponyville Relay Team.
We've got a race
to get ready for!
Yeah!
Come on, Ponyville!
You can do it!
Go Fluttershy!
Whoo hoo!
Qualify Ponyville!
Woo-hoo!
Go Rainbow Dash!
Ponyville qualifies!
YEAH!
Woo hoo!
Equestria Games, here we come!
I can't deny it,
I LOVE to win.
But if I ever gotta
choose between winning
and being loyal to my friends...
I'm always gonna
choose my friends.
'Cause as much as I love
winning, I love them waaay more!