Are you sure about this, Scootaloo?
I've never even heard
of a pony zip lining before.
Neither have I, but Spike told me it was awesome!
See anything?
Tree sap and pine needles, but no cutie mark.
Plan B?
Yeah. You know where we can find
a cannon at this hour?
It's no use!
No matter what we try, we always
end up without our cutie marks.
And surprisingly often covered in tree sap.
Maybe we should do something less dangerous.
Like pillow testing.
Or flower sniffing.
This town is full of ponies,
who have their cutie marks.
Why don't we ask them how they did it?
That's a great *safe* idea.
Yeah! And we can start with
the coolest pony in Ponyville.
-Applejack!
-Rarity!
Come on, guys, I said "cool"!
You know who I'm talking about.
She's fast. She's tough.
She's not afraid of anything!
Pinkie Pie?
No! The greatest flyer ever
to come out of Cloudsdale.
Fluttershy?
No! Rainbow Dash!
Oh! Yeah, that makes much more sense.
Of course!
Let's do it. Let's find how
Rainbow Dash earned her cutie mark!
YEAH!
Get back here, you thievin' vermins!
Thievin' what now?
Apple Bloom?
Hey sis! How'd you get your cutie mark?
I never told you that story?
Hey! I thought we were gonna ask Rainbow Dash.
We need all the help we can get.
Fine.
Why, shoot.
I was just a little filly.
Even littler than y'all.
I didn't want to spend my life
at a muddy old apple farm.
I wanted to live the sophisticated life.
Like my Aunt n' Uncle Orange.
So I set out to try my luck in a big city.
Manehattan!
The most cosmopolitan city in all of Equestria.
Ey! Outta the way, you rube!
I knew I'd find out who I was
meant to be in Manehattan.
Aunt Orange! Uncle Orange!
Thank y'all so much for lettin' me stay!
"Y'all". Ahahaha...
Isn't she just the living end?
How quaint.
Don't worry. We'll have you acting
like a true Manehattanite in no time.
And how are you finding good old Manehattan?
Oh, it's simply divine.
Very well said, my dear.
Although, I must admit the city noise
took some getting used to.
Where I'm from, nights are so quiet...
...you seldom hear a peep
until the roosters wake you.
The... what?
I say, my dear, what
in the world is a "rooster"?
What's he talking about?
What do I say?
I don't wanna look like a fool.
Dinner is served.
Thank goodness. Being a city pony's hard work.
I'm so hungry I could eat a...
Cock-a-doodle-doo...
Oh, I wonder what Granny Smith
and Big Macintosh are up to.
I bet they're applebuckin' their way
through the Red Delicious trees.
Oh, what I wouldn't give for just one bite...
I never felt so homesick in all my days
as I did right then.
It was amazin'!
A rainbow pointin' right back to... home.
In that moment, it all became clear.
I knew right then just who I was supposed to be.
That's when this here appeared.
I've been happily workin' in the farm ever since.
There they are!
Get back here, ya thievin' vermins!
That was such a sweet story!
Sweet? Try sappy.
Come on! We've got to find Rainbow Dash
and hear the cool way to get a cutie mark.
All right, little ones. This way. This way.
You really should be more careful.
Somepony could get hurt.
Why you in such a hurry anyway?
We're trying to find Rainbow Dash, so we
can hear how she earned her cutie mark.
Oh, that would be interesting.
You know, I wouldn't have gotten
my cutie mark if it weren't for her.
Rainbow Dash?! Really?!
Oh yes. It all started at Summer Flight Camp.
You'd never guess, but when
I was little I was very shy.
And a very weak flyer.
Nice going, "Klutzershy"!
They oughta ground you permanently.
HA! My baby brother can fly better than you!
It was the most humiliating moment of my life.
And then, out of nowhere...
Leave her alone!
Ooh, what are you gonna do, "Rainbow Crash"?
Keep making fun of her and we'll find out!
You think you're such a big shot?
Why don't you prove it?
Whaddya have in mind?
-You're going down!
-In history, maybe.
See you boys at the finish line!
I've never seen such beautiful creatures.
Butterflies don't fly as high as my cloud home.
And I've never been near the ground before.
What is this place
Filled with so many wonders
Casting its spell
That I am now under
Squirrels in the trees
And the cute little bunnies
Birds flying free
And bees with their honey
Honeeey!
Oh, what a magical place
And I owe it all to the pegasus race
If I knew the ground had so much up its sleeve
I'd have come here sooner and never leave!
Yes, I love everything!
Shhh...
It's okay.
You can come out.
Everything's okay.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Somehow I had the ability to communicate
with the animals on a different level.
Wait, wait, wait. What happened to Rainbow Dash?
What about the race?
Oh. Well, I wasn't there so
I don't really know what happened.
Come on, Crusaders. We've gotta find her.
Besides, I can't take any more singing.
Maybe my sister knows where she is?
Bye, Fluttershy!
Bye, girls!
How do we get roped into this?
Oh, we'll never hear Rainbow Dash's story.
Are you girls still obsessing
over your cutie marks?
Of course! Most other fillies
at school already have theirs.
Mmm, I know how you feel.
For the longest time I couldn't
figure out why I didn't have mine.
Well done, Rarity. Your costumes are very nice.
Nice? They need to be spectacular!
And the performance is tomorrow!
I tried every trick I could think of,
but nothing seemed to work.
The costumes just weren't right.
And the play opened that night!
Maybe I'm not meant to be
a fashionista after all.
What's going on?!
I had no idea where my horn was taking me.
But unicorn magic doesn't
happen without a reason.
I knew this had to do with my love of fashion...
...and maybe even my cutie mark!
I knew that this was...
MY DESTINY!
A ROCK?!
That's my destiny?!
What is your problem, horn?
I followed you all the way out here for a rock?!
Dumb rock!
Ugh!
These namby-pamby stories aren't getting us
any closer to our cutie marks!
They're all about finding who you really are
and boring stuff like that.
Yes, Scootaloo, that's exactly...
Come on, girls! We need action!
We need Rainbow Dash!
As a young filly in Canterlot, I've always
wanted to go to the Summer Sun Celebration...
...where Princess Celestia raises the sun.
And I saw the most amazing,
most wonderful thing I've ever seen.
I poured myself into learning
everything I could about magic.
My parents decided to enroll me in
Princess Celestia's School for Gifted Unicorns.
It was a dream come true!
Except for one thing...
I had to pass an entrance exam!
Well, Miss Sparkle?
We don't have all day.
I knew this was the most
important day of my life...
...that my entire future would be affected
by the outcome of this day...
...and I was about to blow it!
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Twilight Sparkle.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't mean...
You have a very special gift.
I don't think I've ever come across
a unicorn with your raw abilities.
Huh?
But you need to learn to tame
these abilities through focused study.
Huh?!
Twilight Sparkle, I'd like to make you
my own personal protege here at the school.
HUH?!
Well?
YES!!!
One other thing, Twilight.
More?
My cutie mark!
Yesyesyesyesyesyesyesyesyes
yesyesyesyesyesyesyesyes...
-Okay, okay.
-We're happy for you, Twilight.
Yeah, thrilled. Let's get out of here
while we still can.
...yesyes, YEEEES!
Are you okay?
Um... yes.
Aaargh, why don't ever smash into Rainbow Dash?!
You're looking for Rainbow Dash?
If I was her, I'd be at Sugarcube Corner.
Of course, if I was anyone,
I'd be at Sugarcube Corner.
Hey! I have an idea!
Wanna go to Sugarcube Corner?
Well, we're sort of looking for Rainbow Dash,
so we can hear how she got her cutie mark.
Cutie mark? Come with me
and I'll tell you how I got mine!
Why not?
Awright!
My sisters and I were raised
on a rock farm outside of Ponyville.
We spent our days working the fields.
There was no talking. There was no smiling.
There were only rocks.
We were in the south field, preparing to
rotate rocks to the east field.
Then all of a sudden...
I've never felt joy like that before.
It felt so good I just
wanted to keep smiling forever.
And I wanted everyone I knew to smile too...
...but rainbows don't come along that often.
I wondered, how else could I create some smiles?
We better harvest the rocks from the south field.
Pinkamena Diane Pie! Is that you?
Mom! I need you and dad
and the sisters to come in here. Quick!
Surprise!
You like it? It's called...
...a party!
Oh. You don't like it.
You like it!
I'm so happy!
And that's how Equestria was made.
Wha... huh?
Look! We're here!
Maybe on the way home I can tell you
the story of how I got my cutie mark.
It's a gem!
Oh, come on. She's just being Pinkie Pie.
Rainbow Dash! You're here!
I hear *you're* looking for my cutie mark story.
You have no idea what I've been through
today to hear that story.
It all happened during the race at Flight Camp...
...where I stood alone against all odds
to defend Fluttershy's honor.
I've never flown like THAT before.
That freedom was unlike anything I've ever felt.
The speed, the adrenaline, the wind in my mane...
I liked it!
A lot.
Later, "Rainbow Crash"!
Hey!
Turns out the only thing
I liked more than flying fast...
...was winning!
Most people thought that the sonic rainboom
was just an old mare's tale.
But that day... The day I discovered racing...
...I proved that the legends were true.
I made the impossible happen!
And that, little ones,
is how you earn a cutie mark.
Wooooow...
Wait a second.
I heard that explosion.
And I saw the rainbow too.
Rainbow Dash, if you hadn't scared the animals...
...I never would have learned I could
communicate with them and gotten my cutie mark.
I heard that boom! And right afterwards there was
amazing rainbow that taught me to smile.
When I got my cutie mark...
...I saw a rainbow that pointed me home.
I bet it was your sonic rainboom!
There an explosion I could never explain,
when I got my cutie mark.
This is uncanny!
If that explosion didn't happen when it did...
...I would have blown my entrance exam.
Rainbow Dash, I think you helped me
earn my cutie mark too!
We all owe our cutie marks to you!
Do you realize what this means?
All of us had a special connection
before we even met.
We've been BFFs forever
and we didn't even know it!
Come here, y'all.
Gimme a break.
Come on, Crusaders!
Maybe we just need to try zip lining again.
Hey. How about a song?
NOOOOO!
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"Today I learned something amazing."
"Everypony everywhere has a special
magical connection with her friends..."
"...maybe even before she's met them."
"If you're feeling lonely and you're
still searching for your true friends..."
"...just look up in the sky."
"Who knows? Maybe you and your future
best friends are all looking at the same rainbow."
Gross!
When did you get so cheesy?
Just write it, Spike.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000