Mail's here!
Please be a "yes".
YES!
She can make it!
Going out on a limb here,
but I'm guessing that
Princess Cadance said she
can come this weekend.
I'm finally going to get to
spend some quality time
with my sister-in-law.
This is the best news EVER!
Um, so sorry for
barging in like this.
But I'm so excited I just
couldn't wait to tell somepony.
The Equestrian Society for the
Preservation of Rare Creatures
has given me permission to
observe the rarest, tiniest,
most adorable magical creatures
in all of Equestria!
The Breezies!
Wow, Fluttershy,
that's fantastic!
Oh! It's not just fantastic;
it just might be
the best news EVER!
I just got the most incredible
mail anypony's ever received
in all of recorded
pony postal history!
It's a flyer about a one-day
sale on used patio furniture!
Ah! Could this day
get any better?
Whoo hoo!
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
Here's a wrap in
case it gets cold.
And I packed you a basket
of nice fresh apples
in case you get hungry!
Have a great time.
Oh, I will.
And I hope you have
fun with Cadance!
ALL Aboard!
Goodbye! Goodbye, everypony!
Fluttershy!
I'll never
forget you!
Ooh, something floaty!
La la la la la.
I'm a bit nervous
about Cadance's visit.
What could you be
nervous about, Twilight?
Cadance just loves
you to pieces!
I know.
But I really want her visit
to go without a hitch!
Why wouldn't it?
Well, the last few times
we've seen each other
haven't exactly
been "worry free."
The fate of Equestria
has hung in the balance
during most of
your visits with her.
Exactly.
Cadance and I haven't
really had a chance
to just enjoy being
friends again.
Which is why it is so important
that this visit be about
the two of us having some
real quality time together.
I'm guessin' you've got a
plan that'll keep it that way.
The timing couldn't
be more perfect.
For one day only, right
here in Ponyville.
The 'Starswirl the
Bearded' Traveling Museum!
Cadance and I can spend
the whole day looking at
Starswirl the Bearded artifacts.
Sounds like the
perfect, drama-free way
to spend the day
with Cadance.
Not counting the drama
surrounding which of the bells
from his cloak they've
chosen to put on display.
Spoiler alert: It's this one.
Uh, heh heh, sorry.
Something in my throat
like a big ball of "lame?"
I think it sounds delightful.
Yep. Definitely sounds
like you two will have
some real quality
time together.
Exactly.
Just quiet time.
Your Highness.
I'm teasing, Twilight.
We're sisters-in-law;
we don't have to be so formal.
Knowing you, you've
made some plans.
Boy, have I. Hang on
just one second.
You guys...
Now, now, don't you
worry about a thing!
We'll make sure that
nothing, but nothing,
interferes with your visit.
Go on! Have a hootenanny
with your kinfolk.
You really are the best friends
a pony could ever have.
Coming, Cadance!
Ha! Two sisters-in-law bonding.
Well, I for one am
gonna make sure
that nothing spoils
their day.
What is that thing?
Whatever it is...DUCK!
Rarity, That doesn't look
anything like a duck!
What is that?
Not a what
but a "who," dear.
Oh, no, that sounds like...
DISCORD!
What in tarnation
are you doin' here?
And why the jumpin'
junebugs are you blue?
More like a shade of
cerulean, to be precise.
Whatever color you are
is the color of trouble!
Oh, Rainbow Dash,
I've changed!
Surely you remember
I was reformed
by lovely little Fluttershy!
What are you?
Sick or somethin'?
Well, of course I'm sick!
The blue skin?
These sneezes?
Could somebody find
me a fainting couch?
What?
Charming, thank you.
I can't stop sneezing
and wheezing.
In short, I need help.
If you're so sick, why have
you come here instead of...
y'know, staying home in bed and
getting over your weird illness?
Because this condition
has left me helpless.
Simply helpless.
Why, I can barely lift a spoon.
I came to find the one pony
who truly understands me
and could nurse me
back to health.
Where is that dear,
sweet Fluttershy.
I need attention!
I need some care!
I need...
You need to chill!
Fluttershy's out.
Oh, of course.
Her trip to see the
Breezies.
Ah yes, I had forgotten
that was today.
How do you know
about her trip?
She told me about
it in her last letter.
You and Fluttershy write
each other letters?
Of course we do.
We're friends.
It's just such a shame
that today of all days
is when I really need her.
Oh, well. I know
what to do.
Good thinking, head on
home, put your feet up.
I'm sure eventually
you'll have the strength
to make yourself
soup or something.
No, no, no.
I mean while she's gone, you
ponies can take care of me.
Isn't that what
friends are for?
Taking care of
each other?
Let the healing begin!
Not it!
Well! That's some way to
treat a suffering friend.
Don't you worry, Discord,
I'll give you cuddles
and read stories and
tell you all about me!
I was born on a Tuesday....
You're so sweet to offer.
But Rarity and Applejack
already volunteered
to be my own personal
nursemaids!
We did?
I SO hope you don't
mind, Pinkie Pie.
Well, as a matter of
fact, I most certainly...
Hey! Who keeps throwing away
these perfectly good balloons?
That joker's
up to somethin'.
And whatever it is, we're
gonna keep it as far away
from Twilight and Princess
Cadance as possible.
You're right.
We promised we wouldn't let
anything ruin their visit.
Although I do so wish that
"anything" had turned out
to be something else.
Did I hear you two talking about
Princess Cadance's visit
with Princess Twilight?
Maybe.
Fluttershy had mentioned
that those two
were getting together today.
How wonderful for them both.
It is so rare that those two
get to see one another.
I don't know about you, but I
sometimes wonder how close
they could actually be.
All those years apart
before being reunited?
They're plenty close.
And if they're not, this rare
opportunity to focus
on their friendship will
certainly bring them closer.
Unless...
Don't even
think about it.
They mustn't be disturbed.
Disturb them?
Why I wouldn't dream of it.
Not when I have two such
dear friends of my own
who have already offered
to take care of me.
And at such peril.
This flu of mine is highly...
Contagious.
Oh no! I've gotten
you both sick.
Whomever shall I turn to
now in my time of need?
A whole day to celebrate
Starswirl the Bearded.
What could be better?
Absolutely nothing!
Is that the candlestick
he used to light the way
when he was exploring the
caverns of Maretania?
It sure is.
Oh, I can't believe I'm getting
to see it in real life!
Discord! What are
you doing here?
Oh, dear, dear Princesses,
I'm sorry to say I'm sick.
Blue Flu.
Blue Flu?
I fear I've already given it
to poor Applejack and Rarity.
Magic health bubble.
Good thinking.
Indeed.
How would Twilight
nurse me back to health
if she was sick, too?
You will be letting
me stay at your place
until I'm all
better, won't you?
Stay?
With me?
Uh, now is not
really the best time.
Though I'm sure you
already knew that.
But taking in the sick
and the desperate:
isn't that what
Fluttershy would do?
Isn't "helping" something
that friends do for friends?
Unless, of course,
you're really saying that
you're not my friend.
No. That is not
what I'm saying.
Oh, how elated I
am to hear that.
Shall the three of us
head back to your place?
I don't want to get
anypony else sick.
I guess we don't have
much choice.
Carry me?
It isn't far.
I think you can manage.
Oh. poo
Need anything else?
Just knowing that I have
a good friend like you
to take care of me has
made me feel better already.
I'll be fine here on my own.
Oh. Just before you go.
Just a little, small request.
It's going to be fine.
We'll just get him
what he wants
and be back to the
exhibit in no time.
What was it that you needed?
♪ A little glass of
water, please? ♪
♪ A fresh-pressed
hankie if I sneeze? ♪
♪ Some tea with honey
from the bees ♪
♪ Whenever you can brew it
I'll get your tea.
♪ And while I get a little rest
A teeny tiny small request ♪
♪ Some codfish oil for my chest
Poured from a crystal cruet ♪
A crystal cruet?
♪ My goodness,
I'm a nincompoop ♪
♪ Because I fear I've
got the croup ♪
♪ I need a vat of
pumpkin soup ♪
♪ And scarves made out
of zinnias! ♪
♪ Did I say zinnias?
I meant silk! ♪
♪ Or something shiny
of that ilk, ♪
♪ And then I'll need
some nice warm milk ♪
♪ And pastry from Abyssinia.
♪ And since my stomach's
feeling crummy, ♪
♪ Why not give my aching tummy
♪ Something soothing,
something yummy ♪
♪ Piled up with noodles
♪ And a slice of homemade rye
♪ With stacks of
Swiss way up high ♪
♪ Served with sides
of sweet mince pie ♪
♪ More basil; I need oodles
Anything else?
♪ I'll be grateful for
your charity ♪
♪ Until the bitter end
♪ Because I've heard
that tenderness ♪
♪ Is what you lend
an ailing friend ♪
Tenderness; isn't
that right, friend?
Right, but...
So! Who's ready for
my big reprise?
♪ I'd like my glass
of water, please ♪
♪ Some magic spell
to cure disease ♪
♪ A firm 'gesundhoof!"
when I sneeze ♪
♪ A fresh bouquet of roses.
♪ Some lozenges
will soon appease ♪
♪ My wheezing when I
start to sneeze ♪
♪ A wig to keep
me from the breeze, ♪
♪ And blankets for my toeses.
♪ Take tweezers out
of my valise ♪
♪ and then massage
my knobby knees. ♪
♪ A bowl of peas!
Some extra cheese! ♪
♪ A cuddle with a Pekinese!
♪ A singing harp
who's named Louise! ♪
♪ A goat on skis!
A new trapeze! ♪
♪ And more and more and
more of these ♪
And just because I oughta...
♪ Make sure I'm
drinking in the right ♪
♪ Amount of fluids
day and night ♪
♪ I wish I may, I wish I might
♪ Have just one little thing
♪ Oh will you please
finally bring ♪
♪ Me that tiny glass
of water? ♪
Oops. Sorry.
All right. This
is ridiculous.
How did you even
catch this flu?
Inadequate hoof
and claw washing?
There must be some
way to just cure you.
There has to be a spell or
a remedy in one of my books.
There is one way!
And you didn't think to
mention it earlier?
Slipped my mind.
On a hill at the very
edge of Equestria,
there grows an
exquisite magic flower.
Pick the flower as it
drops its petals at sunset.
Then you can make a
magical, soothing elixir
to cure the Blue Flu.
I suppose you have a good
reason you didn't bother
to go get this flower
as soon as you
realized you were sick?
Well, I couldn't travel
that far in my condition.
By the time I got
there, I'd be too weak
to even attempt to
retrieve the flower.
So where exactly are
Cadance and I headed?
Well, you want to head north,
turn left at the--Oh.
You know, it would
be much easier
if I took you
there myself.
I thought you were in
"no condition" to travel.
I'm not.
We'll need to make
some arrangements.
Doing OK there?
To be honest, I'm a
little out of practice
when it comes to flying.
Well! Then lucky for you,
we're here.
It's just at the
top of that hill.
I'm really sorry
about this.
All I wanted was for us
to have some peaceful,
quality time together.
I know. I was looking
forward to it, too.
This is the top.
But where's that flower?
Oh.
Come on.
If we hurry, we can still
have some time together.
One last pull.
Whew! Let's get Discord and
this flower back home,
then all our problems...
What in Equestria?
Twilight! Help!
Get your coils off
my sister-in-law!
Aaahh!
Let go of my sister-in-law!
Thanks!
Don't thank me yet!
Just a little more.
And for good measure.
Are you OK?
Yes. Better than
OK, actually.
Then let's get Discord
back to Ponyville,
make that elixir, and
finally get a chance
to spend some quality
time together!
To the ends of Equestria!
To face such great danger!
And she did it for me.
She did it all for me!
For me! For me!
YOU...
WERE...
FAKING?
I was.
But I had a very
good reason.
We're listening.
Well, I was in my
thinking tree.
That's where I do most of
my really deep thinking.
I was there and I
said to myself I said.
Discord, your friend Twilight
says that she's your pal,
but she never writes and she
never pops in for a visit.
I don't even know
where you live.
Now that she's a Princess,
maybe she's decided that
she's too good for you.
I have never considered
myself too good--
But how was I supposed to know
for sure that I'm
truly still friends
with one of the most
important ponies around?
I'm not more--
By seeing if you would go
to the ends of Equestria
for me, of course!
Which you did. Literally.
Congratulations, Twilight,
you passed my friendship test!
Why the angry eyes?
You love passing tests.
It's not because my little exam
put a damper on your visit
with Princess Cadance, is it?
Made it so that there was
no time for you two
to focus on your friendship?
You didn't put a damper
on our visit at all.
I didn't?
He didn't?
Spending the day at the
Starswirl the Bearded exhibit
would have been more
relaxing, but to be honest,
relaxation is the
last thing I need.
It is?
Don't get me wrong.
Life in the Crystal
Empire is wonderful,
but it's become a
little... predictable.
I enjoy a little
excitement now and then.
Getting to face all
these challenges today
was just what I needed.
And facing them with you just
made me realize even more
how lucky I am to have
somepony like you as a friend.
We may not see each
other very often,
but I know you'll always
be there when I need you.
Just like she was
there for you, Discord.
Yes. She's a
real sweetheart.
We're all so lucky to
have her in our lives.
What in the world?
I think it's pretty clear that
my visit with Cadance
didn't go quite the
way I expected.
But in the end, I realized that
when you're with a good friend,
even the most chaotic day can
end up being a great experience
that brings you closer.
Wouldn't you agree, Discord?
Yes, Twilight.
I don't wanna go sayin'
you got what you deserved.
Well, I have no
trouble saying it.
You got what you
deserved!
Now, now.
He's learned his lesson.
Isn't that right,
my little patient?
I'm so glad that you're back
from your trip, Fluttershy.
Just your presence here is
making me feel so much better.
I was just wondering.
Could I trouble you for
just one more thing?
No!
What?
I was simply going to ask for
a teeny tiny glass of water.