Look at that, Tank!
Cloudsdale's here!
That means Ponyville
is next up for winter!
You're doing awesome,
everypony! Keep it up!
We need those leaves
off those trees!
Once we get autumn cleared
away, it'll be "Hello, Winter!"
Was that a yawn
I just saw?
How can you be tired when the
most exciting time of the year
is right around the corner!
And don't forget
the best part...
our first winter together!
Come on, wake up!
Once those ponies bring in
the big fat clouds
full of snowflakes, we'll
have a ton of snow
for our extreme sledding!
Ha ha ha!
Whoa!
Whoo hoo!
And over there we can
play horse hockey!
With no shoulder or rump pads!
Everything's looking
great, don't you think?
Almost everything. Does
Tank look all right to you?
Well, he does seem to be
moving a little slowly.
I know, right?
And he looks kind
of sleepy...
Totally!
just like he always does.
Yeah, heh-heh, I'm
sure you're right.
Regular Subtitles by YayPonies
We have Muffins
http://main.yayponies.eu
Well?
I suppose his heartbeat
COULD be a teensy, weensy,
eensy bit slower than usual.
OK, so give him a
vitamin or something.
I don't think he
needs that.
Maybe we're just
staying up too late.
Too many Derring-Do stories.
That's not it either.
Well, what's wrong
with him then?
Nothing. He's
perfectly fine!
He's just going
to hibernate.
You do realize he's
not a bear, right?
When the weather grows cold
and less food is available,
many animals hibernate
to conserve energy.
It's like taking a really
long nap during winter.
And then they wake
up in spring!
And see? Even
tortoises do it.
When the time comes, Tank will
leave and dig into the ground.
But don't worry, he'll
reappear when the spring sun
warms the ground back up.
Come on! Tortoises
don't hibernate.
Somepony put that picture
in there as a joke.
It's not a joke.
Well then your
book must be wrong.
Rainbow Dash, Tank
needs to hibernate.
It's healthy for him, just like
sleeping is healthy for us.
Whatever, OK, thanks.
Come on, Tank.
Where are you going?
To get a second opinion from
a REAL reptile expert.
I told you, Rainbow
Dash. I'm a DRAGON!
Come on, you're
practically twins!
I'm purple!
But if you don't have to
hibernate, why should Tank?
Because he's a TORTOISE.
And I'm a DRAGON.
Same family though, right?
No!
I'll take that as a yes.
Look, if Fluttershy says
tortoises hibernate,
then I guarantee
tortoises hiber--
Well, what would you know?
You're a dragon!
Nopony knows you like
I do, Tank.
All you need is some hard work
to get the ol' blood pumping.
Come on!
These things are heavy!
Chock full o' snowflakes.
We're gonna have such a
killer time in the snow, Tank!
Tank? TANK?
Aw, look at that
cute wittle Tanky!
All snuggly wuggly,
getting ready to hibern---
DON'T SAY THAT WORD!
Which one? Snuggly?
Wuggly? Tanky? Hiberna--
THAT ONE!
I was just saying
how cute he loo--
If you think hiber-- you know,
that napping thing--
is SOOO cute, why
don't you go do it?
Somewhere far away from here!
What are you looking at?
Pinkie Pie and I are just
having a conversation!
Look Rainbow Dash, we all
know how upset you are
about Tank hiber--
SHHHH! Don't say that word!
That's what started this all!
We know how upset
you are about Tank,
but you shouldn't take your
anger out on your friends.
WHO SAID ANYTHING ABOUT ANGER?
I DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING ABOUT ANGER!
I'M NOT UPSET!
AND I AM NOT ANGRY!
DO I LOOK ANGRY?
C'MON TANK, LET'S
GET OUTTA HERE!
I need you bright-eyed
and bushy-tailed,
not sleepy-eyed
and scaly-tailed...
...which is
exactly what you are.
But get up anyway!
You CAN'T hiber--you know!
What about all the primo things
we're gonna do
together this winter?
Building snowponies,
starting snowball fights,
sipping hot cider by the fire.
DON'T YOU WANT TO DO
THOSE THINGS WITH ME?
Think, Rainbow Dash, think!
Tank's only hibernating
because it's cold, right?
Well, I'd rather have
him awake in the heat
than asleep in the cold.
I'll just have to STOP WINTER!
So, where do
these clouds go?
Over by Clear Skies.
But there's Clear
Skies everywhere.
Yo! Clear Skies
right here!
But there's Clear
Skies over there, too.
That's Open Skies.
There's open
skies everywhere!
I'm not everywhere;
I'm right here.
Wait, so, you're Open Skies,
and you're Clear Skies...
then what's all that?
Open, Clear Skies!
Hey! Where'd our
fluffy clouds go?
Fluffy Clouds?
He's over there!
Ha! Stopping winter is
gonna be a breeze!
♪ When life gives you lemons ♪
♪ You can make lemonade ♪
♪ But life gave me Tank, here ♪
♪ And my choice has
long been made. ♪
♪ No winter will come to
Ponyville ♪
♪ I'll do it on my own ♪
♪ I will keep you by my side ♪
♪ So I will not be alone! ♪
♪ And I'll fly, and I'll fly
until the end of the sky ♪
♪ So I'll be the one who
doesn't have to say goodbye! ♪
♪ I'll clear the skies forever
So we won't be apart ♪
♪ I'll keep the
weather warm for you ♪
♪ And the winter will
never start! ♪
♪ Weather makers, Pegasi ♪
♪ You make the seasons
in the sky ♪
♪ I don't wanna sabotage you ♪
♪ But you see I've got to try! ♪
♪ No winter can come here now ♪
♪ I'll keep the warmth
and the sun somehow ♪
♪ I'm sorry ponies
this has to be ♪
♪ For I need my friend
and he needs me ♪
♪ I know it's wrong but
what does it matter? ♪
♪ Cause nothing's
gonna stop me now ♪
♪ I'll change it all
it's only the weather! ♪
♪ And nopony's gonna
bring me down! ♪
♪ I'll keep the
sunlight shining free ♪
♪ And I'll bust the
clouds apart ♪
♪ so you can stay with me! ♪
♪ And I'll fly, and I'll fly
until the end of the sky ♪
♪ So I'll be the one who
doesn't have to say goodbye! ♪
♪ I'll clear the skies forever
So we won't be apart ♪
♪ I'll keep the
weather warm for you ♪
♪ And the winter will
never start! ♪
Here comes the next shipment!
Move those clouds over!
For every hoofstep back, they
go three hoofsteps forward!
What am I gonna do?
Cloudsdale...THAT'S IT, TANK!
If I can't stop
winter in Ponyville,
maybe I can stop
it at the source!
Lunch hour! Perfect!
The winter lab!
We're in, Tank!
Now, we just gotta figure
out a way to shut it down!
Sabotage snowflakes?
I think we gotta go
bigger than that.
Wait here.
Hmm. We could get
rid of these clouds,
but that's still
not big enough.
Slam dunk! With no water, they
can't make clouds or snow!
They can't make WINTER!
I hate to do this to
those weather ponies,
but desperate times call
for desperate measures!
Oopsie! Looks like these
were a little loose!
And there goes
winter...down the drain!
Whoa! I can't see!
Oof!
Let's get outta here!
What in the name of
Celestia's goin' on up there?
Prepare yourselves, everypony...
Winter is coming.
EVERYPONY! LOOK OUT!
You OK, Tank?
Rainbow Dash! Are
you all right?
No.
Knock, knock!
How are you feeling,
Rainbow Dash?
Whatever.
The poor thing
looks so sad!
Just what are we
going to do?
I don't know
what we CAN do.
Buck up, sugarcube, you just
ain't yourself these days.
Whatever.
Oh, how can I say
this tactfully?
You've lost your
sparkle, Rainbow Dash!
I hate to say this...but well...
you've become...a party pooper!
Didn't you hear me?
I said whatever.
I don't know if you're here
to cheer me up or what,
but I'm fine.
Let me handle this.
Rainbow Dash, your winter
is going to be PETLESS!
Whatever did you
do that for?
Because she'll never get past
this until she lets it all out.
Uh, it's OK! Tank'll come
back in a few months!
MONTHS? [wailing]
I DON'T WANT HIM TO GO!
All right, all right.
There there.
Nice goin', Fluttershy.
How do we get her to stop?
She's got to be about done now.
Can't be too much left in there.
Feeling better?
Uh-huh.
Oh, you poor,
poor thing!
I can't bear to see
Fluttershy cry!
It's...just...heart-wrenching!
You, too?
Nope. I'm good.
Look, everypony, I know how
hard it is to say goodbye--
I'm mostly sad because
you're NOT sad!
What? Me? What
about Applejack?
Applejack cries on
the inside, Twilight!
It's true.
It's all right, Fluttershy.
It's all right.
You think she's done or
just gettin' a third wind?
I don't know. Rainbow
Dash? Are you OK?
I think so.
I feel better.
Really, I do.
Thanks, everypony. I don't
know what I'd do without you.
Or him...
Oh, Tank. I'm sure
gonna miss you.
Well, guess we're starting
winter with a bang.
The fun's come early! Yee-haw!
You think we could mess
up winter every year?
It's way less work!
Uh, I don't think Rainbow
Dash could handle it.
Riding that entire
season from Cloudsdale
to Ponyville WAS
pretty awesome.
I thought you guys might
like to say goodbye to Tank.
He's ready to hibernate.
You're using the word!
She's using the word!
And when Tank
finishes hibernating,
I'm going to throw him the
biggest Welcome Home party ever!
Or wait. Should it be a
"Welcome Above Ground" party?
Or a "Happy Wake-Up" party?
Maybe an "It's
about time" party?
And I'll design him a
very special suit
just for the occasion,
whichever one it
ends up being!
I'm glad you're feelin' a
little better, Rainbow Dash.
Yeah. Me too.
So, you really want to do
this hibernating thing, huh?
Goodbye Tank!
Have a good
sleep, Tank!
See you later,
little fella!
Goodbye Tank,
we'll miss you!
Well? Ready for
some winter fun?
Uh, I'm gonna hang here
and read to him a bit.
That little guy can never get to
sleep without a bedtime story.
I'll be right there.