Has anypony heard from
Pinkie Pie since yesterday?
I don't see what's
so important
we had to meet her
here this early.
Celestia hasn't even
raised the sun yet.
I hope everything's OK.
Thank goodness you're all here.
There's no time to lose.
Whoa!
Careful.
What is all this?
My sister Maud's
going to be here soon
and I need your help
taste-testing my
rock candy recipes.
Uh, we're happy to help
you, Pinkie Pie,
but this seems like an
awful lot of candy...
Even for you.
I may have gone a
teensy bit overboard.
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
Everypony ready for more?
My teeth hurt.
I think we've had plenty.
And shouldn't you be on
your way to pick up Maud
from the train station?
But you've only tried
half of the flavors
and we have to choose
the perfect ones
before she gets here
so I have time to make more.
Maud is your sister;
I'm sure she'll love
your rock candy.
And I'm pretty sure
you've made enough.
She's only staying
for the week.
It's not just
for Maud, silly.
I'm making candy
for all of us.
It's part of a very important,
super-duper special tradition
that only the closest and
bestest of friends can share.
We're going to make rock
candy necklaces together.
It all started when Maud and I
were fillies on the Rock Farm.
She taught me the Pie
family rock candy recipe.
It has a secret ingredient.
It's rocks.
And she showed me how
to string the pieces
to make them into a necklace.
And once we were
done, we'd trade.
Maud and I have been trading
necklaces back and forth
since I moved to Ponyville.
They're a sign that we'll
always be best friends.
Aw, what a great tradition.
Hold on.
The "secret
ingredient" is rocks?
Yeah.
But these are a special kind
of rock that Maud discovered.
What kind of a rock are they?
I can't tell you that, silly.
It's a secret.
Now that Maud is heading off
to get her Rocktorate
in Rock Science,
this may be our last
chance to trade them
for a really long time.
I can't wait for
you all to meet her.
I just know that my best
Ponyville friends
and my best sister friend are
going to become bestest friends.
We can make bestestest friend
rock candy necklaces together!
She expresses herself through
fashion just like Rarity.
And she's really smart and loves
reading, just like Twilight.
And she's honest and
loves forest things
and is good at games and...well?
SHE'S AWESOME!
She sounds amazing.
But won't she start worrying
if you aren't at the train
station when she gets here?
She sure will.
I gotta get out of here!
I sure hope Maud
has an appetite.
Never met a pony, or a
critter, who didn't love
Granny Smith's
apple-spice muffins.
Oh! It's no use!
I simply cannot find
anything suitable to wear.
I doubt she'll notice
what anypony's wearing.
So what's the big deal?
The big deal is that it will be
very difficult to show Maud
what a strong fashion presence
we have in Ponyville
if the most fashion-forward
pony here
can't keep her hat
from falling apart.
I think we're all a little
nervous about Maud's visit.
She's Pinkie Pie's sister
and it's obvious Pinkie really
wants us to hit it off.
Being able to make those rock
candy necklaces together
is really important to her.
I'm sure everything
will be fine.
WE'RE HERE.
Where's Maud?
She's coming.
you sure?
She's not quite
as fast as me.
I asked Gummy to stay with
her in case she got lost.
Is she even moving?
WE'RE OVER HERE, MAUD!
Hmm.
Sedimentary.
Huh?
This is a sedimentary rock.
That's really fascinating,
isn't it, girls?
We're just so thrilled you
could come for a visit
before your big trip.
Pinkie Pie has told
us so much about you.
I'm Twilight and this is
Applejack, Fluttershy,
Rainbow Dash, and Rarity.
We're ever so
glad to meet you.
We're just gonna
have the best time.
Pinkie Pie tells me you
share my love for fashion.
I'm really into expressing
myself through my wardrobe.
And what is the delightful
frock you're wearing now saying?
It doesn't talk.
It's a dress.
Oh! Yes. Of course.
I just meant...
Uh. So this here's Winona.
That's Owlowiscious...
Tank, Opal, and Angel.
Pinkie Pie told us
you have a pet, too.
He's in my pocket.
Oooh, You have a pocket pet?
Like a tiny mouse?
Or a baby bird?
Or a trained butterfly?
It's a rock.
His name is Boulder.
This is going to be the best,
most awesome, funnest week ever.
I can't wait for us all
to become bestest friends.
Maud? Would ya care to
try one of Granny Smith's
famous apple spice muffins?
Oh, uh, ha, that's not--
It's crunchy.
Maud's right. They
are crunchy!
Yum.
So, uh, Pinkie Pie
tells us you like games.
Boulder and I sometimes play a
game called "camouflage."
It's kind of like
"hide-and-seek,"
but way more intense.
Awesome.
Any luck?
I truly wish I had spent
more time with Boulder,
because I'm having a very
hard time remembering
what he looks like.
It's like lookin' for
a pebble in a haystack.
More like, "in a pile
of pebbles."
Well, you don't have to
make it even harder.
Agh! I give
up.
This is impossible.
It'll hurt Maud's feelings
if we all stop playing.
Besides, look how much
fun Pinkie Pie is having.
IS THIS IT? IS THIS IT?
Just a little longer, OK?
All right. Fine.
Found him.
Where was he?
He was hiding in my pocket.
Oh, come on!
I don't mean to interrupt,
but we really should get these
little critters home.
It's getting awfully late and
they've had a very busy day.
Maud and I'd better
get going, too.
I want her to taste
the rock candy
we're going to use for our...
...best friends necklaces.
Oh yeah!
She sure is different
from what I expected.
We spent all day
digging in the dirt
and he was in her pocket
the whole time?
On the bright side, Boulder
seemed really sweet.
He's a ROCK!
Come on, girls.
I'm sure Maud was just nervous
about meeting all of us.
Maybe she was just
acting a little "off"
because she's shy or somethin'.
Exactly.
It must be awfully intimidating
to meet all of us at once,
especially since we're
already such good friends.
Maybe if we spent some
time with her one-on-one
to try to get to
know her better?
I'm sure we'll be making those
best-friend rock candy necklaces
in no time.
Where shall we start?
I've chosen a few fabrics
I think would be stunning with--
Choices, choices, choices.
Of course, if you don't see
anything that speaks to you,
I would be happy to suggest--
I like this one.
Pinkie Pie didn't tell
us you were so funny.
What do you mean?
Oh, well, it's just, I
believe that is a dish towel.
But, it does go very
well with your complexion.
I'm sure I could
work my magic
and turn it into
something fabulous.
Rarity and my sister
working together
to design something amazing.
This is the best day ever!
Perhaps I could sew
all of these together
and make you something
you would like.
No, thanks.
One is enough.
Doesn't Maud make
the coolest scarves?
Quite.
Hello there, Hummingway.
I'm ever so happy to see you.
What's he saying?
He says hello, and he's
happy to see us too.
I wish I could
speak hummingbird.
Hummmmm, hum, hum,
hum, hummmmmm.
These spiders only
live in Ponyville,
and even though they may
look a teeny bit scary,
they're actually
very sweet
and help keep other, more
dangerous insects away.
I was looking at
the rock.
Oh.
Thanks again, Fluttershy.
Start thinking about which
flavors you want to put
in your best-friend
rock candy necklace.
Oh, gosh.
I'm not sure we're
even friends yet.
Maud is a total bookworm.
She loves poetry.
I've got lots of poetry.
Do you read anything
by Quill and Ink?
Or Flourish Prose?
I prefer to read my own poetry.
I'd love to hear some of it.
Rock. You are a rock.
Grey...
you are grey...
like a rock...
which you are.
Rock.
I've written thousands.
She's so prolific!
This next one is about rocks.
They're all about rocks.
Rocks, these are my rocks.
Sediments.
Make me sentimental.
Smooth and round.
Asleep in the ground.
Shades of brown. And grey.
You 'bout done peeling them
apples for the cider, Maud?
I think this one is done.
Oh, uh, yep.
That's a very interestin'
method you've got there.
Should I peel another?
NO! I mean, naw...
I'm sure there's plenty
apples in it already.
Can we taste it now?
Sure, why not?
WOW!
That's the best apple
cider I've ever had!
What do you think, Maud?
It tastes like apples.
Told you she was
super honest.
Just like you.
We're practically twins. Heh.
Yeah!
Let's see you beat that.
THAT WAS AMAZING!
Whoa! How'd you do that?
I threw it.
I guess you won
this one, Maud.
I'm not really into "winning".
Great! You're all here.
Maud is off looking for rocks,
so this is the perfect time
for us to set up
everything we'll need
to make our best-friend
rock candy necklaces.
What's wrong?
Well? I'm not sure it's the
best time to make best-friend
rock candy necklaces.
Why not?
Uh...
Well, darling, you see...
You're ever so
thoughtful to share
your special bonding
ritual with us, but...
But what?
The truth is, we've all
been trying real hard
to get closer to
Maud, but, well,
maybe some
ponies just don't click
the way others do.
We just wouldn't feel
right making something
that means we're best
friends if, well, we aren't.
Oh. OK.
If anypony needs me I'll be in
here trying to figure out
what to do with 200
pounds of rock candy.
I feel awful,
just awful.
Maybe we should have
just pretended
we were friends with Maud.
If we didn't tell Pinkie Pie
that we hadn't all become
the best of friends,
I think Maud would have.
Maybe. But who really knows?
That pony is a riddle wrapped
in a mystery inside an igneous.
Don't you mean
"inside an enigma"?
Nope. I mean igneous.
It's a kind of rock.
Ask me how I know that.
I've come up with
just the thing
to bring everypony
closer together.
I call it Pinkie-Rainbow-Rari-
Twi-Apple-Flutter-Maud
Fun Time!
Huh?
It combines
everypony's interests
into one giant activity
that we can all enjoy together
and that will totally bring all
my bestest friends together
as bestestest friends.
You'll need these.
Like I said, "Huh?"
Probably better
for me to show you.
Watch this!
Applesauce tunnel for Applejack.
Pretty, shiny stuff for Rarity.
Reading material for Twilight.
Critter time for Fluttershy.
Cupcakes for yours truly.
And it's a race
for Rainbow Dash.
Pinkie Pie, what is that?
A rock slide, of course.
For Maud.
First you climb, then you slide.
I've got a bad
feelin' about this.
Huh?
OH!
Oh, goodness.
Watch out!
Huh?
Ahhhh! Help!
What? How? What?
Pinkie Pie, what
were you thinking?
I guess I wasn't.
I know how important it is
to you that your friends
become my friends.
But I just don't think
it's going to happen.
I think it would be best if I
just go back to the Rock Farm
and spend the rest of
the week there.
It was nice to meet you all.
Makes me happy knowing Pinkie
Pie has such good friends.
But we never even got to make
our rock candy necklaces.
Wait, Maud. I'll come with you.
I can't believe Maud
cut her trip short.
I can't believe we
nearly lost Pinkie Pie
to that ridiculous
obstacle course.
Thank goodness Maud was
able to reach her in time.
Did you see how
fast Maud moved?
And the way she smashed
that huge rock into dust?
How in Equestria
did she do that?
Pinkie Pie was in trouble.
Maud would move mountains
for her if she had to.
That's it! I think
I've finally realized
what we all have in
common with Maud.
Something that just might be
worthy of a very important,
super-duper special tradition
that only the closest and
bestest of friends can share.
Thank you for
coming with me.
I don't know how long I'll be
gone on my rock research trip.
I'm glad I still get to spend
some time with you before I go.
Me, too.
I'm sorry I put so much
pressure on everypony to bond.
I only wanted my friends to get
to know my amazing older sister.
What are you doing here?
Pinkie Pie, we're so sorry
we hurt your feelings
by not bonding with
Maud right away.
And Maud, we're sorry that
you felt the only way to spare
Pinkie Pie's feelings was
to leave Ponyville early.
We've seen how much you care
about Pinkie Pie, first-hoof.
Pinkie Pie's happiness means as
much to us as it does to you,
and we're sorry we
couldn't see it sooner.
The thing that makes us click
and creates a special bond
between us is how much
we ALL love Pinkie Pie!
Aw, shucks.
That's a pretty great thing to
have in common if you ask me.
What do you think, Maud?
Sure.
What's wrong?
Sorry, darling, I think
we all just thought
she'd be a bit more
excited about this.
Are you kidding me?
I've never seen her more
excited in my entire life.
I don't know if you've noticed
but I don't show my enthusiasm
for things quite in the
same way my sister does.
Uh, we noticed.
And we're totally cool with it.
Maud, we'd like to give you
something to take on your trip,
so that you remember all
your friends from Ponyville.
Thank you.
Try not to eat all the
candy before you leave.
Are those all the
necklaces Pinkie Pie sent you?
Mm hm.
You haven't eaten any of them?
I don't really like candy.
But I do love Pinkie Pie.
Mmmmm!