Hey there, my
unicorn friend.
Have you heard?
About Princess Twilight
Sparkle's coronation?
Who hasn't!
I'm on my way there now. So
much baking to do and...
No, no, about the
Earth ponies.
I know their crops have
been underperforming, but...
That's not it.
They're HOARDING the
food for themselves!
I heard the Mayor
of Appleoosa say
that if unicorns and
pegasi want to eat,
they can use their
OWN hooves to dig.
How awful!
We unicorns have to
stick together, right?
Ah, Chrysalis.
Another successful
field trip, I presume?
Spreading distrust among the
unicorns and earth ponies
is almost TOO easy.
We could take down
Twilight and her friends
a hundred times,
but as long as
they have the "love" of
Equestria behind them,
they'd crawl back to
defeat us. Not anymore!
No friendship,
no magic!
It's SO obvious when
you think about it.
I did my part freaking
out the pegasi!
And Grogar's long absence
has given ME time to prepare
the next part
of our plan.
Grogar's Bell!
This artifact can steal
ANY creature's magic.
It holds that magic until
it is released by THIS spell.
Which means.. all the power
inside is OURS for the taking!
You're drooling
on the bell.
Let's try the spell
before Grogar gets back.
I'm sick of waiting for that
old goat's "master plan."
Take my hands.
So we can all be
part of the spell!
Unless you'd prefer I
take all the magic myself?
Our pact stands. What
we do, we do together.
Once we defeat the
protectors of Equestria,
we can claim this land and rule
our kingdoms, ALONE once more.
♪♪
Grogar: I have returned!
Twilight Sparkle's
coronation is today.
And we are going to ruin
it with THIS artifact!
But to succeed, you
must work together.
Chrysalis: Oh, way
ahead of you, Grogar.
♪♪
The Bell! You had it all this
time!? Why didn't you tell me?
We're VILLIANS, duh.
♪ [comedic music] ♪
That was unexpected.
Wait. Discord
was Grogar!?
Like the whole time?
Should we follow him..?
Without magic, he's no threat.
Besides, WE have plans.
♪ [happy music] ♪
Celestia: Doesn't she look so
adorably regal up there?
Our little Twilight,
all grown up.
Should we tell her that we've
cleared out our royal suites
so she and Spike can move in?
Oh, maybe wait until
AFTER the coronation.
Twilight doesn't
need anything else
to worry about today.
So, you freakin'
out yet?
About what?
Oh, I don't know. It's not
every day the princesses
that have ruled Equestria
for hundreds of moons
retire and pass all their
responsibilities on to you
and your friends..
Oh, THAT. Actually, I'm
feeling pretty good!
We've all faced so
much, and come out OK.
I know we're up
to the challenge
of keeping Equestria
safe and happy.
There's nothing we
can't handle together.
Which reminds me...
Royal advisor?
What's that?
A new position I
created for you.
You've been
at my side
for every step
of this journey.
Knowing I had
you to count on
gave me the
strength I needed
to grow and succeed.
I wouldn't be
here without you.
Thanks, Twilight.
You know I'll always be
your right-hoof dragon.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Because now that my
crown's been fitted,
we have some royal
errands to run!
♪♪
And you're sure this is
where Pinkie told us to get
the blackberries for her
special coronation dessert?
Maybe they keep their
produce in the back?
Nope! This is
all we got.
But I got a special
on these taters!
Um, no thank you.
We'll keep looking.
Blech!
Ooh, Twilight, darling!
You're just in time.
Only one more
pre-coronation stop!
We're picking up
the final touch
for your apres-hors
d'oevres gown.
Is that before or
after the royal
marshmallow-eating
contest gown?
What? I hadn't
made one of those!
You must tell me when they
add these sorts of things...!
It's OK, Rarity.
I was just joking.
Joking? Day of
your coronation?
You've come a long
way, Twilight.
♪♪
Well, that's odd.
They LOOK open...
What do you want?
Oh! Well, this
being a thread shop,
I thought I
might buy some..?
Put the bits in
the mail slot.
What was
THAT about?
You know designers. Don't
like being interrupted
when they're on a
creative roll!
With thread this exquisite,
can you blame them?
Rainbow Dash: Weather for the
coronation is sunny skies!
It was weird, though.
Not many pegasi wanted to
help me clear the clouds.
They were kinda
on edge.
They're not the only ones..
It's the first shift in royal
power in over a millennium!
Of course, everypony
is a little jumpy.
Change does that.
But I'm sure it's not because
they're worried about YOU.
How could they be?
HOW many times have you
saved their flanks by now?
You're right. I'll just
have to let everypony know
that even with
Celestia and Luna gone,
we'll make sure
things stay the same.
Twilight! There you are!
You mind tellin' your friend
here that I don't need
an official guard
wherever I go?
Especially if he ain't
gonna help carry apples?
I appreciate you taking such
good care of my friends,
but we're fine now.
It was the strangest thing. He
kept callin' me "Earth pony,"
like I didn't have a name!
And watchin' me like he
thought I'd steal the silver!
Do NOT go in that kitchen!
You look like you
were in a sugar war.
For some reason,
the bakers are SUPER
grouchy with each other.
That unicorn chef started
throwing dessert at Mrs. Cake!
I tried to help, but I got
caught in the crossfire!
Tasty, tasty crossfire...
You sure this is just
pre-coronation nerves?
Discord: Oh, my
aching metatarsals!
Y'know, you forget how
convenient snap-travel is.
Wait. Did you just
WALK here? On foot?
Yes, actually. And I have
a confession to make.
You see, I might have
made the teeniest boo boo.
All very well-intentioned
and noble on my part, of course...
Get to the
point, Discord.
You remember that whole
thing with King Sombra?
That was slightly my fault.
And by slightly, I mean...
I brought him back.
You DID!? But why!?
It seemed like a good
idea at the time!
Which is why I also brought
back three other villains
who are now on the loose...
..And not really big
fans of yours.
So... my bad.
Luna: Let me get
this straight.
You wanted to boost
Twilight's confidence,
so you brought back Chrysalis,
Cozy Glow, and Tirek
to attack her?
Don't forget Sombra!
And while you united
these three villains,
YOU pretended to be Grogar?
Discord! How could you do
this to Twilight!? And us!?
Look what a great job
you did defeating Sombra!
All the confidence
you gained!
Remember the cheering?
The hoof bumps?
Except it was
all a lie.
A well-intentioned lie!
For all the time
you've spent with us,
you really haven't picked
up too much in the way of
friendship lessons, huh?
You've been setting
up challenges for us
the whole time,
haven't you?
None of our successes
were actually real!
Of course,
they were!
You just had an extremely
good-looking safety net.
Spike: And how was that
supposed to HELP again?
I intended to prepare
Twilight for anything
by orchestrating an epic
attack at her coronation.
You beastly beast!
Don't you know how much
this day means to Twilight!?
AND ME! I made her dress!
Why wait until now for
such a horrible plan?
You don't take a final exam
on your first day of class!
Just think, after
defeating THREE baddies,
Twilight would
HAVE to believe
that she's the leader
we all know she is!
You have made a grave
misjudgment, Discord..
Do you have anything ELSE
you would like to tell us?
Would you like the good
news or the bad news?
THAT wasn't the bad news!?
All my chaos magic is... gone.
Trapped in Grogar's bell.
[sigh] So what's the good news?
Chrysalis, Tirek, and
Cozy Glow now have
all of the real
Grogar's magic.
In what WORLD is
that GOOD NEWS!?
Compared to me
losing my powers,
anything else
IS good news.
Twilight, Luna, we
need to make a plan.
Maybe it's not too late to stop
this DISASTER from happening.
I... I need some
time to think first.
Well, there isn't any time!
Look what I overheard
them saying!
Oh! Just listen to my voice
and use your imagination.
Let the fool go. Without
magic, he's no threat.
Besides, we have plans.
The lame six are so
busy being perfect,
they haven't even noticed
what we've been up to!
Have I mentioned how
great revenge is?
I hope you got a name picked
out for your future kingdom.
Because it's time to
destroy Equestria!
They're probably on their way
to attack Canterlot.. right now!
Then we'll stop 'em!
HOW? Stopping Sombra by
himself was hard enough!
And that was with lord-of-
chaos training wheels!
Twilight, it doesn't
matter if Discord set up
your successes or not.
WE believe in you..
and always have.
Lean on your strengths to
counter your weaknesses.
My strengths?
Right. Spike!
Send a letter to Starswirl.
Tell him we need the Pillars to
guard the border of Canterlot.
If the villains are
coming for a fight,
we'll have one
waiting for them.
With Chrysalis on the loose,
she'll go after Starlight.
Warn Cadance and
Shining Armor.
They're our final line
of defense if we fail.
The ultimate battle for the
fate of Equestria...
is coming!
We're not going anywhere
until you two STOP ARGUING!
Chrysalis, say something
nice about Tirek.
GAH! He's...red.
Tirek...?
She's...not as
annoying as I expected.
Good! Now we were talking
about Grogar's Bell.
We should take the
magic inside it!
You know how
powerful Discord was.
That much chaos
magic in OUR veins...
But taking it ALL
would be madness!
It's impossible for any
other creature to control!
I guess if you need a
guinea pig to find out
if anypony can use chaos
magic... I'll volunteer!
FOOLS! Now I have more
power than ALL OF YOU!
Kneel before my might!
Ahh! Take it back! TAKE IT BACK!
Still think chaos
magic is a good idea?
Leave it in the bell. We've
got a kingdom to conquer.
So, where should
we strike first?
[chuckle] Everywhere.
♪♪
We've faced enemies
of Equestria before.
And we've ALWAYS succeeded.
That wouldn't be possible
without all of you.
You're welcome!
Dude. Read the room.
So I ask for your
help again today,
in what is our
biggest battle yet.
ALL of Equestria is at stake,
and I can't do this alone.
But I'm not afraid. Because
with friendship as our armor,
and teamwork as our power,
nopony can ever bring us down!
Oh, COME ON.
Where'd you get that, a daily
affirmations calendar? Yeesh.
Cozy Glow!? You're...
...about to wipe
the floor with you!
Wow, it's true! Alicorns
really DO have more fun!
Starswirl: Spread out
and stay ready, friends.
Canterlot depends on us!
♪♪
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Ha ha ha ha!
♪♪
Magic seasoned with
age. Delicious!
No!
♪♪
Oh, run along! The big
stallions are playing!
Oh! Somnambula! Warn...
the princesses....
♪♪
Ah! The perfect dessert
to a LEGENDARY meal.
♪♪
Stay with your
buddy; no running.
Just follow
Counselor Trixie.
Chrysalis: Starlight, starbright,
where's the pony
I want to FIGHT?
I have to go. You got this?
Nopony does a great and
powerful escape like Trixie.
Ah. Just the headmare
I want to see.
YOU didn't make
an appointment.
What is this place!?
Somewhere you
can't hurt anypony.
Wrong. I can hurt YOU!
Agh! Stay still so I can blast you!
Oh, yeah, real
motivating.
♪♪
You'll pay for that!
Put it on my tab.
♪♪
Now I'll have all eternity
to take my revenge on YOU!
Stand down, Cozy Glow.
Gee, I guess I could. But...
I'm having too much FUN!
Ready, sister?
Wait! What are you..?
NO!
That's the problem
with you magic-types.
You're so reliant on
all your special power,
you forget to use
your BRAINS!
Keep telling yourself
that. NOW!
WHOA!
♪♪
SURPRISE ATTACK!
Fly my pretties!
♪♪
Wah! Agh!
You think your pathetic
shield can stop us?
[cackle] The Pillars have
been defeated.
Your school is abandoned. Face
it, Twilight. You've lost.
You can attack us
and we may fall.
But Equestria will still
stand, united in friendship!
And we won't stop
until we defeat you,
no matter how many
ponies you take down!
Didn't you all notice
something was wrong
in Equestria?
We've been busy.
A whisper here,
a rumor there.
Destroy some crops.
Cause some damage.
Turn pony against pony.
Until your whole
kingdom is on edge,
waiting for just
one tiny thing
to push them
over the brink!
There's no backup friends or
rainbow magic to save you now!
Golly, I think it's time
for some REDECORATING!
You know what's stronger than
friendship, Twilight? FEAR!
Because when you have
to protect yourself,
you don't have time
for anypony else!
Too bad you never
taught THAT in school.
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Huh?
Ugh!
♪♪
Go, Twilight. Get help!
We'll hold 'em
till you get back.
NO! I can't
leave you here!
It's our only chance!
You'll come up with
SOMETHING to save the day!
You always do!
We believe in you!
Fly, you foal!
♪ [intense music] ♪
♪♪