Perfect.
Just take the broken limbs down, Rarity.
Don't you all care about nothin'
other than prettifyin'?
Somepony has to.
You are making an absolute mess
of the town square, Applejack.
Yeah, well, the storm's gonna
make an even bigger mess...
...if we don't prune all these loose branches
so they don't tumble down on anypony.
I simply cannot imagine why the pegasus ponies
would schedule a dreadful downpour this evening...
...and ruin what could have been
a glorious sunny day.
Think more practical-like, will ya?
They accidentally skipped
a scheduled sprinkle last week, so...
...we need a doozy of a downpour
to make up for it, is all.
Oh no! My wonderfully styled
mane shall be ruined!
You shoulda hurried up and
finished the job, already.
It's coming down too fast!
Help me!
There. Hunker down to your heart's content
whilst I finish this.
Ooh, no no nooo!
What now?
I'd prefer not to get my hooves muddy.
Gah. There is just no pleasin' ya, is there?
Everything's gotta be just so.
Well, and how does muddying my hooves
serve any useful purpose?
You wouldn't know useful
if it came up and bit you.
That doesn't even make any sense.
-Does so.
-Does not.
Does so infinity. Hah!
Does not infinity plus one. Heh.
What's say we go our separate ways before
one of us says something she will regret?
I reckon y'all are gonna say
something you'll regret first.
On the contrary. I believe it shall almost certainly
be you who says something you will regret first.
-I'm not sayin' anythin'.
-Nor am I.
-You'll just be on your way then?
-After you.
Perhaps we should stick together
for now and find some shelter.
Uh-huh. Perhaps we should.
And fast.
Nice and dry under here.
Sorta.
Ooh! Unacceptable.
Applejack! Rarity!
Twilight?
Come inside, girls, quick.
Whoa, Nelly.
Is inside a tree really the best place
to be in a lightnin' storm?
It is if you have a magical lightning rod
protecting your home like I do.
Come on in.
We are most grateful for your invitation.
Thank ya kindly for your hospitality.
Uh...
Do be a polite houseguest and
go wash up, please, von't you?
If I gotta spend one more second
with that fussbudget Rarity today...
...I can't be held responsible
for what I'm gonna do.
Some storm, huh?
The pegasus ponies sure have
outdone themselves this time.
I hope you and Applejack
don't have any trouble getting home.
It may indeed be a problem.
Well, you're welcome to stay if need be.
Spike is away in Canterlot on royal business.
I'm home all alone tonight.
You and Applejack should totally sleep over!
We'll have a slumber party.
I've always wanted one of those.
Oh! Oh, goodness.
Uh... I do believe I have another
engagement scheduled for this evening...
...that completely slipped my
mind until just now, hahahah.
Oh, silly me. I can't possibly stay here all night...
...with Applejack.
"Slumber 101: All You've Ever Wanted to Know
About Slumber Parties (But Were Afraid to Ask)"
My own personal copy.
It's a fantastic reference guide.
You should see the table of contents.
I've been waiting for a chance to use it
and today is the day.
This is gonna be so great!
Yes, uh... Great.
What in tarnation?!
Now wait just a goll-darn minute.
You made me wash the mud off my hooves...
...but it's okay for y'all
to have mud all over your faces?
Silly. This is called a mud mask.
It's to refresh and rejuvenate your complexion.
We're giving each other makeovers!
We have to do it. It says so in the book.
"Slumber 101: Everything You..."
Oh, hay. Would you look at the time.
I gotta skedaddle on home quick,
I'm powerful late for, uh...
...somethin'.
Uh, g'night!
Or maybe I'll sit here for a spell.
Hurray! Slumber party!
What in the world is this for?
To reduce the puffiness
around one's eyes, of course.
Puffiness-shmuffiness.
That's good eatin'.
Isn't this exciting?
We'll do everything by the book.
And that will make my
slumber party officially fun.
Did you hear that, Applejack?
You certainly would not want to do anything that
would ruin Twilight's very first slumber party...
...would you?
Of course not.
'n you wouldn't either, I reckon?
So do we have an agreement?
You betcha.
Oh! Gross!
You know, there's messy
and there's just plain rude.
You know, there's fussy and there's
just plain gettin' on my nerves.
Fortunately, I can get along with anypony,
no matter how difficult she may be.
Oh yeah?
Well, I'm the get-alonginest pony you're ever gonna meet.
That's not even a word.
This is gonna be the bestest slumber party ever! Yay!
Yay.
Sooo...
How are you "getting along" over there, Applejack?
Just fine, Rarity
This is so awesome.
Makeovers: check.
Ooh! It says here we have to
tell ghost stories. Who wants to go first?
Me!
I'd like to tell y'all a terrifying tale
of the prissy ghost...
...who drove everypony crazy
with unnecessary neatness.
I'm sure y'all are familiar with that one.
Never heard of it. But I have a much better one.
It's the horrifying story
of the messy, inconsiderate ghost...
...who irritated everypony
within the hundred miles.
That's not a real story. You made it up.
It is a ghost story. They're all made up.
I've got one!
This story is called
"The legend of the Headless Horse".
It was a dark and stormy night...
...just like this one. And three ponies
were having a slumber party.
Just. Like. This one.
...and just when the last pony
thought she was safe...
...there, standing right behind her.
Just inches away was...
The Headless Horse!
Ghost story: check.
Now, who wants s'mores?
...then you place one marshmallow
on the top of the chocolate...
...and be sure it's centered - that's critical...
...and then carefully put another
perfectly square graham cracker on the top.
Aaand... done! Ta-da!
Nah, you just eat 'em.
You could at least say "excuse me".
Oh, I was just about to
but you interrupted me.
Pardon.
S'mores: check.
Now, the next item of fun we have to do is...
...Truth of Dare.
I dare Applejack to do something
carefully and neatly for a change.
Oh yeah? Well, I dare Rarity to lighten up...
...and stop obsessin' over every
last little detail for a change.
I think the truth of the matter...
...is that somepony could stand
to pay a little more attention to detail.
And I think the truth is somepony
ought to quit with their fussin'...
...so the rest of us can get things done.
Um... I don't think this is
how the game's supposed to work.
"You have to give an honest answer to any question
or do whatever anypony dares you to do."
I dares you to step outside...
...and let your precious
tidy mane get ruined again.
You have to. It's the rule.
HA!
Fine!
Okay. I dare Applejack to play dress up...
..in a frou-frou glittery lacey outfit.
Happy?
Very.
Um... do I ever get a turn?
I dare you to enter the next rodeo
when it comes to town.
I dare you *not* to enter the next rodeo
that comes to town.
I dare ya to not comb your mane
a hundred times for a bit!
And I dare you to comb yours just once!
I, uh... I think we should check off
Truth of Dare and move on.
Let's see what our next
fun-fun-fun thing is, shall we?
Hm... What does this mean?
Pillow fight?
Oh, please. I am not at all interested
in participating in something so crude.
IT... IS... ON!
Oh, I get it!
Pillow-fight.
Fun!
Uh... girls? Maybe we should take it down a notch.
I will if she will!
She started it!
Maybe we should just call it
a night and get some sleep.
Keep your muddy hooves on your side of the bed.
My hooves ain't muddy.
They were. There might still be a little on them.
There ain't. See?
Now who's bein' inconciderate?
I have to make the bed again
so the blanket will be right.
Get up!
Hey!
Uh-uh-uh.
You'll ruin it. You have to do it like this.
Yeah... that's not gonna happen.
GERONIMO!
Hey!
You did that on purpose.
Um.. yeah.
Get up so I can fix it again!
Can't hear ya, I'm asleep.
I ain't budgin'.
[You will if you want any blanket.]
[Give it back!]
[I will not!]
[Yes, you will!]
-[Won't!]
-[Will!]
ENOUGH!
It says right here that the number one thing...
...you're supposed to do at a
slumber party is have fun!
And thanks to you two I can't check that off.
I've been tryin' my darnest to get along!
No, it is I who have been trying *my* best.
-No, it was me!
-No, it was I!
-Me!
-I!
*I* hope you're happy. Both of you.
You've ruined my very first slumber party.
The makeover, the s'mores,
Truth of Dare, the pillow fight...
I mean, is there anything else
that could possible go wrong?
Sorry I asked.
You see? That's why we needed
to take down all those loose branches in town.
Not spiffy 'em up.
But I...
Out of my way, missy. Time's a-wastin'.
Wait! Stop! Don't!
No waitin'! No stopin'! Doin'!
And that, my friends, is what
we call gettin' 'er done.
I tried to tell you it would
come crashing down in here.
Well, you shoulda tried harder.
I'm mighty sorry, Twilight.
It's... well, it no okay!
It's a giant tree branch
in the middle of my bedroom!
And the book doesn't say anything about having
a giant tree branch in your slumber party.
Or at least I haven't found that entry yet.
What in tarnation are y'all doin' over there?
Cleaning up this mess somepony made.
Who was that again? Oh, right. That's you.
We gotta do somethin'!
Baking... BFFs... Brothers...
There's nothing in here about branches!
Rarity, for pony's sake!
Stop sweatin' small stuff
and help me get rid of this thing!
I said hussle over here and help me!
Look...
I'm sorry, alright?
What was that?
I said I'm sorry!
I shoulda listen to you when you noticed
where this here branch would end up.
You annoin' attention to detail
woulda save us from this whole mess.
But right now, you need to stop being so dang
fussy, pickin' up all those little things...
...and help me move the one big thing in here
that actually matters.
Please!
But I'll get all icky!
Consarnit...!
What a... You... I mean... Yes.
Ickiness is often a side effect of hard work.
But y'all need to get over it on account of
I just can't fix this mess I made myself.
I need your help.
Let's do this!
Well, they do have a section
about backyard slumber parties.
Is that what we're doing right now?
Does this count as camping?
I look awful.
Better?
Thanks.
Oh, pretty. Where did these come from?
They're not in the book either.
Is it bigger than a barn?
Nope.
Is it smaller than a saddle?
No. Only three of your twenty questions left.
Oh, we're never gonna guess
what you're thinkin' of. It could be anythin'.
Are we getting warmer?
Why? Is it too cold in here for you?
I can turn up the heat.
She means are we gettin'
any closer with our guesses.
Oh...! No.
And that technically counted as a question,
so only two more left.
Is it...
...a sixed-legged pony with a purple polka-dotted
mane and shootin' stars comin' out of his eyes?
Who flies through the air all over
the world to hide magic sparkly eggs?
That's it!
It is?
No.
It's that.
But it was just so nice to see
you two finally getting along...
...I wanted you to be able to win together.
See? We could have been
having fun like this all along.
If only somepony hadn't been so persnickety.
Well, maybe she wouldn't have been
if somepony else hadn't been so sloppy.
Sorry for bein' just a pain in the patootie.
Oh no, I'm sure I was much worse.
That's kind of you to say,
but I'm the one who's sorry.
Oh, I'm much more sorry than you are.
-Are not.
-Are too.
I declare my first slumber party a success!
Have fun: check.
Now take two steps your left.
Uh, no. My left.
Whi... Which is it?
That mess is your fault, not mine.
Sorry.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"It's hard to believe that two ponies who seem
to have so little in common could ever get along."
"But I found out that if you embrace
each others differences..."
"...you just might be surpriced to
discover a way to be friends after all."
So...
Who's up for another slumber party tomorrow night?
How about a week from Thursday?
Oh, how about two weeks from Saturday?
A month from now?
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000