I... can't... believe... the Grand...
Galloping... Gala... is... tonight!
Pinkie! Please stop shouting.
I'm trying to concentrate.
Pinkie Pie! Stop that right now.
It's time to prepare for the Gala and I refuse to
let you put on your new dress when you're all sweaty.
What's Twilight doing?
She's got an awesome magic spell
she's been working on for the Gala.
Where are the others? It's getting late.
Hold your horses, girl. We're here.
Perfect! I'm ready.
For what?
All right, Spike.
An apple!
Are we having pie?
Shh! Watch!
Thanks. But that's just the start.
Fluttershy, did you bring your friends?
Yes.
Will they be safe, Twilight?
You have my word.
Ta-da!
Neat, huh? And don't worry.
They'll be mice again at midnight.
Opalescence, no!
Wait! Come back!
Those horses were supposed to
pull our carriage. How will we get to the Gala?
What ever shall we do?
Uh... ahem. Excuse me.
Uh, would you boys mind
pulling our carriage to the Gala?
Oh. Yeah.
Right.
Come on, you guys.
Let me in!
Sure thing, Spike.
Heavens no! We're getting dressed.
Dressed? Uh, beg pardon, Rarity, but, uh...
we don't normally wear clothes.
I'm sorry, Spike. Some of us do have standards.
I still can't believe we're gonna be at Canterlot tonight.
Our home town, Twilight!
And he best part is that we all get to
hang out together all night long!
Uh... I-I don't know, Spike.
We'll just have to see.
We're gonna be a mite busy.
Busy having fun!
Oh. Okay.
Don't worry, Spike. We'll all get to
spend some time together.
Great!
Cause I planned out my
insider's tour of Canterlot.
I've gotta show Rarity the crown jewels.
And Applejack the Princess's golden apple tree.
And Pinkie, we gotta go to my favorite donut shop.
Then let's get moving! Hyah!
Excuse me!?
Um... I...
If you weren't friends with our neighbor Rarity...
Wow!
You all look...
...amazing!
I can't believe we're finally here!
With all that we've imagined, the reality
of this night is sure to make this...
...the best night ever!
At the Gala!
(At the Gala!)
At the Gala
In the garden
I'm going to see them all
All the creatures
I'll befriend them at the Gala
At the Gala!
All the birdies
And the critters
They will love me, big and small
We'll become good friends forever
Right here at the Gala
All our dreams will come true
Right here at the Gala! At the Gala!
At the Gala (It's amazing!)
I will sell them (Better hurry!)
All my appletastic treats (Yummy, yummy!)
Hungry ponies (They'll be snacking!)
They will buy them (Bringing money!)
Caramel apples, apple sweets (Give me some!)
And I'll earn a lot of money
For the Apple family
All our dreams and our hopes
From now until hereafter
All that we've been wishing for
Will happen at the Gala! At the Gala!
At the Gala
All the royals
They will meet fair Rarity
They will see I'm just as regal at the Gala
At the Gala!
I will find him
My Prince Charming
And how gallant he will be
He will treat me like a lady
Tonight at the Gala
This is what we've waited for
To have the best night ever
Each of us will live our dreams
Tonight at the Gala! At the Gala!
I've been dreaming
I've been waiting
To fly with those great ponies
The Wonderbolts
Their daring tricks
Spinning round and having kicks
Perform for crowds of thousands
They'll shower us with diamonds
The Wonderbolts will see me
Right here at the Gala
All we've come for, all we've dreamed
Our "happy ever after"
Finally they'll all come true
Right here at the Grand Gala! At the Gala!
I am here at the Grand Gala
For it is the best party
But the one thing it was missing
Was a pony named Pinkie
For I am the best at parties
All the ponies will agree
Ponies playing, ponies dancing
With me at the Grand Gala
Happiness and laughter at the Gala! At the Gala!
At the Gala (At the Gala!)
With the Princess (With the Princess!)
Is where I'm going to be (She will be!)
We will talk all about magic
And what I've learned and seen (She will see!)
It is going to be so special
As she takes time just for me
This will be the best night ever!
Into the Gala we must go
We're ready, now we're all aglow
Into the Gala let's go in
And have the best night ever
Into the Gala, now's the time
We're ready and we look divine
Into the Gala
Meet new friends
Sell some apples
Into the Gala
Find my prince
Prove I'm great
As the Wonderbolt is
To meet, to sell, to find, to prove, to whoop, to talk
Into the Gala!
And we'll have the best night ever!
At the Gala!
Yeah! This is gonna be the best night ever.
You know why? Cause we're all gonna
spend time at the Gala to...
...gether.
Or not.
Princess Celestia!
Twilight! It is so lovely to see my star student.
Oh, I'm so excited to be here!
We have so much to catch up on.
Well, I want you right by
my side the entire evening...
...so we'll have plenty of time together.
That's just what I was hoping you'd say.
Hurry, Rarity...
Oh, but not too fast.
But don't wanna lose him...
WAIT!
Have to play it cool.
Oh, but don't be cold!
I can't lose him, I can't!
He's everything I imagined!
Even better than I imagined.
Oh my! A meadowlark!
I think she's calling to me.
It's exactly what I wished for!
Howdy, partner! You hungry?
As a horse!
Well, what's you're hungering for?
Caramel apple? Apple pie?
Apple fritter? Apple fries?
I'll take that big apple pie!
Well, thank you kindly, sir!
Yeehaw! In the first minute.
I made my first sale. Just like I expected.
Always hungry after a show. Eh, Soarin'?
Yeah!
Mmmyyy pppiiieee!
You saved it! Thanks.
Hey, no prob.
Hey! I know you.
You're the pony that saved us in Cloudsdale
and won The Best Flyer Competition.
Hay yeah! Name's Rainbow Dash.
Well, Rainbow Dash.
Looks like your skills saved us again.
Oh, at least they saved Soarin's apple pie.
Yeah...
Wanna come hang out with us?
Sure. Why not?
I'm... hanging... with the... Wonderbolts!
The shiny dance floor...
The pretty party ponies...
The fancy band...
Shiny! Pretty! Fancy!
GOTTA DANCE!
I'm at the Grand Galloping Gala
I'm at the Grand Galloping Gaalaaa!
It's all I ever dreamed
It's all I ever dreamed! Woohoo!
It's all I ever dreamed! Yippee!
I'm at the Grand Galloping GalaaaAAAA!
It's all I've ever... dreamed?
Well, hello.
I am Prince Blueblood.
I am... Rarity.
Oh my, what a lovely rose.
You mean...
...this rose?
Thank you. It goes with my eyes.
My little meadowlark is right around this bend!
Was that you?
Yep! I love whistlin' while I work.
Oh! Yes... Well... Excuse me.
Oh!
I see a toco toucan! And a spider monkey!
And, oh! Is that a wallaroo?
Oh, Fluttershy. You're such a loudmouth.
Hey, Spitfire!
You ever done a rain cloud double backflip?
You ever soared past lighting? It's awesome!
Welcome to the Grand Galloping Gala.
Princess! I've been so excited
to spend time with you and...
Yes. Me too, Twi... Oh, good evening!
Welcome to the Gala.
...which is why I...
Ladies! Lovely to see you again.
Looks like getting a chance to talk to
the Princess is gonna be a magic trick in itself.
First minute, first sale.
Second...
Fourth...
Sixth...
Sixtieth minute... no sales.
This ain't what I expected at all.
I'm at the Grand Galloping Gala...
...and it's not what I dreamed.
This isn't at all what I imagined.
This isn't what I hoped.
This isn't hanging out.
This isn't what I wished for.
No!
I waited all my life...
...for this moment.
And I'm not going to...
...let it slip by.
If it's the last thing I do...
...I'm gonna make this...
...the best night ever!
I just have to be more bold, like Twilight says.
I'm so sorry to have scared you, my friends!
But I'm leaving now, so you can all come out!
Gotcha!
It's okay. I promise not to hurt you.
I just wanna be your...
...friend?
Mmm... Sounds good to me.
Come on, Rainbow!
If they don't notice you,
you gotta make them notice you.
Just give him a chance, Rarity.
His princely side is sure to come out
if you're just patient.
Miss Rarity! Stop!
Oh.
Prince Blueblood! How chivalrous.
One would hate to slip.
Yes. "One" certainly would.
One's cloak should take care of the problem.
Oh, of course it will.
Come on everypony!
I know what will make you
shake those groove-thangs!
You reach your right hoof in
You reach your right hoof out
And you shake it all about
You do the Pony Pokey
Meeting lots of folks with clout
That's what I'm talking about
You step your left hoof in
You pull it right back out
But you better help him out
You do the Pony Pokey
But you'd find a different route
That's what it's all about
You kick your back leg in
You pull your back leg out
You reach your back leg in
Just be brave and have no doubt
You do the Pony Pokey
Feeling like you're gonna pout
That's what I'm singing about
You tilt your head in
You tilt your head out
Then you shake it all about
You do the Pony Pokey
Even though your date's a lout
You're better off without
You stomp your whole self in
You stomp your whole self out
And you stomp yourself about
You do the Pony Pokey
And you give a little shout
COME OUT!
That's what I'm talking about
You do the Pony Pokey
And that's what it's all about
YEAH!
Young lady, this is not *that* kind of partay.
Ooooooh...
They don't want a party.
These ponies want a paaartaaay!
Two apple fritters, please.
Two apple fritters comin' right up.
That'll be four bits.
I'm going to have to pay, aren't I?
It's okay, Rarity.
I got you covered.
Thank you, Applejack. At least
somepony here has good manners.
Oh!
Fritters! Dumplings! Caramel apples!
My royal lips have touched common carnival fare!
I'm going to the buffet for
some... hors d'oeuvres.
Well, no wonder nopony wants my food.
They're fillin' up on all those
fancy-schmancy vittles.
Well, my down-home apples are
plenty good enough for this crowd.
I'll just dress 'em up a bit and prove it to 'em.
I'll catch you yet, my pretties.
Oh yes. As soon as one of you little birds
or monkeys or bears touches this net...
...you'll be MINE! MINE!!!
Come on, everypony!
You wanted a partay?
Now it's paaartaaay!
Yeah!
Now that's a beat, yeah!
C'mon, dance!
Yeah, woohoo!
Okay, all you high-class ponies.
Here's a highfalutin apple cake for
all your hoity-toity taste buds.
STAGE DIVE!
You, sir, are the most UNCHARMING
prince I have EVER MET!
Seems like the only thing royal about you
is that you are a ROYAL PAIN!
Ewww...!
Uh, stay back! I just had myself groomed!
Afraid to get DIRTY?!
This is my chance!
Yes!
Well... it can't get any worse.
You're... going to LOVE ME!!!
Run.
Ooh! Rarity, your glass slipper!
Now your prince is sure to find you.
No!
Let's go!
Hey, Pony Joe. Another donut.
Don't you think you've had enough?
Another donut! Extra sprinkles!
Twilight Sparkle! Ha, ha.
Long time no see.
Hey, how was the Gala?
How was your best night ever?
That sounds like the worst night ever!
It was!
I just hope Princess Celestia isn't upset
at us for ruining the Gala.
That was the best Grand Galloping Gala ever!
Princess Celestia?!
Pardon me, Princess...
...but tonight was just awful.
Oh, Twilight. The Grand Galloping Gala
is always awful.
It is?
That is why I was thrilled you were all attending.
I was hoping you could liven things up a bit.
And while the evening may not
have gone as you planned...
...I'm sure you'll agree that in the end...
...it didn't turn out so bad
for this group of friends.
You're right, Princess.
Friends have a way of making even the worst
of times into something pretty great.
Yeah! Hanging out with friends!
-Talking!
-Laughing!
You mean doing exactly what
I wanted to do the whole time?
Yes, Spike. You were right.
As horrible as our night was...
...being together here has made it all better.
In fact, it's made it...
...the best night ever!
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000