Dear Twilight, it is difficult
to express how grateful I am
to you for teaching me the
power of friendship.
You would think after more
than a thousand years,
there would be nothing
left to learn
And yet, even a pony as old as
I can continue to be surprised
by how much there
is to know.
"I hope you find these
postcards enjoyable
and I look forward to
seeing you again,
though I can't say when my
journey will be complete.
Your friend, Starswirl."
It must be gratifying to have
your idol writing to you
about the friendship
lessons he's learning.
I'm not sure I'll
ever get used to it.
Of course, if he really wants
to learn about friendship,
he could just come
to our school..
Professor Sparkle?
The Mail Pony just came
with uh, a few things.
Oo! The sewing machines
I ordered for my class!
These came, too.
I wasn't sure what
to make of them.
These machines were costly,
but I am quite certain
the friendship lessons
I can teach my students with
them will be invaluable.
Oh don't worry, darling.
I'll think of something
and I didn't use school
funds to buy these.
I made the purchase
entirely with my own bits.
It's not that. It's this!
"Why waste your time at
a friendship school
that's just a school?
Learn everything they teach and
more at Friendship University!?"
Who would open
another friendship school?
Oh pffft. I'm sure it's nothing
to worry about.
You're the Princess
of Friendship.
What could this other
school possibly offer?
It isn't just another friendship
school, it's a University!
It says they teach
"the same lessons
of competing schools
in half the time."
That's twice the
learning!
And it's in Las Pegasus?
If Professor Rarity lets us skip
her sewing class -- ROAD TRIP!
I think we need to
look into this school.
I don't like to judge
solely on appearances,
but.. what kind of
friendship school is this!?
Only the best friendship
school in the West...
and maybe all of Equestria!
There's more ponies in here
than at our whole school.
Who is running this place?
[Male voice] Welcome, friends.
You are about to embark on a
journey of amazing magnitude,
one that will change
your lives forever.
Prepare yourselves to
embrace a new path
and become students of
FRIENDSHIP U!
Flim and Flam. Of course.
♪ If you're alone and you
can't make friends ♪
♪ we understand your plight ♪
♪ Until now there was
just one way ♪
♪ your friendships could
take flight ♪
♪ There is a school
real far away ♪
♪ that'll teach you
what to know ♪
♪ But if you live here
you couldn't stay ♪
♪ you'd learn you have to gooo.. ♪
♪ Now there is an alternative
to all of that adversity ♪
♪ Not just a school
I'll have you know ♪
♪ But a whole University! ♪
♪ At Friendship U
our aim is true ♪
♪ In a city not
some backwater ♪
♪ You'll learn the
things you need to know ♪
♪ At our new alma mater! ♪
That's it, everypony!
You heard correctly!
Friendship U, the one and only
University of friendship!
♪ As you can see we're a
success by any kind of stat ♪
♪ That may be so for all I
know but I still smell a rat ♪
♪ Everypony lookie here that
other school's headmare! ♪
♪ Her presence is a testament
to the mutual respect we shaaare..
What? No it isn't!
♪ It really is the final piece
to make our work complete ♪
♪ To have the
Friendship Princess ♪
♪ bless our school is
such a treat ♪
Were so honoured!
♪ At Friendship U
we teach to you AND YOU! ♪
♪ All of our friendship
knowledge ♪
♪ You'll learn it all
in half the time ♪
♪ at the one and only
friendship college ♪
But how can anypony learn
friendship in half the time!
Our coursework is
so accelerated
to take longer'd
be a crime!
♪ The lessons that we teach ♪
♪ Have been reviewed and
checked and edited ♪
♪ Which might explain
why our school's about
to be accredited ♪
♪ At Friendship U
Oh yes, it's true ♪
♪ Even the Princess of
Friendship agrees ♪
♪ The only place in
Equestria to give out
friendship degrees! ♪
Yeah!
Friendship U!
That's it, everypony!
Let's hear it!
Tell us again why
it's the best!
♪ It's the only University
of Friendship U! ♪
Yeah!
Accredited?
It means officially
recognized or authorized.
We know what it means.
But who would
accredit this place?
Why the EEA, of course!
Chancellor Neighsay?
The Equestria Educational
Association has taken an
interest in institutions
that teach friendship
in a pony-first environment.
Surely you didn't
think your school
has a monopoly on
the concept?
Well, she did write
the book on it.
Ah, yes.
"How to teach
friendship to creatures
who will one day use it as
a weapon against us."
How could they use
friendship as a weapon?
You tell me; it's your book.
Meantime, this university
appears to be a promising option
for ponies who'd prefer to stick
to the EEA book on the subject.
You can't be serious.
They're obviously
up to something.
It's Flim and Flam!
Well, that certainly
wasn't.. friendly.
One would think the headmare
of a school of friendship,
albeit an unaccredited one,
would behave differently.
Unless she was trying to
undermine the competition? Hmm?
I... No... What? I am not!
I did think the Princess of
Friendship would be friendlier.
Now, now fillies
and gentlecolts,
let's show the Princess
just how friendly we are
by signing up for
some classes!
Why don't I show you around?
I'm sorry, but approval from
the EEA won't convince me
that this school is
what you promise.
And what would it
take to convince you?
Well, somepony who's
opinion I respect, for one.
Really? Somepony like... this?
Twilight?
Uh oh.
Starswirl? What are
you doing here?
Why, studying friendship at Flim
and Flam's wonderful school!
Oh, please..
I think I know a
disguise when I see one.
Take off that
ridiculous beard!
FLAM!
How's it going in here?
Oh.. It-it's really me.
I'd heard rumors
you've returned,
but I didn't believe
it until now.
And if a pony of your
stature is studying here,
there really isn't anything
else I need to see.
I, Chancellor Neighsay,
hereby confer upon Friendship
University complete and
unreserved EEA accreditation!
I-I don't understand.
Why would you come
here and not my school?
My travels brought
me to Las Pegasus.
I didn't come for the school,
but Flim and Flam convinced
me to try it out.
Twilight: You can't
trust Flim and Flam!
They tried to con the
Apples out of their farm!
They sold fake health tonic!
They run a resort
in Las Pegasus!
Technically, our resort
is a legitimate business.
I spent a thousand years
thinking the worst
of a "bad" pony.
You taught me to look
for the best in him.
Whatever Flim and
Flam's past may be,
starting this school shows they
want to change for the better.
I wish I could believe that.
Besides, what's untrustworthy
about opening a
school of friendship?
They don't even
charge for classes.
I don't know.
But I know they're
up to something
and until I find out,
I'm begging you, come
to my school instead.
I understand feeling
threatened by competition.
But my word, Princess, I
wonder if the ill-manners
of the creatures at your
school aren't contagious.
I think I will take my leave
before I become infected.
Twilight, I promise I'll
visit your school soon,
but for now, perhaps it's
best if you return there.
You don't think they're running
an actual friendship school,
do you?
Darling, of course not.
Which is why we
have to investigate!
But we can't go poking
around the school.
Everypony'll think
I'm still just
"threatened by
the competition."
Only if we do it
as.. ourselves.
In these disguises,
we could pass as students
at out own school.
I don't know, Rarity.
Ah-ah. What did I say about
using our real names?
Sorry, "Plainity." But
I'm pretty sure this..
isn't enough of a disguise.
Hey, strangers. Are
you two new here?
We sure are. Completely new!
Great! See you in class!
Now, I've read enough Shadow
Spade to know the key to going
undercover is rehearsing
your backstory.
I'm "Plainity" and I love
bland-old-normal stuff.
No frills for me.
OK! Heh. Your turn.
[groan] My name's Eyepatch.
I have an eyepatch.
Per-fect!
Now, how do we start
our investigation?
I think we should split up.
You enroll in some classes
and find out what they're
actually teaching.
I'll look around and
see what I can find,
assuming I'm not recognized....
Welcome, newest students!
Let's dive right in, shall we?
One of the most important
elements of friendship
is being thoughtful,
true or false?
If by thoughtful you mean
generous, I'd say true.
Correct! Ha hah!
It was a trick question.
Very impressive, Ms...?
Plainity.
Well, well well, Ms. Plainity,
keep it up and you'll be ready
for our next level in no time!
Now, let's see if you can
demonstrate for the class.
What's something generous you
could do for me right now?
Class, Plainity here
is now my star pupil.
If any of you want a chance
at studying with Starswirl,
I'd take notes on
her every action.
Hello?
The door is open, so I'll just
assume it's OK to come in
and look around, unless
somepony says it's not.
All right, then.
"The Element of Laughter
and its applications."
OK, that seems pretty genuine.
"When to support your
friends' decisions
and when to talk sense."
Huh, that's actually
kind of interesting.
Ah-ha! "Friendship
University's true goal
is to help friends
become better friends?"
Where is the proof
that it's all a scam?
There isn't any...
Twilight Sparkle!
Did you really think an eye
patch was enough of a disguise?
No, I didn't!
Well then, we agree that
everypony will recognize the
Princess of Friendship
in this photo of you
sneaking into our office.
I can see the headline
now, "Princess of Jealousy!
Twilight Sparkle bent on
ruining her competition!"
So sad.
A news story like that
would destroy your reputation.
Nopony will want to go to
your school after that.
Just wait until the
papers get a hold of this.
Princess Unhinged!
It'll be the talk of Equestria.
Well, gentleponies, I've
finished another stack.
The lessons in these worksheets
are quite fascinating.
Twilight? What's
going on here?
Oh, just your protégé getting
caught snooping in our office
in disguise! Well, sort of.
Oh honestly, Princess Twilight,
envy does not look good on you.
I'm not envious!
I know these two
are up to something.
I'm just trying
to find out what!
The only pony I see who's up
to something is the pony
in this picture, and it is
not the Princess I know.
Well, it's about to be the
Princess all of Equestria knows.
Unless...
you decided to drop the whole,
"uncover the scam" thing.
Then we'll rip this silly
picture up and not let it
completely and utterly
ruin you and your school.
You can be generous with
all sorts of things.
Gifts, compliments, your time.
Hey, Eyepatch!
Where's your eyepatch?
[gasp] Was your cover blown?
You could say that.
Flim and Flam took a picture of
me sneaking into their office.
Were we wearing our eye patch?
If I don't stop investigating,
they're going to tell everypony
that I'm trying to
sabotage their school
because I'm jealous.
But but but...
that's ridiculous!
I don't know.
Maybe I am just upset
that Starswirl came here
instead of my school.
Flim and Flam may have
turned over a new leaf.
We should probably just go home.
Twilight, you are not
the kind of pony
to let your emotions
cloud your judgement.
If you think Flim and
Flam are up to no good,
you can't give up,
even if their lessons
really are impressive!
Wait. WHAT?
Which reminds me. Can you
get a message to Spike?
I want to return
those sewing machines.
I need the bits if I'm going
to keep advancing here.
Tuition's free, but the
worksheets sure aren't!
Flim and Flam are
charging for these?
Well, they have
to cover expenses,
and Flam insists that
everything extra
goes to improving
the school and...
This is the scam, isn't it?
Let's find out!
These lessons are
so valuable.
Are you sure I
can't give you more?
Ah ah ah! Unnecessary!
Being able to share them
with a pony like you
is our real reward.
Oh, my. And you want to study
alongside Starswirl, hm?
It's all I have.
Come back for the rest
when you can afford it.
Wait! I'll sell the
shirt off my back!
Aaand that's the kind of
determination that'll get you
to the next level, student
whose.. name I know!
Twilight, maybe I should
take over the investigation.
Think of your reputation!
My reputation isn't worth
much if I won't risk it
for what I think is right.
Besides, I have a plan.
Well, brother of mine, we've got
almost all the bits we need
to expand our resort.
If we add another level of
classes and worksheets,
we'll be there!
Maybe we should add two
levels, just to be safe.
Ah! It's a thing of beauty.
But I was thinking,
what if we added another
extreme pool slide here?
Sure, as long as the pipes for
the musical chocolate fountain
go through.. here.
Twilight: But
shouldn't it go closer
to the pudding
hot tub here?
Fair point, but-- WHAT?
I knew your school was a scam!
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the
Princess of Jealousy.
I guess we'll be going
to the papers after all.
And I suppose I'll just
lead your students
into this secret room of bits
and resort expansion plans!
Err.. let's not get hasty.
You have something on us;
we have something on you.
Let's just call it.. even.
I don't think so.
You can destroy my
reputation if you want,
but using your students' bits to
expand your resort is wrong,
even if the lessons you
teach are good ones.
Of course, they're good.
We copied them from your book.
We just skipped
every other page.
"All the lessons,
half the time!"
Ugh. Fine. If you really
want to call it even,
give back the bits and stop
charging for my lessons.
Then you can teach them
as much as you like.
Nah! Running a school is
more work than we thought.
Besides, we almost have
everything we need.
I think not!
Plainity?
My star pupil?
Not Plainity, but...
Rarity!
Who?
We decided to bring
somepony else here
to listen to everything
you just said!
[mumble] Hey! Starswirl. We
were just about to--
Return the bits
you've collected from
your students and
close your school?
[gulp] Yeah. That.
Ah, it seems I'll
never stop learning
from your example,
Twilight.
It is a valuable lesson to stand
up for what you know is true.
I wish I had known it too.
Thanks for returning our bits,
but how are we going to
learn about friendship now?
Well, I can refer you to a
fairly reputable establishment
just outside of Ponyville.
I'm quite certain the headmare
would consider letting you in.
"Of course, if I ever
go to a school again,
I'll make sure it's yours.
In friendship, Starswirl."
I still don't understand
how Flim and Flam
could have gotten
a copy of your book.
Uh. I finished straightening
up in the library.
Professor Rarity, I just
wanted to make sure
you're definitely
keeping these.
But of course, darling.
If there's one thing I learned
at Friendship University,
it is not to give up when
you know what's right
and I know teaching friendship
through sewing is right!
I just need to figure out how...