Is the banner even?
Are the flowers in place?
...by which I mean
completely out of view.
I'm pretty sure
dragons don't like flowers...
And what about the ceremonial
Dragon-Fire Flame of Friendship?
Is it still flaming?
Spike, everything
looks great!
You're getting yourself
worked up for no reason.
I have lots of reasons!
In fact, I wrote them down.
Uh.. You've been hanging around
Twilight for too long.
Heh...
Reason number one:
I invited Dragon Lord
Ember to Ponyville today.
Reason two, the Dragon
Lord is a dragon.
Reason three: she's coming here
to learn more about friendship.
According to Ember's letters,
the dragons are
trying to be friends,
but competing is
in their nature
and it's leading to
more and more fights.
Which brings me to
reason number four:
The Dragon Lord wants my advice!
And as the new official
Equestrian Friendship Ambassador
to the dragons, I
can't let her down.
I know you feel a
lot of pressure,
but you've got this, Spike.
I...
I just want things
to be perfect.
[gasp!] Thorax... you're in Ponyville!
Of course I am, silly!
You invited me and I'm not one
to back out of an invitation.
Hey, Twilight.
Hey, Starlight.
Twilight: Heyyy...
Starlight: Hello....
Thorax: Oooh!
I can't believe you
did all this for me!
Great banner!
Love the stage!
What's this flame thingy?
Oh, it's pretty.
You invited Thorax
over to Ponyville
on the same day as Ember!?
Apparently...
That doesn't seem
like a good idea.
How are you going to
entertain them both?
I have no idea!
I completely forgot
Thorax wrote
and said he needed to talk
and I told him to come over.
I didn't realize it was the
same day I invited Ember!
What am I gonna do!?
Well, maybe they'll
like each other?
Probably not.
Ember is tough and
self-assured and intimidating.
And Thorax is...
Spike, I'm so glad
you invited me.
You are one of my closest,
nicest, most caring,
most understanding
friends ever.
Oh! Is that ice in the
shape of a dragon?
Yeah, I see
your point.
They might not
get each other.
Or worse, they'll
hate each other.
And if the leader of the
Changelings and the Dragon Lord
get into a fight...
I could be responsible
for starting a war
that could ruin
Equestria as we know it!
I'm sure that
won't happen.
Now, pull it together.
So... Thorax...
everything good with you?
Well, honestly, no, not really.
I have indigestion, not
sure if it's the new diet,
or stress or maybe it's both.
No!
Yeah. It really could be both.
And it might be affecting
my sleeping, too.
Twilight: Uh oh..
Thorax: I'm a real tosser and
turner these-
Sounds like you
really need to unwind!
Er.. how about a er.. a trip
to the castle?
You can't miss that view!
Yes, the castle!
I'll give you a
personal tour.
Are.. aren't you coming?
Yeah...I'm just gonna grab some
ice cream for us and catch up.
Heh heh.
Dragon Lord Ember, as the
official Equestrian Friendship
Ambassador for the Dragonlands
and for Ponyville,
I, Spike of Ponyville,
welcome you to...
Ponyville.
I gotta work on my
official speech..
OK. Thanks.
Heh heh.. right. The hug thing...
Heh heh.
This place has a lot of colors.
In the Dragonlands, everything's
just rocks or the color of ash.
ACHOO!!
That's probably why..
Hey, Twilight!
Actually, I'm Starlight.
Starlight Glimmer.
Nice to meet you.
Oh, sorry.
I'm.. really gonna have to get
used to these pony names.
Lots of "lights"
and shiny things.
Er.. so where is Twilight?
She's in her castle--
OH!
We should go visit her then.
Part of friendship is saying
hi to your friends, right?
Uhh...
well yeah.. but...
You're making weird noises.
Do you have a stomach ache?
[gasp] I think I feel one coming on..
Well, you know what us dragons
say: push past the pain.
Now let's go!
Or.. we could stay here.
Or I could go without you.
Heh heh heh. Ah.
I like her.
Oh..
Good, they're not here.
What was that?
Uh, I...I said, it's
all clean in here!
Er.. you must be hungry
from your travels.
Please, I'd love to present
you with an official
Friendship Welcome Banquet.
So this is something friends do?
I could get used to this.
Actually that's
not food...
Dragons love gems.
Fine, but you're telling
Twilight what happened
to her wall.
Just keep her here.
OK, yeah, enjoy
all the crystal... things..
Where are you going?
I thought this was an
official friendship banquet.
Just gotta use the
little dragon's room.
So this is my comfy chair
for fictional reads.
This is my studying chair
because the hard
back keeps me awake.
Oh, Spike! I'm so
glad you're here.
This castle visit
is getting weird.
Twilight really likes chairs.
Oh. What happened to the ice cream?
What? Oh, right!
Uh, they ran out.
Hey, I'm really sorry, but I
gotta borrow Twilight quickly.
Wah!
Be right back!
But we didn't get to talk yet!
Ember's here!
I know; I saw you coming
and had to distract Thorax
by showing him chairs!
Why did you bring Ember to
the castle of all places?
I don't know!
Ember was asking for you, Thorax
wants to talk with me...
we need to switch places!
They might be
getting suspicious!
All we have to do is make both
Thorax and Ember feel special
and keep them apart
for a few more hours.
We can do this.
Ah! What's happening!?
Ah..!
I think it's the map!
It's calling... you!
Apparently, you also have to
solve a friendship problem.
The map is calling me!?
Oh... amazing! The map is
really reaching out!
Not a good time,
I get it.
Starlight: Spike, are you here?
Ember's eaten all of
Twilight's decorations and--
Oh! Hey Twilight. Heh...
Glowing map.. [gulp] glowing spikes...
That's not good.
I KNOW!
At least your friendship
problem is in Ponyville?
OK, OK, to pull this
off, I'm going to need
both of you to help.
You two need to keep
Ember and Thorax separate
while I
get ice cream.
You mean find the
friendship problem.
Yes....
Go easy on me.
I'm under a lot
of pressure!
Friendship Problem?
Anypony got a
friendship problem here?
Any problems to solve?
Friendship problems?
Friendship Problems!
Anypony got a
friendship problem here?
No? OK.
Uch. Well I think vanilla
strawberry cream is overused!
Hmph.
Yes! Fighting!
Uh, I mean, what seems
to be the problem?
Ember, there you are!
OK... right,
more pony hugs.
How's your trip to
Ponyville so far?
Well, I'm certainly learning
a lot about friendship.
I had no idea it was polite
to decorate your walls
in your friends' favorite foods.
Heh heh. Oh, my...
Where'd Spike and Starlight go?
I feel like I'm being avoided.
Hmph.
No! They're just making
sure everything is perfect
for your welcome party later.
In the meantime, how about
I show you around town?
Sounds good.
I can't exactly learn
about friendship
if I don't make new friends.
Oh!
Uh.. Hey Thorax...
Um. Twilight and Spike had some
boring official paperwork
to deal with, so looks like
you and I get to hang out.
What would you like to do?
But I wanted to
talk with Spike.
He said he'd be right back.
Oh you will, but first how
about we grab a bite to eat?
Huh. Well you know, now that you've said
it, I am a little hungry.
Is there a dining
room in the castle?
NO!
... I mean yeah, but
that's castle food.
If you want the good
stuff, we gotta go to town.
... and that's why you should
never let cupcake flavors
get in the way of
your friendship.
Huh. I guess I never thought of it
that way. Thanks, Spike.
Oh, come on! Glow!
Thorax: Spike!
There you are!
Done with your boring
paper work I see.
Ha ha ha...! A-huh.. A-huh..?
Yup, heh heh. I am done with whatever
Starlight says I was doing...
Thorax wanted to get
out of the castle.
I thought coming to town was
a really, really great idea.
Well! Maybe now we can talk.
Ssssure.
I'll leave you guys to it.
First of all, I want to say
thank you for having me over.
I'm in a bit of a
leadership pickle
and I could use
some advice.
Well, I definitely want to help
you out as quickly as possible.
Here's my problem: there's this
renegade group of changelings
who still feed off of love.
Even though I said, "Hey, let's
not do that anymore," they say,
"Hey this is how we've
been doing things
for hundreds of years-"
-but it's like they don't
want to even though
I'm the leader and I
asked politely...
Hello!
I am Ember, daughter of Torch,
winner of the Gauntlet of Fire
and lord of all dragons!
Usually when I do that, the
dragons are eager to meet me.
That's not how
ponies make friends.
Ahh... I get it.
This is a weird friendship
thing you ponies do, right?
Uh... you guys
are in town, too?
What are you
talking about?
You've been with
me this whole time.
No, I'm Starlight.
Riiiiight.
I'm sorry, but you
can't blame me.
You both look and
act so much alike.
Both: What!?
And they said to me just
keep saying the same thing.
You know I think my leadership
problems started in childhood.
I must've been three when ...
Three's a different story --
and you definitely
gotta hear it,
but the story about my
brother was when I was two...
Or was I one?
This is my seat!
I saw it first.
Well, I got here first.
Thorax, excuse me for a second.
Ponies, please.
If I may, I think I can help
solve this.. friendship problem.
You two should sit together.
You both like the same place;
you both ordered muffins;
you're both ponies.
I think if you made
a little effort,
you'd find that you
have a .... whoa!
OK, that had to have done it.
Come on spikes, glow!
Hey, that was
really great advice.
So what do you
think I should do?
Actually, I uh need a minute.
Alone. To really come
up with great advice.
I'll be right back!
[sigh] Great. No problem.
Leave me again...
It's fine....
I'm just saying, you're both
purple ponies with purple hair.
You both have cutie marks
with sparkle-y things.
Heh. Mine's more of
a glimmer..! Heh.
How is that different?
Oh, good, Spike.
Can you please tell
these two I'm right?
They look very similar.
Er.. Well, you know, one thing
friends do is let something go
when it's upsetting
somepony else.
But I'm right.
Besides, who are you to be
telling me about friendship?
I've barely seen
you all day!
Uh.. well.. I've seen you...
Are you calling me a LIAR!?
Hey! No one yells
at my friend!
Spike, get away from the bear!
Actually the bear's a changeling
and he's quite gentle.
Not anymore!
Aaah! My worst fears are happening!
NO!
Huh. Back away, Spike, I'm not
going to let this dragon
harm a scale on your back!
You back away! I'm not
going to let you harm him!
Wait, did you say you're not
going to let me harm Spike?
Yeah!
But that's what I'm doing.
Uh..what?
Yeah, what?
Ahh.. Equestria as we know it is over!
The war that pits
changeling against dragon
is about to begin!
And it's all my fault!
My title of Equestria's
Friendship Ambassador is a lie--
Oh. Hey. You guys
aren't fighting?
Why would we be fighting?
Because I accidentally
invited you both
over to Ponyville
on the same day?
Both: So what?
So, I was trying
to keep you apart,
because I didn't
think you'd get along.
Oh, I get it.
You thought he wouldn't like me
just because I'm a dragon
and I'm bad at friendship?
No! No! Of course not! But...
Wait, isn't that
why you're here?
I can say I'm bad at friendship;
you can't say it about me!
You know what? I don't
want to talk about it.
Wait, please...
[sigh] I'm sorry.
No, no. It's cool.
You thought I'd be too soft
and someone like Ember
would never respect me, just
like my own changelings.
No, that's not it!
Thorax! Wait!
Oh, no.
What have I done?
Why are you still here?
[sigh] Because I'm having
trouble leading my pack.
So I don't really
want to go home.
Wait, you're in charge?
Ho boy, you need to
be more assertive.
That's my problem,
I don't know how.
I tried asking them to please
follow my directions
and I even offered
a prize and--
SHH! Stop talking.
That's how you do it.
Whoa. That just
gave me chills.
I know you have
it in you.
You turned into a
bear to defend Spike.
Huh. I guess I can be tough when
I'm defending my friends.
But.. when I'm just enforcing my
rules, I feel unsure of myself.
There's nothing to
be unsure of.
You're the leader
for a reason.
Make a decision and
let it be known
that the decision is final.
And if that doesn't
work, turn into a bear.
That's good advice.
I know it is.
So what's your deal?
Why do you think you're
so bad at friendship?
I don't want to
talk about it.
Oh, you have to.
How else are you gonna
solve your problems?
Through feats of strength
and fire duels, of course.
Hiyah!
Uh... how did that help?
Crushing another
dragon in competition
establishes my dominance
and makes me feel great!
Right, but how do
you think they feel?
Humiliated! Ashamed!
They probably want to run
away and bury themselves
under a rock and...
... never come out.
They're probably sad.
Kinda low.
Definitely not happy.
That's because that kind of
competition can divide you.
And it doesn't get to
the heart of the issue.
Talking about your
feelings does.
A-Achoo!
Ach. I think I'm allergic
to feelings.
You know you don't have to  be
sappy or huggy-feely about it,
but you should let your
friends know how you feel.
Ah.. I know where
we can start.
Where?
Oh. Spike. Heh.
I got there.
♪♪
I think they're gone.
They probably never
want to see me again.
Or ... they want
to see you now.
Guess what, Spike?
I know. I'm so sorry--
LET ME TALK ABOUT THIS!
I feel...
... mad.
OK.., that's a good
first attempt.
Now maybe try to
be more.. specific?
I'm...
ugh...
upset!
You have every right to be.
I KNOW I DO!
And I know I need to
tell you how I feel
because my friend, Thorax, said
it would make me feel better.
AND IT DOES!
Yeah! And I have no
problem telling you
what you did
was wrong
because my
friend Ember
is helping me be
more assertive.
Whoa.
Nice!
Ha ha!
You guys should be mad at me.
I was so worried about
how it could go wrong,
I didn't even think about
how it could go right.
Can you forgive me?
I really do
feel better.
So, yeah. I'm good.
Heh. Me too.
Oooh..
Ohhh.. again?
No way! It's finally happening!
I solved a friendship problem!
Actually, you created
the friendship problem
by not trusting your friends.
Yeah, but then I solved
it by learning my lesson.
I should have told
my two friends
about each other immediately,
instead of assuming
they wouldn't get along.
Good job, Spike.
Is this another part
of pony friendship?
Telling each other what
you learned all the time?
Yeah, pretty much!
Yep!
Spike: So! As a
show of unity,
I present the Dragon Fire
Flame of Friendship
to both Dragon Lord Ember
and Thorax, Leader of
the Changeling Pack.
May the Flame of Friendship
burn for eternity.
A-Achoo!
You should have more
things made of rocks.