Uh, Headmare Twilight?
Sorry to bug you in
the teachers' lounge.
Is it OK if I miss class?
Mm hm. You can make
it up tomorrow.
Actually, I'll be
gone for a week.
A week!? In the middle
of the semester?
Oh! Is everything
all right, Smolder?
Not exactly.
My brother's been
having a hard time
since I left for school.
I want to go home
and check on him.
He's a really sweet guy,
and the other dragons
can be kinda rough.
Did you say sweet guy and
dragon in the same sentence?
Yeah. He's sorta
like you, Spike.
Aww!
I'm sorry to hear about
your brother, Smolder.
But the Dragonlands are really
far for you to go by yourself,
and I'm not sure about you
missing so much class.
Hey! What if she got
school credit for it?
Kind of like a... Kindness
field trip! I'll go with her!
Thanks! The Dragonlord is way
too busy for personal problems
when it's baby-dragon-
hatching season.
Baby-dragon-hatching season!?
[gasp] All those cute little
snouts poking out of those
adorable little shells?
Teeny tiny twitchy tails!
Can I go too..?
Well, you are the perfect pony
to lead a kindness field trip.
[sigh] Fine. But I'm going to
expect a full report
when you get back!
How many pages?
I was talking
to Fluttershy.
Hatching season
sounds fascinating!
Spike: OK, I made a list of what
cheers me up when I'm down,
so if your brother's like
me, he's gonna love it!
What should we do
first: the "smile" song,
the sharing circle, or
friendship bracelet weaving?
I'm not sure those
are the kind of things
my brother's gonna be into...
Well, what would make
your brother happy?
Just having Spike and me
accept him for who he is
will make a huge difference.
Dragons who appreciate
his more sensitive side.
I got it! Showtunes!
Yeah, no. But
good try.
Oh! Um, that's an
interesting smell.
Ah! The stink of sulfur,
sharp rocks under my claws.
It's good to be home.
I can't wait to meet
your brother, Smolder.
We're gonna be best
buddies, I just know it!
He usually hangs out near
here. I'll go try and find him.
Spike, do you mind
if I take a peek
at the cute
little baby eggs?
No problem! I'll stay here and
finish this comfort blanket.
It'll be like a hug
every time Smolder's brother
wraps it around himself.
Aw, I'm sure he'll
love it, Spike.
♪♪
[excited gasp]
Oh, my goodness!
Good morning, little one. I've
come a long way to meet you.
Did you know there's a
whole wide world out here
waiting to say hello?
Did you? Oh, did you boo? [cooing]
It can't answer
you. It's an egg.
Ah! Dragonlord Ember,
how nice to see you.
Nice to see you too, uh
...which one are you again?
The party one? Apple Dash?
Or was that the country one?
Fluttershy. The one
who loves creatures.
Are all these.. yours?
WHAT? No! None
of them are.
Watching over eggs is just
part of the glamorous life
of a Dragonlord.
I think it sounds wonderful.
Yeah? Then maybe
you can help.
[gasp] I'd love to! Just
tell me what to do!
I don't know! It's my
first time being in charge.
Dad wasn't big on sharing
Dragonlord details.
It's.. kind of a burn
or be burned job.
Well, I'm sure
you're doing great!
Not really. The eggs should
have hatched by now...
But none of them
have even cracked.
Oh, dear. Maybe
they're lonely?
Don't you worry. Auntie
Fluttershy's here.
And the Dragonlord and I are
going to do everything we can
to welcome you into this world!
Really? How?
Um. I have no idea.
Now that's a thing of beauty.
♪ [tense music] ♪
Whoa!
Well, if it isn't our
little pony-friend, Spike.
That's "Equestria's Official
Friendship Ambassador
to the Dragonlands" to you.
And I'm not little.
I had the molt, see?
Ooh, runt's got wings!
I'm so impressed...
What's that supposed to be?
Nothing!
Agh!
Looks like a...
baby blanket to me.
It's not a baby blanket!
It's a... comfort blanket.
Aww... Did your pony
pals make it for you
with friendship and gumdrops?
No... I made it.
And by the way, knitting is
a lot harder than it looks.
Check out the baby
blanket, guys!
It's a lot harder
than it looks!
Hup!
Got your bwankie!
Aw, the little baby crying...
Whoa, miss!
Bet he broke a claw
and everything! Hah!
Give it back! That's
for my friend!
Cut it out!
You know laugh-fire is
dangerous! It can...
...do that.
Garble!
Smolder?
What are you doing here?
How's it scalin', bra?
We'd better get out of here
before your brother shows up.
Garble isn't very nice
to sensitive dragons.
But... Garble
IS my brother.
Your brother!?
Got a problem with
that, ponyboy?
Oh, brother.
Ohhh..!
I've missed you, bro! We got
a lot of fun to catch up on.
There's no lava
diving at school.
Good luck getting
Garble to do anything.
Huh. Yeah, he's been so
weird since you left.
Hiding, and
moping around...
I have not!
Have so!
Easy, guys. I learned
at Twilight's school,
ganging up on each other isn't
half as cool as you think.
Aw, Pony school made you soft.
Wanna try me and find out?
[gulp] Maybe later.
So... Let's get lava
diving! Whaddya say?
Better stay here, shrimp.
Lava might ruin your
blankie-wankie...!
Let the wimp tag along.
Then we'll have
somedragon to dunk! Hahaha!
Hm! Only gonna warn you
once. Spike's my friend.
You mess with him,
you mess with me.
Besides, he came here to
hang out with YOU, Garble.
Aw, how sweet...! Hah!
Let's go do dragon stuff.
Garble can have fun
with his new friend!
But I'm not having fun!
And he's not my friend!
Yeah just ignore them, GarGar.
Smolder! Not in public!
Oh, it's OK to
have a nickname!
Sometimes I'm
called Spikey Wikey.
Seriously? You're
admitting this?
I am not hanging
out with him.
Give him a chance, Garble. You
guys have a lot in common.
Ugh. Fine. Race you to the Lava Pit.
Wait! I thought you said
your brother was sweet.
All the tough guy
stuff is just an act.
He's a big marshmallow.
Yeah. Not seeing it.
Well, maybe a
burned marshmallow.
Smoky on the outside,
but squishy inside.
He just needs friends who
can appreciate that part.
Like you.
You're not
changing your mind
about helping me
cheer him up, are you?
Me? 'Course not!
OK! Lava jumping, just
like old times, huh GarGar?
Yeah. Just like old times.
Except for one little,
annoying thing.
Scales away!
Come on in! The lava's fine!
Ya know, whenever I'm
feeling a little down,
it always helps if I do
something with a friend.
How about we jump together?
Agh!
Ooooh. Spike? You OK?
Er. I know there must be something
worse than lava up your nose.
Ah ah ah ahchoo!
I just don't know it is.
CANNON BALL!
Agh! [splash]
Woohoo! Ha ha ha!
Oops..!
SWALLOWING lava. Swallowing
lava is definitely worse.
My bad.
And then they all lived
happily ever after!
Time to come out, little ones!
Maybe you'd like a song?
I think you might be
encouraging them to stay in.
Dragons aren't much for
touchy-feely stuff.
Oh. I'm sorry.
Goodness! Why are
the eggs shaking?
[gasp] Are they finally hatching?
I wish. They've been
doing that for days.
I'm sure it means something.
But it's probably not good.
Try this. Red velvet.
Guaranteed to brighten
anycreature's spirits!
Feeling better already.
I don't know about you,
but a change of scenery
always turns my
frown upside down.
AAh!
I will be the bigger dragon.
Sometimes just hearing what
someone appreciates about you
can make you feel
better about yourself.
I'll go first.
Spike, I think
it's really nice
that you're trying
to cheer up GarGar.
Agh...!
Thank you, Smolder.
My turn.
I like how you always
let everycreature know
how you're feeling, GarGar.
ONLY SMOLDER GETS
TO CALL ME THAT!
Thank you for
speaking your truth...!
More fresh lava, comin' up!
OK, NEW activity. Who wants
to make vision boards?
Hey, Garble! Smolder! Surf's up!
Let ME show you how it's done!
You coming?
I'll.. catch up with you.
Ah Spike! There
you are!
Hey, Fluttershy.
For a land that's
all rocks,
this place is surprisingly
easy to get lost in.
How are the baby dragons doing?
The eggs won't hatch!
They just keep shaking.
I'm starting to think the
dragons are too scared
to come out. I was
hoping you could help...
...If you're not too busy
cheering up Smolder's brother.
Not a chance. Smolder's
brother is GARBLE.
The only thing that cheers him
up is to make me miserable.
Hey, Spike! Wanna
play lava ball?
Huh!?
Excuse me! But that's
not a very nice game.
Ah, nearly got you!
ENOUGH!!
Ahem. I mean, leave my
friend alone, please.
Spike came all this
way to cheer up Garble,
which was a very
kind thing to do.
Aw, do you need
cheering up?
What's wrong, Garble?
Did somedragon hurt
your wittle feewings?
No! I don't know what
she's talking about!
Spike's the one who's gonna cry!
HEY! Are we lava
surfing or what?
Uh yeah! Yeah! Let's go
hang with a REAL dragon.
Not a pony wanna-be!
See? It's no use.
Why don't I see what I
can do about the eggs,
and you cheer up Garble. At
least he listens to you.
Just you wait, Garble. You're
dealing with Fluttershy now.
And she's packing a whole
lifetime of kindness.
Oh...
Koochie koochie koo.
Koochie koochie koo...
koochie! Koochie koochie
koo. [angry] I said Koochie!
Spike: Uh, what are you doing?
[gasp] SPIKE!
Hi Ember!
Shouldn't you be doing
whatever it is you do
at Twilight's school?
I wish. It's a long story.
Wow. These eggs
really do look scared.
Wait, aren't the hatching
grounds supposed to be hot?
Uh of course! There's a lake
of molten lava under them.
That's why the
eggs are laid here;
the heat makes them hatch!
Then something's wrong.
I don't think the
eggs are shaking
'cause they're
afraid. They're cold.
You're right! But what
happened to the lava?
I might have an idea.
Garble? Smolder? Is
any dragon there?
♪ [drumming] ♪
Oh, my. Are those...
bongo drums?
Fire, dragon, wig and wagon...
Feelin' like I be saggin'...
Oh, yeah, I dig!
♪ [drumming] ♪
Ragin' lava, balaclava ...
Huh?
Fresh lava coming up!
♪♪
See?
I wondered where that
lava was coming from.
They must be draining it
from the underground lake!
Grr!
Put that rock back! Immediately!
Uh, yes, Dragonlord Ember!
How long have you been
removing these boulders?
A while..?
It made our lava pools
so nice and warm-like.
Ah! It's supposed to be
heating the EGGS!
Now they'll never hatch!
Sorry, Dragonlord Ember!
We'll put the lava back!
Agh! Here you go, lava! Aw come
on! Don't you have to go!
Faster!
It's liquidy!
I don't think it works that way.
The hatching grounds can't be the
only warm place in the Dragonlands.
There's got to be somewhere
else we can take the eggs!
You know how fragile
those things are?
No way we'll be able to
move them all safely.
Grr! YOU! Go and bring
all the dragons
to the hatching grounds.
We'll have to make
the heat ourselves.
What do you think you're doing
sneaking around here, Pony?
Sneaking? It looks to me like
the only one sneaking around
is you, Garble. Why didn't
you tell me you were a poet?
I'm not!
Ah!
♪♪
♪ Words, rhythm, sometimes
rhyme. Weird punctu-ation. ♪
Sure sounds like poetry to me.
It's OK, GarGar.
Fluttershy won't think you're
soft for being a poet.
And neither would anydragon
who was your real friend.
Ugh. OK, fine. But I'm not a
flowery namby pamby poet.
I'm a beat poet...dig?
I totally feel you!
And you better not tell
my friends about it!
But...why? If I was a poet,
I'd want to share my
creations with everypony.
I'm the only one Garble
will perform for.
He hasn't written any
poetry since I left.
That's why he's been so sad.
I NEED to create! But if the
other dragons ever found out
I like this junk, they'd
make fun of me. Forever.
Is that why you pick on Spike?
To make your friends
think you're tough?
Wait. You've been
picking on Spike?
Uhh. Only when you're not looking...
But if I didn't pick on Spike,
they'd just pick on me.
And he is kind of a weakling...
Hmmph! I'll have you know Spike
is STRONGER than you are!
Any day!
Yeah, right. That
little cupcake-making,
blanket-cuddling
pony-dragon? Gimmie a break!
[gasp] First of all, there's nothing
wrong with being a pony!
Second, Spike isn't
afraid to be who he is,
no matter what you...
or anycreature thinks.
That's real strength... Not
like somedragons I know.
For a pony without a horn,
she's sure got a point.
I've been looking all
over for you guys!
We need your
help! Hurry!
I've ordered everydragon
to warm up the eggs,
but they still won't hatch.
I don't know what
else we can try!
We can't give up! There's got
to be something we can do.
How 'bout we wrap the eggs
in a bunch of baby blankets?
Heheh! Yeah! The wimp can knit
'em up real quick-like.
Hey, watch it! That laugh-fire
could burn someponies!
Burn! Good idea, Spikey Wikey!
Eggs. Come. Burst
into that light.
Break through
shells that... bind!
♪♪
Break free. Explore!
Stuck between rock
and... hard place!
Freedom. Come. Don't be shy.
Look those others in the eye.
Stake your claim.
Don't stop, just do!
Be the one and only.. you!
Spike, look!
Wha-Huh!? Their laugh-fire is so hot,
it's hatching the eggs!
Come to light. Proud to be.
Open up! Bam! Be... FREE!
You did it, GarGar!
You performed in front
of other dragons!
Heh. And it was SUPER-LAME.
What kind of weakling
writes poetry?
The hero of the
Dragonlands, that's who!
Yeah! Garble saved our eggs
because he was strong enough
to be who he is, whether
you liked it or not.
I grew up thinking it was OK
to make fun of differences.
But my friends have taught
me to celebrate them!
And from now on, in my kingdom,
that's exactly what we will do!
Now, if you don't
mind, can you teach me
how to write poetry like
that? It's pretty cool.
Uh, yeah. Sure, no problem!
Yeah, me too!
I wanna learn!
Take a number, guys.
I'll take them all! Oh, my!