Hey, Applejack.
Whatchya doin'?
Well, I was practicin'
my distance buckin'.
Distance bucking? What for?
Because Cousin Braeburn and
the rest of the Apple Family
in Appleoosa seem to think
that their team can beat
Ponyville at Buckball.
WHAT? Ha! That's ridiculous!
Nopony beats Ponyville!
I mean, I could beat the whole
town of Appleoosa at Buckball
with one wing tied
behind my back.
So I can count on you to join
the Ponyville Buckball team?
Oh, yeah! I am so there.
I've just got one question.
Mm?
Uh, what's Buckball?
Regular subtitles
By YayPonies
WARNING: Cuteness overload.
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
So basically, Buckball
is the coolest game ever.
Offense! Defense!
Teamwork. Non-stop action.
It's got it all!
Wow, Rainbow Dash. You
sure seem to know a lot
about this game. I've never
even heard of Buckball.
Yeah. I'm kind of an expert.
Hah, an expert who hadn't
heard of the game either
until I told you.
Well, it's a
new game.
I probably know more
than most ponies
so that makes me
an expert.
I don't know anything
about it at all.
But it sounds like there's
a ball and bucking,
so I'm betting it's
super-duper fun.
The point is my
cousin Braeburn
somehow convinced
a Pegasus
and a unicorn to
come play
with him on the
Appleoosa team.
And he can't stop bragging
about how his team
is gonna beat ours.
But, um, we don't
have a team.
Well, between Applejack and me,
we've got two
thirds of a team.
All we need is
a unicorn.
That's where you
two come in.
Uh, they know we're
not unicorns, right?
Uh, obviously. You're
gonna be on my team
and Fluttershy is gonna
be on Applejack's team.
We'll play against each other,
along with whatever unicorns
wanna try out until
we find the best one.
Oooohhhhhh! Phew,
that's a relief
because I left my
unicorn costume at home.
I know a lot of you are
here because I told you
what an amazing
game Buckball is.
And even though it's already
an Apple Family favorite,
most of you probably don't
know anything about it.
So I thought we'd give
you a quick demonstration.
The two earth ponies
are on offense.
They meet in the middle of
the field for the buck off.
They both try to be the
first one to kick it.
And the Pegasus is on defense.
She tries to keep the ball
from going in the goal
and passes it back to the
earth pony on her team.
Just give it a
little kick, Pinkie.
Oooh! I get it!
And all the unicorns have to
do is float these here baskets
around the outside
of the field
and catch as many balls as
possible for their team.
You two get
the idea?
Absolutely!
Oh, I don't know. That
ball moves pretty fast.
All right. Now let's see which
of you has what it takes.
Um...what do I do?
When the ball comes
towards you... catch it.
OK, just try your best, Pinkie.
I have been doing this
a lot longer than you.
HA-uhh.
Nice kick.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whee! Haha!
Great save, Fluttershy!
Coming your way, Pinkie!
Somersault, kick!
Hey, this game is easy!
Oh, it actually is
kind of fun.
Where did Pinkie Pie
learn to buck like that?
And Fluttershy's spinning
tail catch is pretty amazing!
Um... OK, well let's see
what the rest of you can do.
Now, don't expect to be able
to beat me twice in a row.
Well, hello there
Mr. Ball. Whee!
Hiyah!
Hurry along, butterflies,
before that ball
comes and hits you.
Nope. Um. OK, let's see
what the rest of you can do.
Nope.
Definitely, not.
Noooo.
Not a chance.
No.
Nope.
And...no. Uh, this didn't
go how I thought it would.
It sure didn't.
This game is a
whole lot more fun
than I thought
it would be.
It's exactly as much fun
as I thought it would be...
A WHOLE BUNCH!
Carrying my water,
my water, my water.
Carrying my water
on my shoulder pole.
SNAILS, LOOK OUT!
Amazing!
You should be more
careful with these.
You could lose them.
Hey, Snails? Can you float one
of those baskets over here?
Sure.
What do you want
me to do with it?
CATCH!
Anything else?
Wow, Snails, you're a
natural at Buckball.
It's a good thing, too. We
were running out of unicorns.
Do you think you'll be
ready to play with Applejack
and Rainbow Dash against
the Appleoosa team?
I guess I'll find out. Plus,
after I deliver this water,
I don't really have
anything else to do.
Well, Snails, with
you on the team,
Ponyville is one step closer
to crushing Appleoosa.
And after today,
it's pretty clear
who the other two
players should be.
What do you mean?
I thought you and Dash
were going to play.
Yeah. If you're not
crushing Appleoosa, who is?
Uh you two, obviously.
Um, you want us to
play Buckball
against Appleoosa
instead of you?
Mm hm.
That's un-credible.
Unbelievable and
incredible? Come on.
I can't explain it, but
you two are really good
at this game and if it
means beating Appleoosa,
I'll give either one of
you my spot on the team
quicker than Granny
Smith can core an apple.
Me too. I'd normally be so
pumped all of Ponyville
was counting on me to win,
I'd run right over
the competition,
but you still flew
rings around me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I
was just having fun.
Well, you can have all the
fun you want as long as it's
while you're beatin' the
hide off of Braeburn's team.
I do like fun.
Honestly, the game was
a little scary at first,
but once I got the hang of
it, I had a pretty good time.
Let's get this
party started!
All right, but if we really
wanna beat Appleoosa,
we're gonna have
to get serious.
Serious?
Serious how?
With serious practice!
Wow. This looks
pretty intense.
Well, duh. You two are
gonna be representing
all of Ponyville, and
more importantly...Us!
That's why before we leave
for Appleoosa tomorrow,
you two are gonna practice
just as hard as we would.
So, let's hop to it.
Snails already has
a head start on you!
OK. If you wanna win,
you've totally gotta
get this drill down.
I-I-I do?
It's all about ball control.
Ready? GO!
Come on! Faster! You don't
want Ponyville to lose
because you can't get
into high gear, do you?
Whoaaa.
All right, being able to
buck a ball into a goal
from any direction is the most
important thing in the game.
If you say so.
WHEEE! WOOO!
Keep it up! Just one miss'll
ruin the Apple Family's
Buckball reputation forever.
WHOA--What?
Whoops.
Come on! Push. Push! PUSH!
Come on now! Every shot
is for Sweet Apple Acres.
And me! And Dash!
And all of Ponyville!
Whoa. Ow.
Faster!
Whoa.
C'mon, now!
Whooaaa!
C'mon!
Keep it up!
Whooaaa!
C'MON!
What in the apple
happened to those two?
I don't know! They mopped
the field with us before.
All right! That's
it for today, y'all!
I thought practice was
supposed to make us better.
Maybe we just need
a little rest.
Or a whole lot of it.
Just be sure to get your heads
in the game before tomorrow.
All of Ponyville is
counting on a win.
I really don't want to let
Applejack and Rainbow Dash
down, or anypony else,
but after that practice, I'm
not feeling very confident.
Maybe we weren't that bad.
I guess I was hoping you
saw something I didn't.
I know our friends
want us to win,
but how can the whole
town be counting on us
if most ponies have never
even heard of Buckball?
I know! How can we
disappoint a pony
who doesn't even
know we have a team?
Or that we're going
to play Appleoosa.
Yeah, I don't think
we need to worry.
I'd be surprised
if anypony in this town
cares about this game at all.
Go Ponyville! Go
Ponyville! WIN! WIN! WIN!
Ponyville, Ponyville!
Way to go! You can do it!
Whoa. The whole
town really seems
to care about
this game a lot.
Woo-hoo, go Ponyville!
We kinda went around town and
talked up the team a little.
Yep. We wanted to
make sure you two knew
that all of Ponyville
was behind you.
Greaaaaat.
I hear the whole town's
already planning a parade
for when you get back
after whoopin' Appleoosa.
That should feel pretty good.
It should?
Totally! Just spend the
whole ride to Appleoosa
thinking about
everypony cheering
for the victorious
Ponyville Buckball Team.
I bet Princess Celestia even
comes to congratulate you.
If that doesn't get you in the
zone, I don't know what will.
I don't know what zone Rainbow
Dash is talking about,
but I'm pretty sure I don't
want to be in it. Do you?
Hey, you two are supposed
to be in the zone.
You see... The thing is...
Thinking about everpony...
thinking about us...
there's just no way...
THERE'S NO WAY THAT
WE CAN GET IN THE ZONE
BECAUSE THE ZONE SOUNDS
LIKE A HORRIBLE PLACE
SINCE WE ARE
TERRIBLE AT BUCKBALL
AND WE ARE GOING TO LOSE
AND LET EVERYPONY DOWN
AND WE DON'T WANT
TO PLAY ANYMORE!
I'm still OK with playing,
in case you were worried.
I don't get it.
They're naturals.
Why wouldn't they
want to play anymore?
Maybe us telling them how much
everypony was counting on them
messed them up somehow.
What? That's crazy talk.
Having ponies depend on you
is exactly what you need
to focus and...
Get serious and play hard and...
Get ready to totally smash
the competition and...
And none of that sounds like
Pinkie or Fluttershy, does it?
Guess not.
We got so wrapped up in
what's important to us,
we went and ruined what was
fun about the game for them.
What do we do now?
Pinkie? Fluttershy?
We know you're in here.
We've looked in every
other car on the train.
Maybe you need
to look again.
Yeah. Because we're totally
not in here.
And we're definitely
not in here
if you're going to try and make
us play against Appleoosa.
Or anypony else!
Oh, we're sorry
to let you down,
but it's better
to do it now
than during the game
against Appleoosa.
You don't have to play
We don't?
Nope. We're gonna
take your place,
so you don't have to
worry about that at all.
Why didn't you say so?
But.... We can't take on
Braeburn and his team
without any practice
so we need you to play
just one more time...
Against us.
Now I know we mixed
up the teams before,
but since Dash and I
really need the practice,
we'll play against
the two of you.
Oh, I don't know how much
practice you'll get
against us. We've been
playing just awful.
Don't worry about it.
Applejack and I just
need a little workout.
Yep. You two just
do your best.
I can do that.
Oooooh!
Ooooh!
Looks like you two
really do need practice.
Wheee!
If you need more practice,
we can keep going.
Yeah. I could do
this all day.
Uh, no thanks.
Playing against you two
is just as humiliating now
as it was when we weren't
trying to show you
how awesome you are.
Wait. What?
Finally!
You must have noticed how
you aren't bad anymore.
Oooh yeah. Weird.
But um, why were we
so terrible before?
I guess some ponies
thrive on pressure
and some ponies don't.
And even though we weren't
playing, we were treating
you like us which totally
stressed you out.
And that just sucked the fun
right out of the game for you.
And having fun is
what makes you
really, really,
really good.
But being good doesn't
matter if we're too afraid
of letting ponies down.
Yeah. What about all those
ponies back in Ponyville
counting on us to win.
I'm sure folks want
you to win,
but not if worrying about
it makes you miserable.
Winning's never worth that.
But how do we keep
from worrying about it?
You could do what I do
and not think about it.
Seriously, I don't think
about anything. Ever.
Hmm, works for me!
And with another bouncing
goal from Pinkie Pie,
the score is tied!
You guys are amazing!
Braeburn is really good!
So is that Pegasus. Oh I
don't know if we can win.
You know what I would do...
Not think about it?
...not think--
Oh. Yeah. That.
And as long as
you're having fun,
it doesn't matter
if you win or not.
Hee-hee! I think it's
more fun this way.
And Pinkie wins the buckoff.
But her shot's rejected!
Back to Braeburn, whose
kick's stopped by another
Fluttershy save.
Next point wins.
Lots of tense back
and forth here.
Fluttershy unleashes
her patented spin move.
But Braeburn's there to-
NO! It's Pinkie with
a somersault kick.
What a move! And that's
the game! Ponyville wins!
PONY-VILLE! PONY-VILLE!
Looks like you three
made quite an impression.
Well, cousin, I
have to admit,
your Ponyville team
played a pretty good game.
Ha! Good game? We bucked the
hooves right off of you.
Yep. You sure as shootin' did.
I'm gonna have to get real
serious about a strategy
for our rematch.
Oh, I wouldn't get too serious.
Yeah. Everypony knows the
secret to good Buckball
is just having fun!