Huh?
[gasp] Some poor creature's in
trouble. We have to help it!
Oooh! Listen to that suffering!
It must be in horrible agony!
Oh! It sounds like a herd
of injured Chimerae.
Or, it's Cerberus with
sniffle-itis in two of his heads
and kennel cough in his
third, or maybe it's-
Pinkie Pie..?
That's me! And a one, and a
two, and a I know what to do--
Ugh. At least no animal is
suffering, right Angel?
[out of tune tuba and
bagpipe sounds]
[nervous laugh]
Well, until now..
What is that thing?
It's called a Yovidophone.
It's from Yakyakistan, where
it's actually quite popular.
Is it supposed to
sound like that?
Not exactly. It's
known to produce
a fairly complicated
melodically rich and
harmonious tone.
Are you sure we're talking
about the same thing?
Phew! And that's with only
a few days of practice!
Can you believe it!?
Yes. Yes, I can.
I can honestly say I've
never heard anything
like it in my life.
Well, if you enjoyed listening
to my playing half as much
as I enjoyed playing my playing,
then I should totally play more.
That way we'll be even!
Oh, I don't think that's
necessary, Pinkie.
Please. Don't.
There's a chance I may
have missed a note or two
here or there, but I just
love playing so much!
[sigh] You.. complete me.
Well, I for one am glad
you're having so much
fun with your new hobby.
Uh-huh, sure.
And it's great that you're
learning a new skill and--
and you're just waiting
for me to finish talking
so you can start playing
again, aren't you?
No! But if you're done...
And-a one, and a two,
and-a I know what to do...
Oh. It's OK, she's gone.
Anypony else think that
sounded like an apple core
caught up in a pulp grinder?
Applesolutely..!
A-Absolutely.
OK, so maybe she
isn't good yet,
but she's our friend and
we should be supportive.
She just started playing. She's
bound to get better. Right?
Yeah, we just need to be
supportive of her practicing.
So the getting better part
happens as fast as possible.
Ah!
Agh!
Ah! You're absolutely
right, Spike.
Sometimes it is nice to
get out of the library
and be in the sun.
Especially when you take
the library with you.
[gasp] We need to do something about
Pinkie Pie's playing.
Like now!
Is it really that bad?
Does this answer
your question?
Uh, a trophy?
For second place. SECOND. PLACE.
All because of Pinkie's playing.
And I wanted to turn heads
with my new fall line,
but not like this! [sobbing]
And thanks to her fruit
blastin' melodies,
I've got an orchard full of
nothing but apple sauce,
and it ain't even
saucin' season!
And just look what her playing
did to poor Fluttershy..
Oh! So very tired. It
practically took me all night
to get the nursery
back to sleep..
I mean, I know we said we
should all be supportive,
but Pinkie's been
playing for moons now
and she's not
getting any better.
Yeah, if anything,
she's gotten worse!
OK, maybe we can just
pretend she's really good
and then I'll find
a spell that will--
Oh, no no no, we're not
going through that again!
Remember how well
it worked out
when you weren't
honest with Celestia
about her acting ability?
[groan] You're right. We'll just
have to tell Pinkie Pie
she's not very good
at the Yovidophone.
Well, there's no time
like the present.
Phew! That's weird.
I could have sworn this place
was packed a second ago.
Hey guys! Can I favor you all
with a tune? I take requests!
Actually, we do
have a request
and yeah, it involves
your Yovidophone.
You mean the thing I love more
than anything else in Equestria?
My sun, my moon, my
stars! My everything?
Oooh. Tell me! Tell
me! Tell me!
All right, in all honesty...
Uh... In all honesty,
Rarity has something to say.
Pinkie, Please! Listen
to Rainbow Dash!
Ugh. Fine. So Pinkie...
remember when we all
were shocked to discover
Princess Celestia wasn't
so good at acting?
Yeah, she was awful!
But that's kind of a
random thing to bring up.
I thought you wanted to talk
about my Yovidophone playing.
Well, it's ah, it's just... you
need to know the...Twilight?
[sigh] Pinkie, we
all support you,
but we're afraid you're just
not good at the Yovidophone
and none of us want
you to waste your time
on something you
can't do well.
Oh. Why didn't you
just say so?
Ah! We were all really
nervous to tell you.
Why? It's just a
silly instrument.
Well, lunch break's over,
gotta get back to the bakery.
Those apple turn-overs aren't
gonna apple themselves!
No more Yovidophone
playing for me!
Wow. She took that so much
better than I thought!
No more Yovidophone
playing for me...
And a one, and a two, and
I don't know what to do...
[sigh] Another beautiful
day in Ponyville.
Uh, Twilight, when was the
last time you saw Pinkie Pie?
Hmmm. Not since we told her to
stop playing the Yovidophone.
I'm still surprised with
how well she took it.
I don't think she took it as
well as you think she took it.
Top of the
morning to ya!
Is it morning? I
hadn't noticed.
That's not good.
Rainbow Dash: There you are!
We've been looking
all over for you!
It turns out Pinkie may not
have taken our critique
of her Yovidophone playing
in the spirit with
which it was intended.
I saw.
There's gotta be
something we can do.
I'm sure there is, Spike. We
just have to figure out what.
Ugh. I don't get it! So she's no
good at playing the Yovidophone.
What's the big deal?
There's soooo many other things
she's really good at doing!
Yeah. Not being able to play
the Yovidophone is nothing
compared to all the
things she can do well.
And that's exactly
what we'll show her!
I bet if we get her to
do the stuff she likes
and is good at doing, she'll
cheer right back up
and forget all about
the Yovidophone.
Hoo whee! That's a
great idea!
Let's get started. Apparently,
there's not a moment to lose!
Achoo!
So, I'm guessing
nopony had any success?
Huh. My party cannon
idea was a real dud.
Don't blame yourself.
None of us did any better.
Well, not to worry. I came up
with the perfect solution.
Instead of trying to remind
her what she's good at,
we'll remind her what she's best
at. And that's being our friend!
We're going to throw her a
Pinkie Pie appreciation party!
That's a
wonderful idea!
If anypony needs to know
how much she's appreciated,
it's Pinkie Pie!
We can get the
whole town involved,
just so she can see what a good
friend she is to everypony!
Then I hearby officially
declare today
"Pinkie Pie
Appreciation Day!"
Now this is perfection!
Yeah, if anything can
help Pinkie cheer up
and make her forget
about her Yovidophone,
this is definitely it!
It sure is. OK, who's
going to get her?
No need. Gummy's on it.
In fact, there he is now!
Uh, Gummy? You were supposed to
bring Pinkie Pie. What happened?
Is she still coming!?
Fluttershy, can you
understand what he's saying?
I could... if he
was talking.
Let me try something.
Gummy, where IS Pinkie Pie?
Maybe we should
just go and get her.
What in tarnation
is goin' on here?
This decor is dreadful!
And all of Pinkie's
stuff is... gone?
It is a puzzle.
Maud: Excuse me.
Oh, yes of course.
Um, Maud, can I
ask you a question?
You just did.
Well, can I ask
you a question?
You just did.
Agh! Fine! How about if
I ask you a-- wait.
Oh, for goodness
sakes. Maud!
All of your sister's
things are gone. Explain.
No, they're not.
They're right here.
Have you seen
Pinkie Pie?
Lots of times. I
grew up with her.
OK... let's try this
a different way.
Why did you pack up
all of Pinkie's things?
She asked me to.
What!?
Pinkie told me to
pack up her room
and take everything
to the rock farm.
WHAT!?
She said she
wouldn't need them
since she's moving
to Yakyakistan.
WHAT!?!?
Terribly sorry, Maud.
Must have misheard you.
It almost sounded like you said
Pinkie's moved to Yakyakistan..
[chuckling]
Uh, Rarity, she
did say that.
Uh... terribly sorry,
Applejack; must have
misheard you.
It almost sounded like
you said she did say that.
Maud, I don't understand. Why
would Pinkie leave Ponyville?
Yeah. Why would she wanna
go live with the Yaks?
She said without
the Yovidophone,
her life had
no meaning
and at least
in Yakyakistan,
she could listen to
the masters play.
She hoped that would give her
some semblance of happiness.
Well, no. Nononono!
That will not do.
I say we go to
Yakyakistan right now
and make her
come back home.
We can't just march up there
and tell Pinkie what to do.
But, we didn't even get
a chance to say goodbye.
Well, we may not be able
to go to Yakyakistan
and force her to come home,
but we could go say goodbye.
And if we happen to mention how
much her friendship means to us,
and how much we'd miss her
if she were gone forever,
and then she decided to come
back home on her own...
Then what are we waiting
around here for?
Let's get going
to Yakyakistan!
We're almost there.
Pinkie's got to be
around here somewhere.
But where?
[Beautiful Yovidophone music]
Is that..?
The music of the Yovidophone.
Are you sure? Because that
actually sounds kinda good.
Oh, I'm sure. Come on!
Huh. Not what I expected.
Shhhh!
Oh, sorry.
Shhh!
Tch. I said I was sorry!
Fluttershy: Ah! There she is!
Gimme another.
But pony already had
twenty-five ice--
[bang] I said GIVE ME ANOTHER!
Pardon me.
Excuse us.
Sorry!
I feel nothing.
Maybe we can
help with that.
Oh. Hey. What are
you guys doing here?
Just hear us out.
We respect your decision
to move to Yakyakistan.
But we just wanted to remind
you how much you mean to us,
and how much we'd miss you if
you decided to move here for--
Fine. I'll move
back to Ponyville.
Wow. That was a lot easier
than I thought. We're awesome!
Pinkie, what's wrong?
That's what's wrong.
I thought coming here and
listening to real
Yovidophone playing
would make me happy.
But it makes
me feel worse.
I'm never going to
sound like them.
Yovidophone Fan-pony
watch instrument
while Yigrid visit
little Yak's room?
Eh, if I can't play it, I
might as well do menial chores
for those who can.
OK, so Pinkie Pie is
obviously still miserable.
Oh. I can't bear to
see her like this.
Indeed. But what
else can we do?
Yeah, we've tried everything!
Maybe not! Look!
Hee hee!
Whoops! Sorry. I forgot what
an awful Yovidophoner I am.
Playing it makes you so happy!
[sigh] It sure does.
I mean it did.
Then you should never stop!
So say we all!
Absolutely!
But you were the ones
who told me to stop
because I wasn't good.
And we were wrong.
Playing makes
you happy.
And as long as it
makes you happy,
it doesn't matter
how good you are.
So get up there and show
these yaks how it's done!
[loud whisper] I don't
know if you've noticed,
but the audience are all yaks
and they kinda have "issues"
with things
that aren't perfect...
like my playing.
Pinkie Pie, you get up
on that stage and play.
If these Yaks don't like it,
they'll have to answer to us!
Well, OK. If you all say so...
Ahem. Ladies and gentle yaks!
Performing for her
very first time here,
let's give a big round
of stomps for... Pinkie Pie!
Ahem. Um, hi. So er.. any yaks
here from out of town?
OK. And a one, and a two and a
uh, kinda remember what to do...
Uh, I kinda wasn't
expecting this.
Me neither.
Oh! Pony play good set.
You think so? Even
though it wasn't perfect?
Yovidophone is
instrument of happiness.
Playing Yovidophone make pony
happy. Pony playing IS perfect!
Well, if that's the
case, let me play you
the song I just wrote
two seconds ago!
It's called: "I've Got the
Best, Most Supportive Friends
a Pony Could Ever
Ask For."
It's a working title.
And a one-
And a two-
And a you know what to do-