[sigh] I just wanted everything
to be perfect.
I mean, this was
a BIG DEAL!
But when Discord insists
on being involved...
Regardless of what
Spike might say,
that little dragon
BEGGED me to help.
And let me tell you, he
can cause plenty of chaos
all on his
purple lonesome!
I PRIDE myself on baking
under pressure but I just...
Oh, dear.
You'd think we'd be used to
stuff like this in Ponyville.
I still have
nightmares.
It seemed simple
when it started..
Oh! It's BEAUTIFUL!
Eeyup!
NOPE!
I'm not gonna EAT it!
Eat what?
What is it!
I wanna see!
Nope!
Why not?
Because you have
a big mouth.
ME?
I keep TONS
of secrets!
Like Fluttershy's
secret fear of clowns,
or that time I caught Twilight
sleeptrotting through town.
Oh, and did you know that
Octavia went on a date
with Bulk Biceps? Talk about
an odd couple! I heard that...
Oh. All right,
point taken.
But we're
pals, right?
COMRADES. AMIGOS!
COME ON!
BIG MAC IS GOING TO
PROPOSE TO SUGAR BELLE?
[echo] SUGAR BELLE!
SUGAR BELLE!
Of course, Big Mac asked ME
to help with his proposal;
I'm the most romantic
dragon I know.
Oh! It really is a curse
having infinite powers.
Everypony's
always asking you
to move a couch
or help with
a proposal.
Spill it!
EVERY detail!
Don't leave
anything out!
Agh! Do we have to
hear ALL the details?
Is that like, a
friend thing?
[sigh] Eyup.
I don't talk much so I
want to SHOW Sugar Belle
how committed
I am. First...
[gasp] You're making a picnic table
that matches the shelf
you made Sugar
Belle for her shop
when you had a
crush on her
and you're setting
up a romantic meal
overlooking Sweet
Apple Acres!?
Eyup!
Uh. How did you
figure that out?
If you were a
hopeless romantic,
you'd know that was the
only logical choice.
Then...
You painted apples to
leave around Ponyville
with little riddles
tied to the stem
that will lead her
up here to meet you?
Eyup.
Seriously?
Now...
-Yeah--
Oh, I know! You need a
giant rhino named Delores
who can knit a romantic
sweater for two!
Uh... Nope.
Come on! He needs food for
the picnic. That was a gimme.
I do not get
this game.
OK. You finish
your table...
I'll pick up whatever
you need to eat
and Discord will put
all the apples in place.
I will?
Eeyup!
From the Sugarcube Corner,
look for your next clue.
Red, delicious,
sweet like you.
Find it; you'll
know what to do...?
Ugh.
He should stick
to bucking apples.
Sugar Belle's
gonna love it!
I'll get the food.
How long will it take you
to place all the apples?
Are you sure you put
them in the right spots?
Those terrible
riddles on the apples
were VERY clear
on the location.
I'm sure that they
were placed properly.
I-I think. Maybe.
Does it matter?
Oh, OK fine! I'll
double check.
She didn't see the apple!
What are we gonna do!?
Well, we could just
GIVE it to her.
That's not romantic! She
needs to discover it.
Don't be such a
drama dragon.
I've precipitated liquid
cocoa on Equestria,
and herded long-limbed
Leporidae;
I can certainly make
a pony SEE an apple.
Hey Mrs. Cake. I need
to pick up a few things.
Oh, I'm afraid
you'll have to wait.
I'm a bit busy
at the moment!
Oh, is this sour
cream or sweet cream?
Oh, it's kind
of important...
Maybe I could take some
of these off your hooves?
NO! Those are for...
something important too!
All of them? There's...
one, two, three, four..
Twenty-ONE and
yes all of them.
Who needs twenty-one
desserts?
I can't tell you! It's
a secret. Come by later.
Later won't work!
Why not?
I can't tell you!
It's a secret.
Put the vanilla in
the... with the...
UGH! Did somepony
else bake these?
No. Why..?
No reason..
♪ [gentle music] ♪
Thank you!
These are perfect!
You know, if she's
too busy to read
the horribly
written clues..
Maybe you should
just tell her.
[gravelly voice]
Listen up, each of
you has a job to do.
Take a look at
your stems.
Well, tell me about it.
But regardless, go to your
designated location,
deliver your messages and
make me proud! Dismissed!
Oh. I just have to say Big
Mac is REALLY lucky
to have me as a friend.
[nervous voice] OK... One
down. Twenty to go.
THEN I can help you.
Maybe I can help YOU!
Delivering parchments
is my thing!
A little dragon
breath and FWOOSH!
We "deliver" each scroll
into each dessert!
Then you can
help me! Watch!
Whoa!
♪ TA-DA! ♪
Hurry, there's no
need to sneak,
the next apple is
at the boutique!
At Twilight's
castle take a right.
The next apple sits
in plain sight!
What in the blazes
is going on?
Discord..
Oh, are you finally finished?
I've been done for a while.
You know,
thinking back,
I probably could have
been clearer WHICH pony
to deliver the
messages to.
Ya think?
I sent them back to
Sweet Apple Acres.
Apples are TERRIBLE
at taking directions.
Couldn't even manage to
stay in one location.
Now bananas... oh ho, are
MUCH better at listening.
Sugar Belle:
What's going on?
Apples running
EVERYWHERE
and she didn't see the
poem to get to the hilltop!?
Getting her to the
hilltop is easy,
and not seeing the poems
is actually a blessing
when you think about it.
Why would you think
sending FLAMING messages
into my desserts would work!?
You've ruined all of them!
To be honest, I tasted
some and burning them
might have been
an improvement.
What? I NEVER!
-Big Mac: Spike?
-Oh! Hey there, Big Mac. I
bet you're wondering what-
Sugar Belle!
Big Mac?
DISCORD?
Mrs. Cake!
What did I do!?
Nothing.
I thought we were just
saying each other's names!
Well, I guess this
can't get any worse.
As the Lord of Chaos,
I'd advise against
saying things like that.
It's coming!
Save yourselves!
[monster voice]
SUGAR BELLE!
We have a bit of a reputation
for getting carried away.
Especially when
romance is involved. Heh.
But that WASN'T
the case with this.
We were just helping
Sugar Belle with HER plan.
And the last one should
just say, "Eyup."
Oo. Er. So you're saying you want
to put each one of those
inside a dessert?
Well, since Big Mac's plan to
send me a Hearts and Hooves Day
pie with a message
inside didn't go so well,
I thought it'd be
fun to do it right.
Aw! That's SO romantic!
He's a pony of few words;
I love that about him!
So I thought I'd use as
many words as possible
to propose to him!
All he has to say is...
EYUP! [giggle] I can't wait for you
to be a part of the family!
You three played
such a big part
in Big Mac and I
getting together.
I'm glad you could
help with this.
I-love-you-Big-Mac-Would-
you-like-to-spend-
the-rest-of-our-lives-together-
I-hope-you-say-eyup!
And each word has to
go into a dessert!?
That's... one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven...Whoa!
Twenty-one! I know!
Actually, it's twenty-two.
Mrs. Cake was kind
enough to help me bake
ALL the apple-flavored
treats I made
to get Big Mac to visit
me in my old shop,
but THAT one has
the invitation
for HIM to come HERE.
Oh, it's no bother! I
DO love a challenge!
Did I add the sugar to
this one or to that one?
I think I've seen her add sugar
to that bowl six times so far..
Now you three go
deliver that pie!
I have to get some flowers
to spruce the place up!
[gasp] Uh-oh! Spike and
Discord are outside.
If they figure out
what we're up to,
they'll spill the beans and I
want this to be a surprise!
I don't think they
suspect anything!
Why would they suspect
that we're holding
an invitation pie
and that Mrs. Cake is baking a
twenty-one-dessert proposal?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M GONNA
HAVE A SISTER-IN-LAW!
Echo: Sister-in-law!
Sister-in-law!
Shhh!
This is our shot to make
up for all the trouble
we caused when Big Mac first
asked Sugar Belle out!
We can't give away
the surprise!
You need to
play it cool!
Right, right.
Uh, how's this?
Better..?
Come on! Let's go
find your brother!
Screwdriver... nope.
Big Mac?
He ain't here!
Let's go!
Hold on..
That looks just
like the shelf
Big Mac made for
Sugar Belle! Weird...
Maybe we should
wait here for him.
He's bound to
show up soon!
Y'know, when I'm
lookin' for something,
Granny says it's best to
check the least likely place.
COME ON!
♪ [upbeat music] ♪
♪ [slow-paced music] ♪
Screwdriver!
BIG MAC!
♪ [peaceful music] ♪
Agh!
How is Sugar Belle supposed
to propose to Big Mac
if we can't even find him!?
Mrs. Cake isn't finished
yet. We still have time.
Y'know, when I'm
lookin' for somepony,
Granny says it's best to
just stay in one place.
Let's head back to
the farm and wait.
Big Mac is sure
to show up soon!
Well, don't just
stand there. Come on!
LOVE IS IN THE AIR!
Eyup.
Eeeeeeeeeyup.
♪ [gentle solo flute] ♪
Granny!
WHO GOES THERE?
Granny, have you
seen Big Mac?
Oh, hey there,
little dumpling.
I jut had the most
peculiar dream.
That's nice, Granny,
but we REALLY need to
find Big Mac, so...
It was about Grand
Pear, only it wasn't..
And we were in outer space
on some kinda mission
to explore strange
new worlds..
If we get stuck
listening to Granny,
we'll never
find Big Mac!
And Mud Briar was there,
bein' as logical as ever,
but his ears was
all pointy-like.
And then Discord showed up
and... well... you know,
he was pretty
much the same...
Once she gets going,
there's nothing in Equestria
that can stop her.
You sure about that?
-Spike?
-Oh, hey there,
Big Mac.
I bet you're
wondering what-
Sugar Belle!
Big Mac?
DISCORD?
Mrs. Cake!
What did I do!?
Nothing. I thought
we were just saying
each other's names!
Well, I guess this
can't get any worse.
As the Lord of Chaos,
I'd advise against
saying things like that.
It's coming!
Save yourselves!
[monster voice]
SUGAR BELLE!
DISCORD!?
Why does everypony
immediately assume
that this has something
to do with me?
I love you, you love me,
our love will grow
like an apple tree!
So let me ask,
will you marry me?
OK, but to be fair, the message
DID get to Sugar Belle.
♪♪
This whole story is
being twisted
to make it seem like
it was all my fault!
Which it wasn't!
Wait. So you two were
orchestrating a proposal?
That's what I
was doing!
Who are you
proposing to?
Apple Bloom: Discord!
ME?
I love you, I love
you, I love you!
So the messages that
were in the desserts...
..were Sugar Belle's
proposal to Big Mac
before Spike set
them on FIRE.
Oh! So, I'm not the only
one who messes things up,
am I, Mister High
and Mighty Dragon?
Hey! Those desserts
were ruined
way before I
ruined them!
They were NOT!
Well, I MAY have mixed up
a few ingredients...
It was such a rush!
You should both be VERY
disappointed in yourselves.
What about YOU and
your APPLE monster?
Yes, but you all
EXPECT that of me..
All we wanted to do was make
up for messing things up
the last time! Sugar Belle,
Big Mac, we're really-
Where'd they go?
OK, this time it
REALLY wasn't me!
I shouldn't have taken all
those desserts at once.
It's just, how can you say
no to such a sweet idea?
Oh! Ha! Sweet! Haha! I made a joke!
In retrospect, dragon
flame and baked goods
aren't the best combo.
We felt like it
was all our fault.
Except for the
apple monster.
THAT was Discord.
And Mrs. Cake messing
up those recipes..
And Spike burning the
messed up recipes. And--
The point is we
ALL felt bad
for ruining Big Mac and
Sugar Belle's proposals!
It was all green and THEN
Grand Pear looked at me
all dramatical and says "where
NOPONY has gone before"!
And WHOOSH! Away we flew!
Today was...
interesting.
Eyup.
You OK?
I...
I'm sorry, Sugar Belle.
I wanted everything
to go right today.
I wanted our love to be as
perfect as my parents' was
when they planted these
two trees together.
Instead, it turned
into a mess.
Just like when I
asked you out,
just like Hearts
and Hooves Day...
No matter how
hard I try,
I always seem to mess
up when it comes to you.
I think you've got
things backwards.
What do you mean?
From everything you told
me about your parents,
they had to deal with
things a lot tougher
than some burnt desserts
and an apple monster.
I... guess that's true.
This apple tree and pear
tree are stronger together.
They'll survive
whatever comes
because they don't
have to do it alone.
They BELONG together. Like
your parents. And like us.
Eyup.
Today was a disaster. But
today was also the last day
we're ever going to have
to do anything apart.
From here on out,
we'll be together.
And we'll make sure everything
always works out just right.
Big Mac will you...
Sugar Belle will you...
No, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
On three?
Sure. One.
Two.
Both: Will you marry me?
Both: Eyup!
We'll have to thank our
friends for messing up so bad
that they made it all
work out perfectly.
Well, we've ALL made up and
we're here for a do-over.
And this time, thanks to
me, we've got it right!
So, why don't you
two... you know.
Uh. I think they
did OK without us.
And THAT'S how we
were responsible
for the perfect proposal!
Heh. Or should I say PAIR-posal!
If we hadn't messed
up so bad...
It wouldn't have worked
out the way it did!
It's just
like baking.
Sometimes it's the mistakes
that help you discover
something truly
special.
And when all the planning
and grand gestures go wrong,
it reminds you the
most romantic things
are usually the simplest.
Which is what I knew all
along. You're welcome!
♪ [romantic music] ♪
It is my sincere
pleasure to say,
for my SECOND Apple
family wedding,
that I now pronounce
you husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride!
♪ [music swells] ♪
That's your cue!
♪ Happy marriage, happy apples!
Happy marriage, happy apples! ♪
DISCORD!
Oh, just let me HAVE this one!
♪ Happy marriage, happy apples!