The magical properties of this
spell will only have lasting
effects if you focus on--
No! Rainbow Dash!
How in Equestria does
that pony expect to pass
her History of the
Wonderbolts exam tomorrow
if she's wasting time flying?
I'm just gonna fly
right up to her
and tell her what I think
about her lackadaisical
approach to studying.
Won't she be surprised.
Surprise!
What? Huh?
How did you?
Please, Twilight.
That was the worst
sneak attack ever.
What? But--
I saw you giving me the
stink eye from the ground.
And heard you flying towards me
and muttering from a mile away.
Well, if you heard me
muttering then you must know
what I was muttering about.
Yeah, yeah, the
Wonderbolts History test.
No big deal.
No. Big Deal.
Really Big
Deal.
It's a test!
A test that will
determine if you can join
the newly formed
Wonderbolts Reserves.
And being part of the
Wonderbolts Reserves
means you'll have
the opportunity
to live your dream
as a Wonderbolt.
This is the most important
test of your life!
Twilight, not everypony
gets all freaked out
about tests like you.
I do not get all
freaked out about tests.
Uh, seriously?
Your freak-outs are so epic you
sing whole "freak-out" arias
about freaking out.
Fine. I may tend to take my
tests a little seriously.
But that doesn't mean you
shouldn't be studying for yours.
Oooh! And I know just the
pony who can help you!
Me!
This is going to
so much fun!
Sure. Fun.
Subtitles by YayPonies
http://yayponies.eu
Agh! Wha?
Hunh?
This is the most complete--
And ginormous!
book on the History
of the Wonderbolts.
OK, but how am I supposed
to get what's in there...
Into here?
With my handy dandy Study
Checklist, of course.
Of course.
First up: Reading
and Highlighting.
Reading and highlighting
is the foundation
of any good study method.
It allows the student to
hone in and boil down
what's really important,
separating the
good from the bad,
the wheat from the chaff,
getting to the crux of things.
Let's see what
you've got so far.
Um...
Huh?
By highlighting everything,
you don't really
separate the wheat
from the chaff.
Or the good from the bad.
Hey. I am not that tall!
OK, Rainbow.
Clearly reading and highlighting
is not your style of studying.
So let's move on to
the tried and true.
History Lecture!
Yes, Rainbow?
Is it snack time?
No.
Recess?
Can't we just watch the History
of the Wonderbolts movie?
No!
Now just get comfortable
and experience...
the magic of learning.
Ahem!
Prior to the great
Celestia/Luna Rift,
there was no need for the
Earth, Unicorn, Pegasi,
or E.U.P.--Guard.
But after Luna's banishment,
the Protective Pony
Platoons were formed.
On the anniversary of the
first Celestial Year of Peace,
a celebration was held.
Headed by General Firefly...
An elite team of aerial
performers were chosen
to help commemorate this
auspicious occasion.
The first performance
was so full of energy,
so highly charged, that magical
lightning showered down
on the crowd.
Everypony was so filled
with amazement and wonder
that General Firefly dubbed
them the Wonderbolts.
Rainbow Dash!
Can you repeat
any of my lesson?
History lecture?
Nope.
OK, Rainbow...Rainbow?
Rainbow Dash!
Here.
Let's move on to my favorite
style of learning: Flashcards.
Ooh! Does that mean
I'll learn in a flash?
One can only hope.
Colonel Purple Dart, the leader
of the Wonderbolts in the
4th Celestial Era was
known for his...
Wha?
Rainbow, did you
see what happened?
What? No! I was riveted by
your captivating cards.
Hmmmm.
After becoming the
official flying squadron
for Princess Celestia, she
honored them with...
Gotcha!
Got what?
The original Wonderbolts
lightning bolt insignia was...
Ah!
Rainbow Dash.
You could have hurt me.
With a spit wad? Really?
A spit wad to the eye would
have been no laughing matter.
Well, if you can horse
around like this,
then you clearly must
be ready for the test.
Clearly!
Well then, I guess you're
also ready for a...
pop quiz.
Bring it!
The initials E.U.P.
stand for what?
Ernie's Undercooked Pancakes.
The original aerial
team performed for...
Celestia's Cereal
Celebration.
The Wonderbolts were given their
name by this famous Pegasus.
Who is she?
Please don't say Colonel Waffle.
Hello? General
Blazing Donut Glaze.
So, did I ace it or what?
Or what.
You didn't get one
answer correct.
What? But how?
I don't know.
I've never heard
answers so wrong.
And so breakfast related.
If you had taken the
official test today...
My dreams of being
in the Wonderbolts Reserves
would've been totally crushed.
What am I gonna do?
I'm running out of time!
I don't know any
of this history!
I'm going to fail!
I'm gonna fail, I'm gonna
fail, I'm gonna fail.
And it's all your fault!
My fault?
I'm the one helping you.
Maybe your famous
"study methods"
aren't all they're
cracked up to be!
Eh, teacher?
Excuse me, I've used them
to study for many a test
and passed.
Yeah, right.
Do you know the name of the
premiere Wonderbolts choreographer?
Uh, well...
Commander Easy Glider.
Do you know how many Pegasi
flew in the original squad?
Um...
Seven!
Do you know Princess Celestia's
favorite flight pattern?
The Icaranian Sun Salutation.
See? I could
pass the test.
Fine.
Rub it in, why
don't you?
Besides, I don't see why I have
to take this lousy test anyway.
I've proven I'm one of
the best fliers around.
Knowing their origin and being
able to properly represent them
for all of Equestria
is just as important.
Yeah, right.
Some history buff like you
must've made that up
to bring us fliers down.
Knowing history actually
is beneficial, Rainbow.
Beneficial for eggheads.
Girls.
Well, this egghead knows
history and can fly.
Maybe I should
become a Wonderbolt.
Just 'cause you've got wings
doesn't mean you can fly.
Girls!
You're barely able to
just get off the ground.
Girls! Stop!
Now, is that any way
to talk to a friend?
Sorry.
Yeah, sorry.
Don't you have more
important things to do?
Like prepare Rainbow
for her big test?
I've tried everything,
Fluttershy,
but none of my study
methods work for her.
Well, no offense to your
teaching methods, Twilight,
but I think I may have
a way to help Rainbow.
Oh! Who's that?
Who's that?
Celestia and Luna, back
when they were happy.
Now what?
Gummy's an Earth Pony; Winona's
a Unicorn and Tank is a Pegasus.
They're the E.U.P.
helping to protect
the Princess.
How are you
getting all this?
Oh no!
Stop, stop, stop!
That was aw--
Awesome!
I give it three "Woo hoos"
Woo hoo, Woo hoo, Woo hoo!
And an extra "Woo"
for good measure.
Woo!
Well, I give it a
"Whoa, whoa, what?"
I'm totally confused and
I just want to go home.
Whoa! Hey!
Whoa, your woes,
there Woeful.
Someponies learn through
theatrical presentation.
But other ponies learn
through musical intervention.
♪ Back in ancient times there
were the Wonderbolts of old. ♪
♪ A General named Firefly.
Amazing and so bold. ♪
♪ She brought them all together.
Spreading unity in flight. ♪
♪ Performing at their very best.
With wonder and with might. ♪
♪ Next Admiral Fair Weather
and the Colonel Purple Dart. ♪
♪ Gave Wonderbolts a bit of
steel along with lots of heart ♪
♪ An Admiral named Fairy Flight,
a General called Flash. ♪
♪ Helped the bolts fly super
high with style and panache. ♪
♪ Commander Easy Glider was
the real cream of the crop. ♪
♪ For with her wicked moves the
Wonderbolts soared to the top. ♪
♪ Wonderbolts!
♪ Yeah, Wonderbolts!
♪ That is my rappin'
History of the Wonderbolts. ♪
So, do you get it?
Yes, Pinkie Pie!
♪ Wiki wiki wiki, General
this and Colonel that. ♪
♪ They're the Wonderbolts!
♪ something that
rhymes with that ♪
That was pretty terrible.
What? No. Really?
But I've got to
learn this stuff.
Now!
And I am just the
pony to help.
Rarity. You look ridiculous.
I'm going to ignore that comment
out of my desire to help you.
Good luck.
Get ready, Rainbow Dash,
for I am going to take you
on an historical
adventure in fashion.
I am now modeling the rather
unattractive, and frankly,
itchy original Wonderbolts'
flying costume.
Fortunately, thanks to the
vision of Flair de Mare,
the Wonderbolts ensemble
became more streamlined
in a wonderfully
breathable fabric.
Of course, there were
fashion hits and misses.
Just look at those
dreadful bell bottoms.
What were ponies thinking?
I don't know.
I bet General Flash
rocked these things.
Ah! Pinkie! You're real!
Of course I'm real.
I mean, I'm not the
real General Flash,
the 10th leader of
the Wonderbolts.
But I, Pinkie, am really real.
And I'm Admiral Fairy Flight,
from the 7th squadron.
And of course, you recognize
Commander Easy Glider.
And I'm sportin' some
sort of get-up worn
by Colonel Purple Dart.
Just look at us.
Look at us.
Look at me!
It's too much for my eyes!
Now, don't you fret, Rainbow.
This fashion show nonsense
wouldn't help me
learn nothin' either.
Really?
Well, what special study
trick do you have, AJ?
Who me?
Oh, I got nothin'.
Aw.
Why, I could tell you every
little thing there is to know
about the history of Apples.
But I picked all that up
over years in the field
as a labor of love.
How much time you got?
Twelve hours.
Oh, then you are up a creek.
Well, I think we should just go
back to old-fashioned studying.
What about our play?
Just look at these costumes.
Surely something resonates
with your inner Wonderbolt.
And Granny Smith discovered
the first Granny Smith
in Phillydelphia when
she was just a filly.
♪ Commander Easy Glider was
the real cream of the crop. ♪
Pinkie, stop rapping! That
isn't going to help Rainbow.
♪ Well, I suggest you put down
your silly cards of flash. ♪
♪ For I know that
they cannot help ♪
♪ our good friend
Rainbow Dash. ♪
Enough!
No rapping.
No cards.
No costumes.
No play.
And no apples!
I am never going
to pass this test.
Ever!
Just forget it.
Rainbow, I'm sorry
about all that.
We didn't mean to
overwhelm you.
It's OK. You were
just trying to help.
It's just too bad I'm too
dumb to learn anything.
You are not dumb.
You just learn differently.
If by "differently"
you mean "not at all"
then you're totally right.
No, that's totally wrong.
See? Wrong again.
I don't know anypony that's read
more Daring Do books than you.
Well, that's not gonna get
me into the Wonderbolts.
And your knowledge of
jokes and pranks
is only rivaled by Pinkie.
Great, my years of being
a class clown
prevented me from actually
learning how to learn.
That's not what I meant.
You're smart, creative,
inventive, and...Ugh!
Hey! I know you're upset,
but you don't need to--
Whoa!
I almost slammed into that.
I know!
You were jabbering on so
much, you didn't even notice.
But how did you notice?
You were listening and
talking to me the whole time.
Ha ha! You're such a rookie.
An experienced flyer like
me knows how to multi-task.
While you fly?
It's essential.
Yes, I was paying
attention to you,
but was also scanning the sky
and the ground for any problems.
Really?
Flying's not just flying.
In order to stay
safe in the sky,
I've got to hear and
see everything
down to the littlest detail.
For instance, I saw Apple Bloom,
Sweetie Belle and Scootaloo
come out of Sugar Cube Corner.
And from the looks of it,
they had carrot cupcakes
with sprinkles.
And I'm thinking Big Mac
sold a huge order of apples
to Filthy Rich because I heard
him give a very hearty, "Eeyup."
I always make note of
everything when I fly.
No biggie.
Oh my gosh!
What?
Gotta go!
Yeah, I get it.
I wouldn't want to hang out
with a loser like me either.
Thanks for meeting
me, everypony.
What is it, Twilight?
We have to help Rainbow Dash.
Yes, but how?
We've tried every
kind of studying.
My way, your way.
But we haven't tried
Rainbow Dash's way.
Hm, I'm intrigued.
OK, listen up, ponies;
here's the plan.
Hey, Rainbow.
Wanna go for a fly?
Sure.
Got nothin' better to do.
Didn't we just do this?
Yes but, like you said,
I'm such a newbie,
I need all the
practice I can get.
Yeah, well, I'm sure you'll
become a great flier in no time.
After all, you're
good at everything.
So what's going on?
Oh, nothing.
Just getting my
dreams crushed.
Uh,read any good books lately?
Just history books.
I'd tell you what
they're about,
but my brain is
as dry as a rock.
Speaking of rocks, did
you know Pinkie Pie
grew up on a rock farm?
Maybe I'll go work there,
since I have no other plans
for the rest of my life.
Oh, come on now, Rainbow.
You can't give up on your dream.
Seems my dream has
given up on me.
Maybe I'll learn
to shine shoes.
Sell hats.
Dig ditches.
Or maybe you'll be
a Wonderbolt.
Twilight, give it
up! I have.
So! What do you remember
about that flight?
Nothing important.
Except, after Luna was
banished to the moon,
Celestia needed
protective forces,
so Earth, Unicorn, and Pegasi
formed the E.U.P. Guard
of the Protective
Pony Platoons.
Yes?
And at the celebration of the
first Celestial Year of Peace,
an elite flying
squadron performed
headed by General Firefly
who later named the group
the Wonderbolts!
Uh huh?
Commander Easy Glider
established flight choreography
that is still used by
the Wonderbolts today.
Yes!
I know the history.
I know it all.
But how in Equestria
did that happen?
You learned it.
Yeah, I got that, but how?
Well, on our first flight, I
discovered that you catalogue
everything that happens all
around you when you're flying
without even thinking about it.
Don't you see?
I made use of your special
skills by enlisting everypony
to help you learn the
History of the Wonderbolts.
I, Princess Celestia, banish
you, Princess Luna to the moon.
No!
Earth!
Unicorn!
Pegasus!
E!
U!
P!
Eeyup.
Let us celebrate our first
Celestial Year of Peace.
Yeah. Let's party.
I'm General Firefly.
Gee, my costume is
itchy and unattractive.
But I'm gonna assemble
an awesome flying team.
I'll call them the Wonderbolts.
Streamlined style
by Flaire de Mare.
Admiral Fair Weather.
Colonel Purple Dart.
Admiral Fairy Flight.
General Flash.
Commander Easy Glider.
The History of the Wonderbolts.
Oh my gosh, oh my
gosh, oh my gosh!
Thank you!
Thank you all so much!
You're welcome.
But it all came from you.
You learn without
knowing you're learning.
Your main focus is flying,
but then your brain
is also absorbing lots of
other information.
It's actually
really brilliant.
Ha! I always knew
I was brilliant.
Rainbow Dash finally learned
the History of the Wonderbolts.
But she's not the only
pony that needed a lesson.
I needed to learn something
just as important.
One way of learning isn't
better than another.
After all, everypony is
unique and individual.
Ha ha! Whoo!