So sorry, Fluttershy.
I hate being late for our weekly get-together.
The usual!
But you will NOT BELIEVE what happened to me.
Is everything all right?
Oh, it's much more than all right.
I was on my way here,
wearing my latest hat creation...
...when who should stop me on the street?
But Photo Finish!
Photo Finish?
She is the most famous fashion
photographer in all of Equestria.
Anywho, she saw my hat and said
it was absolutely marvelous!
What a lovely compliment.
She was so impressed that she wants
to take some pictures of my shop...
...featuring some of my clothes!
That's wonderful.
Do you know what this could
mean for my fashion career?
Oh, Rarity, I'm so happy for you.
But I'm going to need somepony
fabulous to model for me.
Somepony with beauty.
Somepony with grace. Somepony...
...like you!
Oh, goodness. I don't know.
Oh, this is such a huge opportunity.
And it would mean so much to me.
I'm flattered, really.
Nopony is going to have
your elegance and poise.
-But...
-Nopony!
-There has to be somepony more quali...
-Please!
-Somepony more into fashion.
-Somepony more comfortable in the spotlight
-Please, please, PLEEEASE!
Oh, if it's that important to you,
of course I'll do it.
Oh, thankyouthankyouthankyouthankyou!
You are the best friend a pony could ever have!
What a wonderful way to spend an afternoon.
Isn't it?
Though I was so afraid you wouldn't agree
to model for me that I felt completely frazzled.
I think I feel a pimple coming on.
Oh! Only one solution!
The usual!
Hm... She's going to want to
see attitude and pizzazz.
A-a-attitude and, um... pizzazz.
More light! It has to catch
the sequins just so...
...or the whole outfit is just a disaster.
Oh, and the headdress need more feathers.
Pinkie Pie! More feathers!
And sequins! More sequins!
And more ribbon!
Oh no! Less ribbon.
No! More ribbon.
Oh, this hem is completely off.
PINCUSHION!
Thank you all for helping me.
I'm sorry to be so short with you,
but I'm... I'm just so nervous.
Ooh, doesn't that hurt?
Thick scales. Can't feel a thing.
And even if I could...
...there is no pain that would
keep me from assisting...
...the most beautiful creature in the world.
I'm gonna tell you two a secret.
But you have to promise not to tell anyone.
I promise.
Cross my heart and hope to fly,
Stick a cupcake in my eye.
I have a crush on Rarity!
We won't say a word!
Give me a break. Everypony
already knows how you...
Twilight! You promised Spike
you wouldn't say anything.
He trusts you. And losing a friend's trust
is the fastest way to lose a friend forever!
-But...
-FOREVER!
My lips are sealed.
Though I'm pretty sure Rarity is
gonna pick up on your feelings.
I, Photo Finish...
...have awwived.
Let me just say...
What an honor!
We begin...
...NOW!
Attitude and pizzazz!
Yes! Show Photo Finish something.
No!
Yeees.
ENOUGH!
She hardly took any pictures.
I'm so sorry. I tried my best.
Well, the headdress is too big for you
and cape had too much sparkle.
I can't believe I ever thought
*I* could impress *her*.
It seems that I, Photo Finish...
...have found a next fashion star
here in Ponyville.
Really?
Yes. Really.
And I, Photo Finish...
...am going to help her
to shine all over Eqvestria.
Tomorrow a photo shoot in ze park.
I go!
Did you hear that?
I am going to "shine all over Equestria".
Oh, Rarity. I was so worried
I'd ruined everything.
Oh, never. I knew you'd be perfect.
No, no, no, yes!
That is definitely the one.
Photo Finish is going to love it.
Everypony is going to love it!
Oh, I am so excited for you.
Just don't forget us little ponies when you become
the most famous designer in all of Equestria.
Never.
Put me down here.
Oh, nonononononono.
The model should be in something simple!
Something inspired by...
...the nature!
That's just what I was thinking.
Um... give me a moment and I'll, uh,
put a little something together.
Yes... that will not be necessary.
But... but... how are you going to help me...
..."shine across Equestria"...
...if I don't design something
new for these pictures?
I am not going to help you
shine across Equestria.
I am going to help *her* shine.
She is my star.
You! Go!
I can't, Rarity.
Oh, but you must, Fluttershy.
Photo Finish wants to make you a star.
This is the opportunity of a lifetime.
I know we were both hoping
it would be my lifetime...
...but nonetheless you can't
throw away this chance.
You must do this for me.
You must. You must! YOU MUST!
Floottershy!
It is time to make...
...the magics!
Oh, wunderbar!
You are like a delicate flower.
So much more alluring without
all those sparkles und feathers.
How'd it go? How'd it go?
It didn't.
Photo Finish wanted to work
with Fluttershy, not me.
Oh, Rarity. I'm so sorry.
Is there anything we can do?
I just vant to be alone right now.
You heard her. She vants to be... alone.
What? I didn't think she meant *alone* alone.
Too much blush.
Not enuf.
Too much.
Perfiect.
Oh, yes! Even her schneezes are gressful.
NOW GO!
How do you feel? Excited? Overjoyed?
Frilled beyond your wildest dreams?
N... nervous.
Nervous? Dun be ridiculous.
You're only facing a large crowd of ponies...
...who will be watching your every move
and silently judging you.
Your cue! Now go!
You can't let Rarity down.
You must do this. You must. You must. You must.
-So graceful.
-So lovely.
So perfect for my new advertisement.
It's Fluttershy!
Wow. Look how popular you are.
I'm so excited for you.
You must be having the best time ever.
Oh, yes. Best time ever...
Flootershy! I have been
looking for you everywhere.
We have the thing at the place.
I'll see you at the spa. Our usual time?
Of course! I can't wait to hear all about the...
..."thing" at the place.
I'm the one who should be
mobbed by strangers wherever I go.
Welcome to Carousel Boutique!
Is she still here? We heard Fluttershy was here.
Sorry. You just missed her.
But you're still in luck. I'm having
a huge sale of some of my best designs.
And you are...?
Rarity, of course.
Never heard of you.
Obviously I, Photo Finish,
am fwilled to have found her.
Photo Finish?
-She's a natural in front of the camera.
-Um...
Photo Finish?
I only need to point
and shoot and I capture...
...the magics!
Photo Finish, I'm so sorry to interrupt.
It's just that I'm running late.
How could I have forgotten?!
Your appearance at the ballet opening!
Everypony who is anypony will be there.
Oh, actually I'm supposed
to be meeting my friend...
WE GO!
My hooves are getting positively pruney,
I've been waiting here so long.
Obviously Fluttershy's just too busy with her
new *career* to spend time with her best friend.
I'm sure she just got tied up.
Of course she did.
She's a big bright shining star!
I wish that star would burn out.
Rarity! Fluttershy is your friend.
I know, I know.
And I should be happy for her, but instead I'm just...
...jealous!
Oh, please promise you won't
tell her I feel this way.
Please, please, pleasepleasePLEASE!
You have my word.
Losing a friend's trust is
the fastest way to lose a friend.
FOREVER!
Wow! You look great!
Fluttershy may be the one who's famous...
...but that doesn't mean
I have to stop looking fabulous.
Rarity! I'm so sorry I'm...
Oh no. She's already gone, isn't she?
Sorry.
Oh, I can't believe this.
I am so frustrated I could just scream.
Feel better?
No.
-Can I tell you something?
-Of course.
You promise not to tell Rarity?
I swear.
Pinkie Pie-swear?
Cross my heart and hope to fly,
Stick a cupcake in my AARGH!
I don't like being a model.
No, I hate being a model.
All this attention is awful, just awful.
And I'm only doing it because Rarity
told me I must. I must! I MUST!
I must...
Oh, really?
Well...
If you wanna know the truth, Rarity...
Oh, what were you about to say?
FOREVER!
Nothing!
I was just thinking.
If you really don't like being a model,
you could always quit.
Oh, no. I could never do such a thing.
Rarity would be devastated.
But Rarity told me...
Mmm... Juicy!
Oh, if only all these ponies
didn't like me so much.
Photo Finish wouldn't want me to model anymore.
She'd find somepony else with...
...the magic!
I guess you're right.
You're right.
You're right, you're fight, you're right!
It's Fluttershy!
Don't you see? On her own, Fluttershy
could never do something unattractive.
But if I used my magic to help her do something
unattractive on her next fashion show...
...no one would ever want her to model again.
And if Fluttershy no longer has to be a model,
Rarity will no longer have to be jealous of her.
And I'll no longer have to keep their secrets!
It's the perfect plan!
You can't tell anyone about it.
Promise me you won't tell anyone?
S-s-so you do promise or you don't?
Uh, yes!
Obviously, that's why I...
Zipped my mouth closed, then locked it with a key...
...then dug a hole, then buried the key...
...then built a house up top the hole
where I buried the key...
...then moved into the house atop the hole.
Obviously.
You really think it'll work?
They love you for being you.
So all I have to do is make you *not* be you.
Just leave it to me.
Guess it's time to see what all the fuss is about.
Oh no.
Get her off the stage!
She's an embarrassment to all things fashion!
I, Photo Finish, have made a terrible mistake!
Bravo!
I say bravo!
Bravo? Who could possibly say
bravo to that horrid display?
Such attitude! Such pizzazz!
She's invented an entirely
new kind of modeling! Bravo!
Who is saying these things?
It's her.
The unicorn in the gorgeous cape and headdress.
Now that is a pony, who clearly
knows a thing or two about fashion.
Well, if that fabulous pony likes it...
...then I do too! Bravo!
This is awful. Just awful!
Somehow I've become more popular than ever.
Oh, I'm so frustrated I could just kick something!
If only Rarity didn't want me to be a model so badly.
But Rarity...!
Fluttershy! Are you all right?
I'm great! I'm a super famous fashion model.
Why wouldn't I be great?
Because you ha...!
Out there on the runway,
everyone was turning on you and...
Oh... oh, Fluttershy. It's so awful.
I wanted them to.
You did?!
Of course she did! Because...!
I'm jealous!
I wanted all the attention.
And instead it was going to you.
I even started hoping that you would do something
silly so your modeling career would be over.
But then, when it started happening,
all I could think was...
...how could I want you to fail
at something you love so much?
But... Fluttershy doesn't... Ugh!
Love? Oh, Rarity. I hate being a model.
You do?
More than anything.
Then why did you keep doing it?
I was afraid if I quit, you'd be
mad at me for not wanting to...
..."shine all over Equestria".
And I thought if I told you how jealous I was
of your success, you'd think I was a terrible friend.
Never!
All this time!
If we just told each other the truth.
I promise never to keep my feelings in secret again.
Me too.
Cross my heart and hope to fly,
Stick a cupcake in my eye.
You were brilliant. Brilliant!
I've already got six photo shoots
lined up for tomorrow aloon.
I'm sorry, Photo Finish, but I don't think
I'll be able to make any of them.
Wat?
We go!
Vat has just happened?
Spike has a crush on Rarity!
And you were doing so well.
Now this is a wonderful way
to spend an afternoon.
Isn't it, though?
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"Being a good friend means
being able to keep a secret."
"But you should never be afraid to
share your true feelings with a good friend."
Did you get all that, Spike?
No. I did not.
I still can't believe you told someone
about my secret feelings for Rarity.
You're right. That was
wrong of me and I'm very sorry.
Apology accepted.
Now will you take down
my letter to Princess Celestia?
I would love to.
But... I'm a little busy at the moment.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000