I hope Shining Armor
and Princess Cadance
don't think it's too
soon for me
to come back to the Crystal
Empire for a visit.
But I just know Flurry Heart's
grown so much already.
I wonder if I'll
even recognize her.
She's the only baby
they have, Twilight.
I think it'll be pretty easy
to figure out who she is.
Mm.
Sorry, I know you want to visit
your niece as much as possible
and I'm excited to
see Sunburst again.
I just don't want
to fall behind
on my friendship
lessons back home.
Starlight, your work in
Ponyville isn't going anywhere.
Besides, I think we
all know you can learn
about friendship
anywhere, right Spike?
Spike? Who's Spike?
Uh you're
Spike, Spike.
And why are you
dressed like that?
Guys! You're blowing my cover.
How'd you even
know it was me?
Because you're YOU-- in
a coat, hat, and glasses.
Also, we're the
only ones here.
Right.
Spike, why do you
need a disguise?
The last time we came
to the Crystal Empire.
there was a lot going
on with the new baby
and the Crystalling,
but I still got
mobbed in the street.
I wouldn't say "mobbed."
And this is just
a family visit.
I wouldn't want the presence of
"Spike the Brave and Glorious"
to turn it into
some kind of circus.
We get it. The Crystal
Ponies adore you.
He did save the
Empire. Twice.
But still, I don't
think your presence
will turn our visit
into a circus.
Not if I find the right
disguise, it won't.
Regular subtitles
By YayPonies
We have crystal muffins!
https://yp1.yayponies.no/
Uh disguise or not, Spike, I
don't think you need to worry
about being mobbed.
Nopony's here.
It's like a ghost town.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
Yeah, this is weird.
I guess I don't need
the disguise after all.
It's Spike, the
Brave and Glorious!
He's come to save
us yet again!
Spike! Spike! Spike!
Save you from what?
Yeah. What's going on?
Why was everypony hiding?
It sure looks like Princess
Twilight and her pupil.
But how can we be sure?
We can't. Either one of them
could be the-- you know.
What if this isn't
the real Spike!?
EVERYPONY RUN!
Awww!
OK. Something strange
is definitely going on.
Ugh, you think?
Who goes there?
Um... you don't recognize
the Princess of Friendship?
Of course we recognize her.
But that doesn't
mean it's really her.
It's OK, guys.
They're with me.
And any friend of Spike
the Brave and Glorious
is a friend of the Crystal
Empire, am I right?
Huh. It does look like him.
Well, it would, wouldn't it?
I'm sorry, but we'll need to see
some proof of identification.
We'll take care of
things from here.
Oh Cadance, thank
goodness! What's going on?
We can explain, Twilly
if it really is you.
"Sunshine, Sunshine--"
"--Lady bugs awake! Clap your
hooves and do a little shake!"
It's OK, everypony.
It's her.
Of course it's her.
What's all this about?
A Changeling's been
spotted nearby.
A Changeling!?
That's not good.
No. It's not.
After Queen Chrysalis took
my place at our wedding
and invaded Canterlot
with her army of minions,
we're not taking any chances.
Changelings feed off of love,
and ever since Flurry
Heart's Crystalling,
the Empire is filled with more
love than anywhere in Equestria.
It's possible they've
come for the baby.
That's why we've posted the
extra guards and why we're--
--checking
everypony's identity.
I'm sorry for all of this.
Flurry Heart's really been
looking forward to seeing you.
Oh! She's gotten so big!
Starlight and I will do whatever
we can to help protect her.
To be honest, having you
here is already a big relief.
The Royal Guards were
wondering if Spike,
the Brave and Glorious,
would like to join in the
search for the Changeling.
Really?
Uh, I don't know if that's
such a good idea, Spike.
It sounds dangerous.
Come on, Twilight. This is
Spike the Brave and Glorious
you're talking to. Have you ever
known me to run from danger?
Ummmm...
He'll be safe with our guards.
Or will your guards
be safe with me?
Spike, the Brave and Glorious.
You've faced the evil
Changelings before.
What can you tell us?
Oh. Um. Well, they are
Changelings, so they can change.
Do you hear that? These monsters
can look like any of us,
so be on guard, guards.
Even more than normal.
And they could be anywhere.
So we should cover as
much ground as possible.
You, search that way!
And you search that way!
And I'll just search
here, I guess.
Not many places to hide.
Unless that rock
is a Changeling.
OK, "rock", how do I know
you're really a rock?
Hmm not talking, huh?
Well, you can't fool me.
Whoa!
Whew.
OK. Maybe it's time Spike
the Brave and Glorious
went back to, ah,
protect those guards.
Phew. Just my reflection.
Huh?
Ha hah! Hmm, just my
imagination, I guess.
AUGGGGGHHHH!
Ch-ch-ch-changeling!!
No, wait! Come back!
AAAAHHHHHH!
This is unexpected.
The ice is pretty slippery.
I wouldn't want you to
get hurt because of me.
You... saved me?
It's OK. I know you
don't want to be friends.
Wait!
I don't understand. Changelings
are supposed to be evil, right?
Evil? Oh, not me. All I've
ever wanted is a friend.
From the moment I first split
my egg in the nursery hive.
I was part of the
attack on Canterlot
during the Royal Wedding.
But I'd never seen true
friendship like that,
and I couldn't just steal
it and feed on its love.
I wanted to share it!
After that, I knew I couldn't
live with my kind anymore.
I set off looking for
love to share. But--
But what?
I'm starving!
And there's so much love in
the Crystal Empire right now.
It's what drew me here,
but it's driving me crazy!
That would be from
the Royal Crystalling.
It's pretty much a giant
outpouring of light and love
for a new baby.
Oh, sorry.
I'm just so hungry.
If I had a friend, maybe the
love we shared could sustain me,
but I don't think the Crystal
Ponies want to be friends.
What if I told you there was
somepony they respect and admire
so much, he could convince
them to give it a try?
If only that were true!
It is! I mean, I
am. It's ME! Spike!
Spike? The Brave and Glorious?
I'm sure you've heard of me.
No, but I was raised by
an evil queen. I'm Thorax.
I can't believe you
want to help me.
Why? Hasn't anypony ever
just been nice to you?
Sorry! Sorry! Kindness
like that kind of brings it out.
Do you still want
to be my friend?
Of course! And I am one
hundred percent sure
I can get the whole Crystal
Empire to be your friend too.
But, maybe I should just uh,
talk to them first.
What do you mean? Did
you see the Changeling?
Did you defeat
the evil creature?
Defeating a Changeling
would be brave,
but do you know what
would be glorious?
Defeating two Changelings?
Defeating all the Changelings?
Not having to fight
the Changeling at all
because I made
friends with him.
Ha hah! Oh. Wow. For a second
I thought you were serious!
Ha ha! Could you imagine?
Friends with a Changeling?
I am serious. He
wants to be friends.
Ha ha ha! Right!
Not only are you Spike
the Brave and Glorious,
you're also Spike
the Hilarious! Ha ha!
I'm not joking. The
Changeling is nice.
HA HA HA!
I'm sorry. But I don't
think it's funny.
The Changeling Queen,
Chrysalis, kidnapped Cadance
and cast a spell on me.
There's no such thing
as a nice Changeling.
You're right, Shining Armor.
Sorry. That was a... bad joke.
So? So! What did they say? How
many new friends do I have?
Well... it didn't go
exactly the way I thought.
Uh, I understand. Well,
thanks for trying.
I-I guess it's not surprising.
How can you expect ponies
who look like this.
To trust something
that looks like this?
I think I might know.
Spike, if you're done
searching for the Changeling,
Starlight and I
could use your help.
We're working on a protection
spell for Flurry Heart
and nopony takes
notes like you.
Uh actually, Twilight,
I wanted to introduce
you to my friend, um...
...Crystal! ...Hoof!
Crystal Hoof, my good
friend, Crystal Hoof.
Nice to meet you.
Oh. Well, it's nice to meet you
too. How do you know Spike?
Oh, Spike and I go way back--
--to the Equestria Games.
That's when we met. We've
been pen pals ever since.
Pen pals! Spike, you could have
been using my pen pal quill set!
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, I-I pretty much
only write to him
when you and Starlight
are studying.
I like to brag to all my
friends about my letters
from Spike the
Brave and Glorious.
Well, I'm sure Starlight
and I can manage,
if you want to spend
time with your friend.
Great! Crystal Hoof promised
to take me around the city.
Ha! That was amazing!
I told ya.
Crystal Hoof is nearly as
entertaining as Spike himself!
Ah! This place is everything
I've ever dreamed of.
But I can't keep
pretending
to be a Crystal
Pony forever, can I?
Relax, you're winning them over.
Pretty soon, nopony will care
that you're a Changeling.
Spike!
Twilight told me you
were off with a friend.
And any friend of Spike
the Brave and Glorious
is a friend of mine.
Oh she's so beautiful!
There's so much LOVE
around her. I-- I--
I, I'm so sorry!
I can't-can't stop.
Spike, get away
from the Changeling!
Wait! No! You
don't understand.
This Changeling replaced your
friend to get close to the baby.
What other explanation
could there be?
I don't know.
After it! Don't let
the Changeling escape!
I hope your friend is OK.
Yeah... me too.
Spike, you should
go find Crystal Hoof
while we hunt down
the Changeling.
I'm pretty sure he
doesn't want to see me.
Spread out! The Changeling
is probably still nearby.
Actually, I'm
pretty sure he ran
as far away from
here as possible.
But I bet I know where!
Thorax? Hello?
I just want to apologize. I
should have stood up for you.
Aw, come on, Thorax.
I know you're in here.
Leave me alone!
Um... little help?
Why do you think I would help
you? I'm an evil Changeling!
Because you're my friend.
I just wish I had
been one to you.
Ahhhhhhhhhh!
It's OK. I know it's hard.
Everyone in the Crystal
Empire loves you.
I couldn't ask you to
give that up for me.
You don't have to ask.
What are you going to do?
What I should have done
in the first place.
Let's move, move, move, move.
Have you checked there?
Look around that corner.
I know it's bad that
there's a Changeling around,
but is all this
really necessary?
If there's one Changeling,
there may well be a
whole army on the way.
True, but Starlight
has a point.
This is getting a
little out of hand.
I understand, but I don't
know what else we can do.
I do!
Spike! What are you doing?
Get away from that thing!
No. He's not a thing. His name
is Thorax. And he's my friend.
♪ Would you say I'm a
hero, glorious and brave ♪
♪ If I told you something
you wouldn't believe? ♪
♪ That sometimes I'm scared
and I can make mistakes ♪
♪ And I'm not so
heroic, it seems ♪
♪ But if day can turn to night ♪
♪ And the darkness
turn to light ♪
♪ Then why can't we imagine
a Changeling can change? ♪
♪ No two ponies are
exactly the same ♪
♪ No two snowflakes ever
match their design ♪
♪ And I thought I was strong,
but I was nothing but wrong, ♪
♪ When I forgot to be
friendly and kind. ♪
♪ But if day can turn to night ♪
♪ And the darkness
turn to light ♪
♪ Then why can't we imagine
a Changeling can change? ♪
♪ Would you say I'm a
hero, glorious and brave ♪
♪ If I told you something
you wouldn't believe? ♪
♪ This Changeling it
seems, knows the real me. ♪
♪ And would stay by my
side till the end. ♪
♪ So if day can turn to night ♪
♪ And the darkness
turn to light ♪
♪ Then why can't we imagine? ♪
♪ Just why can't we imagine,
then why can't we imagine ♪
♪ the Changeling can change? ♪
Spike, I'm so
proud of you.
You are?
Of course! You're a celebrity
here in the Crystal Empire
and you just risked
all of it for a friend.
I can't imagine anything
more brave than that.
As the Princess of Friendship,
I try to set an example
for all of Equestria.
But today, it was Spike who
taught me that a new friend
can come from anywhere.
I guess everypony
still has things to learn
about friendship, even me.
And if Spike says Thorax is his
friend, then he's my friend too.
Thank you.
On behalf of the Crystal Empire,
I would like to extend my hoof
in friendship and I am
sure all of my subjects
are eager to do the same.
Welcome to the Crystal
Empire, Thorax.
I'm sorry we didn't take the
time to get to know you.
Maybe we can change that now.
That'd be so amazing! I want
to know all about friendship.
And maybe one day I can
take that knowledge back
to the Changeling Kingdom.
If my kind learned how to
create love for one another,
maybe they wouldn't have
to take it from others!
To Spike the Brave and Glorious!
Looks like you were
right after all.
Right about what?
Friendship lessons
can happen anywhere.