News from Northern Equestria!
Uh... your highness.
Yes?
I am simply to tell you that...
it has returned.
Find Princess Cadance and Shining Armor.
Yes, your highness.
My dearest Twilight,
you must come to Canterlot at once.
Season 3 | Episode 01
The Crystal Empire, Part 1
Subbed and Synced by GrayJeager
Fr.Jeager@Gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://www.youtube.com/user/GhxBronie
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
Where are all my quills?
No, no, no, no, no... ugh!
I need the Magical Compendium
volumes 1 to 36! Where is it?!
Flash cards!
I should make some flash cards.
Spike, I'm gonna need you to quiz me.
On everything.
Everything I've ever learned. Ever.
That isn't gonna be enough cards.
Twilight, calm down.
It's just a test!
Just a test?
JUST A TEST?!
Princess Celestia wants
to give me some kind of exam
and you're trying to tell me to calm down
because... it's just a test?!
Uh... yes?
I'd say she's handling things
pretty well, considering.
Are you sure you don't want me
to go as well?
Yes.
Princess Cadance and Shining Armor
are already there.
The others will be joining them soon.
The empire's magic is powerful.
It cannot fall again, my sister.
She will succeed at her task.
And when she does,
we'll know she is that much closer
to being ready.
Trust me, little sister.
You wanted to see me?
To give me a test?
I brought my own quills.
And plenty of paper to show my work.
Sorry, sorry!
This is a different kind of test.
The Crystal Empire has returned.
The Crystal Empire?
I'm sorry, I thought I'd studied.
I don't think there's anything
in any of my books--
There wouldn't be.
Few remember it ever existed at all.
Even my knowledge of
the empire is limited.
What I do know is that
it contains a powerful magic.
One thousand years ago,
King Sombra, a unicorn
whose heart was black as night,
took over the Crystal Empire.
He was ultimately overthrown,
turned to shadow and banished
to the ice of the arctic north.
But not before he was able to
put a curse upon the empire.
A curse that caused it
to vanish into thin air.
If the empire is filled with
hope and love,
those things are reflected
across all of Equestria.
If hatred and fear take hold...
Which is why I need your help
finding a way to protect it.
You want me to help protect
an entire empire?
It is, as I said, a different kind of test.
But one I'm certain you will pass.
How do I begin?
By joining Princess Cadance and
Shining Armor in the Crystal Empire.
My brother is there?
He is. And your Ponyville friends
will join you there as well.
I have every confidence
you will succeed.
And when you do,
I'll know you are ready to move on
to the next level of your studies.
But what if I fail?
You won't.
But what if--
But Twilight,
in the end, it must be you
and you alone
who ultimately assists
Princess Cadance and Shining Armor
in doing what needs to be done
to protect the empire.
Do you understand?
Then go. There is no time to lose.
Ah! Twilight! That was fast!
Let me guess, you got a perfect score?
A minus?
B plus?
Twilight! Did you... fail?
I was prepared to do my best,
Thought I could handle any test
For I can do so many tricks,
But I wasn't prepared for this
Levitation would have been a breeze
Facts and figures I recite with ease
The square root
of five hundred and forty-six
is twenty-three point three six six six
four two eight nine one zero nine.
She is correct!
I could ace a quiz on friendship's bliss
But I wasn't prepared for this
Will I fail, or will I pass?
I can't be sure...
She can't be sure...
My mind is sharp, my skills intact
My heart is pure...
Her heart is pure...
Oh, I've taken my share of licks
I've made it through the thin and thick
- But no I wasn't
- Oh no, she wasn't
No I wasn't prepared for this!
Uh, prepared for what exactly?
Twilight!
Did you pass?
Are we gonna celebrate
your awesomeness with Princess Celestia?
Not quite.
We're going to the Crystal Empire!
Ha! And you all made fun of me
for packing so many scarves.
I didn't say a word.
Twilight!
Shining Armor?
Twilie! You made it.
We better get moving.
There are things out here we really
don't want to run into after dark.
What kind of things?
Let's just say the empire...
isn't the only thing that's returned.
Something keeps trying to get in!
We think it's the unicorn king
who originally cursed the place.
But Princess Celestia said I was being sent
here to find a way to protect the empire!
If King Sombra can't get in,
then it must already be protected.
Th-That's one of the things, isn't it?!
We have to get to
the Crystal Empire. Now!
Go, go!
Almost there.
Everypony okay?
Oh no, Shining Armor,
your horn!
Sparklriffic!
It's gorgeous!
Absolutely gorgeous!
There are no words!
Focus, Rarity.
We're here to help Twilight.
Not admire the scenery.
I don't see what the big deal is.
Just looks like another old castle to me.
Another old...!
Have you lost your mind?!
Look at the magn--
Very funny.
Cadance!
Sunshine, sunshine, ladybugs awake,
clap your hooves and do a little shake!
One of these days,
we need to get together
when the fate of Equestria
isn't hanging in the balance.
Are you okay?
Cadance has been able to use her magic
to spread love and light.
That seems to be what is protecting it.
But she hasn't slept, barely eats.
I want to help her, but my protection spell
has been countered by King Sombra.
It's alright Shining Armor, I'm fine.
She's not fine.
She can't go on like this forever.
And if her magic were to fade,
you saw what's out there
waiting for that to happen.
That's why we're here.
Why we're all here.
With Cadance putting all her strength
into keeping her spell going,
and me trying to keep an eye
on signs of trouble in the arctic,
we haven't been able to gather
much information from the Crystal Ponies.
Crystal Ponies?!
There are Crystal Ponies?!
Please, continue.
But we have to believe one of them
knows how we can protect the empire,
without having to use
Cadance's magic.
A research paper!
That must be part of my test!
To gather information from the
crystal ponies and deliver it to you!
This is gonna be great!
I love research papers!
Yeah, who doesn't?
Ohohoh! Lemme guess!
Is it Spike?!
No no, Fluttershy! Rarity?
Don't worry, big brother.
I'm really good at this sort of thing.
Are you sure? Absolutely sure?
I'm sorry. I wish I could help you.
But I can't seem to remember anything
before King Sombra came to power.
And I don't want to remember anything
about the time he ruled over us.
King Sombra's spell must be
why their coats aren't... crystally.
Have we really been gone
a thousand years?
Yes.
It feels like it was just yesterday.
If you think of anything,
even the smallest thing...
Of course.
That was a total bust.
Maybe the others are having better luck.
A way to protect the empire!
You know anything about it or what?!
I wish I could help you. Really.
Come on! You gotta know something!
But... I don't have any information.
Oh, um. Excuse me!
Oh, hello!
I was just wondering...
Oh, oh that's okay.
You all look really busy...
Time to gather some intel!
It just feels like something is missing.
I know.
It looks the same, but...
it doesn't feel the same.
Because it isn't!
A spy!
A spy?!
How did they know?
Ah! Must have noticed
my night vision goggles.
Ooh! Night vision-ey!
And when you flip your mane,
it simply must create a rainbow of color.
Wouldn't I look just magnificent?
So sparkly!
I got nothing so far.
Me neither.
My cover has been blown.
I repeat, my cover has been blown!
Ooookay.
Sorry, Twilight,
these crystal ponies seem to have
some kinda collective amnesia or somethin'.
Only thing I was able to get out of 'em
was somethin' about a library.
A library?
Why didn't you say so?!
Uh... thought I just did.
I just... I don't even know what to...
There are no words.
May I help you?
Yes. We're looking for a book.
We have plenty of those.
You do. You really do!
We're lookin' for a history book.
Somethin' that may tells us how
the empire might've protected itself
from danger back in the day.
Yes, of course.
History, history...
Ah, yes!
Which is where, exactly?
I... I can't seem to remember.
I'm not sure I actually work here.
We'll just take a look around.
I'm sure we can find it on our own.
Let me know if you find anything.
I like her!
Anyone else startin' to think
this is a lost cause?
No, no, no, no,
no...
YES!
History of the Crystal Empire.
I just hope it has
the answers we need.
A 'Crystal Fair'.
According to this book,
it was established by their first queen,
and became their
most important tradition.
The fair was held every year to
renew the spirit of love
and unity in the empire
so they could protect it from harm.
My friends and I could put it together.
Everything we need to know is in the book!
That sounds pretty promising.
We'll get started right away.
Come on, Spike.
We've got a Crystal Fair to put together!
Princess Cadance needs our help,
Her magic will not last forever
I think we can do it,
But we need to work together
We have to get this right,
Yes we have to make them see
We can save the Crystal Ponies
with their history
It says that they like jousting
They flew a flag of many hues
Made sweets with crystal berries
They had a petting zoo with tiny ewes
Oh we have to get this right,
Yes we have to make them see
We can save the Crystal Ponies
with their history
There was a crystal flugelhorn
That everypony liked to play
And the Crystal Kingdom anthem
Can you learn it in a day?
Oh we have to get this right,
Yes we have to make them see
We can save the Crystal Ponies
With their history
It looks amazing!
I don't know how
I could have done this without you!
One last check to make sure
everything is in place,
and then the festivities can begin!
What's this thing for?
The last page of the book mentioned
a Crystal Heart as the fair's centerpiece.
So I used my magic to cut one
out of a crystal block.
Nice work, Twi.
Think we're ready to get
this fair up and runnin'.
Hear ye, hear--
My bad.
Hear ye, hear ye.
Princess Cadance
and Prince Shining Armor
do cordially
invite you to attend
the Crystal Fair!
Come on in, y'all.
Got food and drinks thataway,
games and crafts are thataway,
Crystal Heart to the back
near the Princess.
We totally nailed it, right?
Must be feeling a lot of love
and unity about now!
Gonna have some grub, huh?
What are you picking?
Crystal Empire berry pie?
Maybe some crystal corn-on-the-cob!
What is with these ponies?!
Seeing all of this, I feel like
I'm starting to remember.
Remember things from before the king.
Me too.
The Crystal Heart!
Do you think they really have it?
Of course we have it!
Can't have a Crystal Fair
without the Crystal Heart, right?
Of course you can't.
The whole purpose of the Crystal Fair
is to lift the spirits of the Crystal Ponies,
so the light within them
can power the Crystal Heart,
so that the empire can be protected!
I do work at a library!
What's that about
'powering the heart'?
I just can't believe you found it.
King Sombra said he'd hidden it away,
where we would never see it again!
I only hope it will still be
as powerful after all these years!
Mm, funnelcake!
Why did you...?
I think we may have a problem!
I didn't know it was an actual relic!
The book didn't mention anything about
the Crystal Ponies powering the Heart!
There was a page missing...
how did I not notice?!
It's alright, Twilight.
Twilie...