Oh! I just stopped
by to thank you
for letting me borrow your
Daring Do books! I love them.
Wait till you get to "Daring Do
and the Riddle of the Sphinx!"
This is actually my
second time through!
I've read them all,
from "Daring Do and
the Sapphire Statue"
to "Daring Do and the
Fallen Idol!"
Fallen Idol? That's
not in the series.
Oh, it just came
out last week...
Maybe that's why you
haven't heard of it?
No way Daring Do's
biggest fan, ME,
would miss a
book coming out!
Besides, A.K. Yearling
always sends me a copy!
Well, I'm happy to
let you borrow mine
until yours arrives.
"The true story of
the thieving fraud
known as Daring
Do?" WHAT?
Why would A.K. Yearling
write that about herself!?
Oh! It looks
like she didn't.
This book says it's by
Groom Q. Q. Martingale.
Who?
I guess he's a
new writer.
A BAD one.
"The only thing worse
than Daring Do's
destruction of temples
is her cruelty to the
mild-mannered Dr. Caballeron!?"
It was written from
his point of view...
I figured it was
an artistic choice.
More like a disaster!
Listen: "Daring Do isn't
just a fictional character
from over-the-top
adventure stories.
I've met her, and she
is a real, live pony!"
That's supposed
to be a secret!
We're the only ones
who know Daring Do
is really A.K.
Yearling in disguise.
But if other ponies
read this book,
how long will it take
them to figure that out?
We have to go
warn her!
FLUTTERSHY!
Hmm? Oh. Sorry.
A.K. Yearling is
signing all her books
at the bookstore today.
We can warn her about
what's going on!
Don't you think you should
read Martingale's book first?
Just to hear both
sides of the story?
Uh, why? The only true
thing in that pack of LIES
is that Daring Do is REAL.
There's also a
lot of insight
into Dr. Caballeron's
life choices.
Did you know he's actually
a history professor
and amateur bird watcher?
Are you serious
right now!?
A random writer TRASHES our
friend and exposes her secret
and you wanna
talk ABOUT BIRDS!?
[whispering] Also spider cruelty.
WHAT?
You have to
admit Daring Do
wrecks a lot of spider
webs in her adventures.
In order to save precious
artifacts from the bad guy,
who you seem to have
forgotten is Dr. Caballeron!
Are you sure you read
the same series I did?
♪♪
Well, at least A.K.
Yearling's TRUE fans
know Martingale's
book is bogus.
I'm not sure those
are all fans...
♪♪
Why didn't your books
say Daring Do was real!?
This changes everything!
And why do you only write
about her good side?
Is she bribing you?
On page 531 it says
Daring Do kicks puppies!
She does!?
What!? No! Look,
are any of you here
for my actual
book signing?
Nuh-uh. No.
Uh-uh. Frankly, I don't even know
how you can call it fiction
if it's all real. You're as
much of a fake as Daring Do!
Uh.. I guess we're a little
late to warn you
about the new book, huh?
[sigh] I always feared
that someday
everypony would learn
Daring Do was real.
But why? Aren't you
proud of your adventures?
Of course! But I'm not
in it for the fame.
The stories just seemed
too good to keep to myself.
I wish I knew who this
"Martingale" author was,
and why he's determined to
ruin my character... and me!
Maybe we can ask him.
No way! He's doing a
signing across the street!?
You'd better
go without me.
I can't risk the
chance Martingale
might recognize
me as Daring Do.
♪♪
Oops! Um, sorry.
Excuse us!
[gasp] That's not Martingale!
It's Doctor Caballeron
in disguise!
Now it all makes sense!
Daring Do's arch nemesis
created a fake "author"
self so he can write books
that make him sound like
a hero! Who does that!?
Uh, A.K. Yearling?
This is totally
different.
Well, well, well. Up to
your old tricks again, huh?
Just like in Somnambula!
Spreading lies to make
Daring Do look bad!
Would you sign our book?
I am just a simple author,
telling it like it is.
Who should I make
it out to?
Fluttershy, with two T's.
Agh! We know who you
REALLY are!
And unless you want us
to tell all of THEM,
you'd better answer
some questions!
I'm afraid that's all
we have time for today.
Awwww!
But please! Take a free copy
of my book on your way out!
Yeah!
We aren't going to let you get
away with this, Caballeron!
Get away with what? I am merely
telling my side of the story.
You mean lying!
You think everything in A.K.
Yearling's books are true?
In "Daring Do and
the Quetzal's Quest"
she states that the
Fangthorn Flowers are red.
In fact, they are blue!
It's true. They are.
Pfft! That sounds like more
of an editor's mistake.
Still, if that is wrong...
is it not possible that
other, bigger things are too?
Take a look! It's
in my book.
But I don't have to
take YOUR word for it!
C'mon, Fluttershy!
Is something wrong?
It is terrible being
misunderstood.
It is true, in the past
I have not been as nice
to Daring Do as I should.
But I have my reasons!
Want to talk about
what happened?
My team and I were
only ever interested
in researching
artifacts.
And taking them
to our museum
where other ponies
could study them.
♪♪
But Daring Do always
seemed to get there first,
with her own plans.
I offered to team up with
her, but she refused.
She had her own ideas of
where the treasures belonged.
Daring Do did have
a lot of artifacts
on her shelves at home...
But didn't you try to sell
them to the highest bidder?
Only because I
had to.
Since Daring Do kept
taking our artifacts,
our museum closed!
We were desperate for
money to keep it open.
She does destroy a
lot of ancient sites..
Not to mention the homes of
the animals that live there.
And I felt it was MY
duty to tell the world.
Thank you for listening
and understanding, Ms...?
Fluttershy. Two T's.
And I am Dr.
Caballeron.
Martingale is merely a nom
de plume to build my brand.
You know, my team could
use an insightful Pegasus
like you, Fluttershy.
Have you ever thought
of being.. an adventurer?
Who, me?
♪♪
Finally! What
took you so long?
I decided to find
out which author
is really telling
the truth,
so I joined Dr. C's
Tenochtitlan expedition!
♪ [ominous music] ♪
Say WHAAAT?
So Daring Do doesn't
kick puppies?
That was ONE time.
Accidentally!
A.K.! You have to help me!
Groom Q.Q. Martingale is
really Dr. Caballeron,
and he has Fluttershy!
The book thing was
his new plan
to ruin Daring
Do's reputation.
AND he's trying to make
my friend a criminal!
They're off to
Tenochtitlan right now!
He must be after the Truth
Talisman of Tonatiuh!
It requires the wings of
a Pegasus to retrieve it!
That's gotta be why
Caballeron tricked Fluttershy
into joining his gang!
Then it's up to
us to stop him!
Whoa...!
♪♪
Watch where you put
your hooves, everypony.
We do not want to disturb the
fragile jungle ecosystem.
Oh, that's so thoughtful.
Yes, unlike Daring Do,
who slashes plants aside
with her cruel machete.
Thank you.
Fool! Don't you
know that's poison?
I don't want you to get
hurt, my friend. Heh heh.
But I'm hungry.
Oh, I can help
with that! Here!
You are...willing
to share?
Of course! That's
part of the fun
of having an adventure
with friends!
♪ [tense music] ♪
♪♪
Fluttershy! Run!
These ferocious beasts
want to eat us for dinner!
That's a common
misconception.
Have you ever tried
just talking to them?
That's crazy! You
are on your own!
She's a goner.
I can't watch!
We're very sorry for
coming into your territory.
But we're just
passing through.
How...did you do that?
Everycreature likes
to be listened to.
You just need to take the
time to understand them.
You are more talented
than I realized..
Thanks. I'm having the
best time with you all!
Fluttershy must be
having the WORST time
with Caballeron's goons.
We need to catch
up to them
before they reach
the truth talisman!
Why? What's so
special about it?
It has the power to
make the pony holding it
tell the truth.
But Caballeron only
wants it because
it's made of
solid gold.
He'll melt it down and
use it to get rich.
So if this talisman
is so important,
why didn't you
already save it?
You said only a Pegasus
can get it, right?
Yes! But the temple traps
are far too dangerous
to face without a map.
And maybe even with one!
♪ [military snare drum] ♪
Boss, how about we
take the shortcut?
How about you
be quiet!
Uh, I mean... no
thank you, Biff.
Let's just
follow the map.
Aw. I'm supposed to be Dr.
C's second in command.
But he never
listens to me.
Well, keep trying!
I believe in you.
♪♪
At last!
Now we simply have to
wait for the sun
to reach its
highest point.
And our path will
be revealed.
♪♪
Withers. Don't. Move.
Ah ha ha!
There they are!
We can catch them before
they enter the temple!
Gah!
Get back, Rainbow
Dash! It's Ahuizotl-
Wha? Gah!
Daring Do. My old nemesis.
You may have outsmarted
my jungle cats,
but you cannot escape ME!
Ugh! We didn't see any cats!
We're just here to
rescue Fluttershy!
Hmm. It must be a coincidence
that only a Pegasus
can retrieve
Tonatiuh's treasure...
And there are
two of you here.
♪♪
♪ [adventurous music] ♪
Quickly! Before the sun
moves and it closes!
♪♪
Phew! That was
cutting it close.
And without a map, we'll have
to guess which way to go.
Oh, no! I knew
the truth talisman
could not be moved by
magic, but I never realized
we'd have to FLY
to retrieve it!
Our journey has
been for nothing!
Don't be upset,
I can get it.
Oh, Fluttershy,
you are too kind.
But I could never ask that of
you. It might be dangerous..!
I want to do it! For all
of you, my new friends.
And to protect a
historical treasure!
♪♪
Give me a hoof here!
♪ [dark music] ♪
We did it!
You're safe!
Thanks, everypony.
♪♪
Give us the talisman,
Caballeron!
We're not taking
no for an answer!
Wait! You don't understand.
My friends are researchers!
They only want to
study the talisman
and keep it safe in a
museum! Right, Dr. C?
Uh... no.
Ah! But... but...you said...
Now that he's holding
Tonatiuh's talisman,
he has to tell the truth!
Admit it,
Caballeron!
You're only pretending
to like Fluttershy
because she has the
wings you needed
to steal the
truth talisman!
Isn't that
right?
No!
I admit, that was
the original reason.
But my henchponies and
I have come to value
your friendship
and kindness.
Didn't see that
coming.
Or that!
More intruders!? And you DARE
to steal Tonatiuh's talisman!?
Guardian-goyles, ATTACK!
♪♪
Fluttershy! Can't you ask them
to stop, like the jungle cats!?
Um, excuse me?
Uh, Guardian-goyles?
It's no good! They're only
stone and magic, not alive.
I encountered some
like this in Marapore.
Ah, yes. I seem to
recall similar creations
in Flankladesh.
So..? How do you
get rid of them!?
I know they don't
like bright light!
There's none of
that in here.
Not yet... Caballeron!
Do you still have the
Diamond of Lapis-Lux?
Yes. I mean, YES.
I mean... Argh!
How did you know
I stole it?
Lucky guess.
Hold it high!
♪ [heroic music] ♪
Wow! You two make
a great team!
Yeah, I'm not sure
how I feel about that.
Feel later! Now,
it's time to escape!
If we want to get
out of here,
we're all gonna have
to work TOGETHER.
That's...er actually
a good idea.
See? Told you he'd listen.
A truce until we escape?
But how can we trust you?
I cannot lie. Now,
all together!
Ah! You again!?
If I wanted to
play GAMES,
I would get out
my pinochle deck!
This way!
♪♪
Rainbow Dash!
I'm gonna need the deluxe spa
package after this adventure.
That doesn't leave
this temple!
♪♪
That's it! I'm quitting
the henchpony business
to finally follow my dreams
of becoming an opera star!
Uh...maybe you
should hold this.
You cannot hide in there
forever! It's a DEAD end.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ahuizotl won't give up
until he catches us!
I think our problem
is the solution.
Uh, did you forget there's
a monster out there
that wants to crush us?
But WHY? Nopony
ever asked Ahuizotl
what his side of
the story is.
He must have a reason
for being so upset.
Or maybe he's
just a bad guy!
Do I need to remind you he
tried to squash Daring Do
like a hundred times!?
And me as well.
I was so scared,
I had to change my ascot.
Ah! Curse this truth teller!
Understanding begins
with listening.
Prepared to
meet your DOOM!?
Um, not really.
Just here to ask...
Why are you chasing
us, Mr. Ahuizotl?
Well, the thing is,
I'm in charge of
protecting this jungle.
If another artifact goes
missing on my watch,
I'm going to be
in SO much trouble
with the other
guardian creatures.
Oh! That sounds like a
lot of responsibility...
Wha--! It is! And those two have taken
so many relics from my land,
my job is on the line!
So maybe I am a little
violent and ferocious..
Can you blame me?
The only reason I've
been taking the artifacts
is because I thought
I was protecting them.
I was stealing
them to get rich!
Uh.. But I never realized
you had a noble cause!
I thought you were
just being a monster.
I get that a lot.
Maybe there is
something to this
whole "listening to
everypony" thing.
It doesn't always mean
they're telling the truth,
but everycreature
deserves kindness.
True. And because you
returned the talisman
and took the time
to understand me,
I will let you all go.
On one condition!
You swear to never
steal artifacts
from the Tenochtitlan
basin again!
I promise!
I'll even write that
in my next book.
YOUR next book?
You mean you're
actually A.K. Yearling!?
Don't tell anypony!
That gives me an idea..
Hey! What's going on?
I thought your first
co-written novel
would bring out
a ton of fans!
We've been upstaged
by a new author.
And so the noble Ahuizotl
bravely toiled day and night
to protect the jungle's
precious artifacts...