No... nope...
Thank you kindly, Twilight, for helping me out.
I bet Big Macintosh I could get all these
Golden Delicious in the barn by lunchtime.
If I win, he's gonna walk down Stirrup
Street in one of Granny's girdles, heh heh.
No problem at all, Applejack.
But I'm glad, the goal is lunchtime.
All this hard work is making me hungry.
I know, right?
Oh really, Spike? You've been lounging
on my back all morning while we worked.
Exactly! You two were taking
so long, I missed snacktime.
I guess be better get some food.
Nope... worm...
Aha!
Oh, Spike! That looks delicious...!
Spike!
What?
It's a letter from Princess Celestia!
Hear ye, hear ye.
Her Grand Royal Highness
Princess Celestia of Equestria...
...is pleased to announce
the Grand Galloping Gala...
...to be held in the magnificent capital
city of Canterlot on the 21st day of...
...yadda yadda yadda...
...cordially extends an invitation
to Twilight Sparkle plus one guest.
The Grand Galloping Gala!
Look! Two tickets!
Wow, great! I've never been to the Gala.
Have you, Spike?
No and I plan to keep it that way. I don't
want any of that girly frilly frou-frou nonsense.
Oh, come on Spike! A dance would be nice.
Nice?! It's a hiccup more than just nice!
I'd love to go.
Land sakes! If I had an apple stand set up...
...ponies would be chewin' our tasty
vittles till the cows came home.
Do you have any idea how much business
I could drum up for Sweet Apple Acres?
Why, with all that money we could
do a heap of fixin' up round here.
We could replace that saggy old roof.
And Big Macintosh could
replace that saggy old plow.
And Granny Smith could
replace that saggy old hip!
Wow. I'd give my left hind
leg to go to that Gala.
Oh. Well, in that case, would you like to...
Are we talking about the Grand Galloping Gala?
Rainbow Dash. You told me you were
too busy to help me harvest apples.
What were you busy doin'? Spyin'?
No. I was busy...
...napping.
And I just happened to hear
that you have an extra ticket?
-Yeah, but...
-Yes! This is so awesome!
The Wonderbolts perform at the Grand Galloping
Gala every year. I can see it now...
Everyone will be watching the sky.
Their eyes riveted on the Wonderbolts.
But then, in would fly...
Rainbow Dash!
I would draw their attention
with my Super Speed Strut.
Then I would mesmerize them
with my Fantastic Filly Flash.
And for my grand finale the Buccaneer Blaze!
The ponies would go wild!
The Wonderbolts would insist that my signature
moves be incorporated into their routine.
And then welcome me as their newest member.
Don't you see, Twilight? This could be
my one chance to show 'em my stuff.
You gotta take me!
Hold on just one pony pickin' minute here.
I asked for that ticket first.
So? That doesn't mean you own it.
Oh yeah? Well, I challenge you to
a hoof wrestle. Winner gets the ticket.
Girls! These are MY tickets!
I'll decide who gets it, thank you very much.
Whoever has the best reason to go,
should get the ticket, don't you think?
-Drummin' up business for the farm?
-A chance to audition for the Wonderbolts?
-Money to fix Granny's hip!
-Living the dream!
Oh my! Those are all pretty
good reasons, aren't they?
Listen to that. I am starving.
I don't know about you, but I can't make
important decisions on an empty stomach.
So I'll think about it over lunch
and get back to you two. Okay?
Okay.
So who you're gonna give the ticket to, Twilight?
I don't know, Spike. But I really
can't think straight when I'm hungry.
So where should we eat?
Bats! Bats on my face! HELP!
Wait! These aren't...!
Tickets to the Grand Galloping Gala?!
It's the most amazing incredible tremendous
super-fun wonderful terrifically humongous
party in all of Equestria!
I've always always ALWAYS wanted to go!
Oh, the Grand Galloping Gala
is the best place for me!
Hip hip hurray,
it's the best place for me!
For Pinkie!
With decorations and streamers and fairy lights
and pinwheels and piñatas and pincushions...
With goodies like sugar cubes and sugar canes
and sundaes and sunbeams and sasparilla!
And I get to play my favoritest of favorite
fantabulous games like pin the tail on the pony!
Oh, the Grand Galloping Gala
is the best place for me!
Cause it's the most gallerific
superly-teriffic gala ever in the whole Galaxy!
Whee!
Oh thank you, Twilight!
It's the most wonderfulest gift ever!
Um... Actually...
Are these what I think they are?
Yes, yes, YES! Twilight's taking my to
the Grand Galloping Gala in Canterlot!
The Gala!
I design ensembles for the Gala every year,
but I've never had the opportunity to attend.
Oh, the society, the culture, the glamor!
It's where I truly belong.
And where I'm destined to meet... HIM!
Him...!
Who?
Him.
I would stroll through the Gala
and everyone would wonder...
"Who is that mysterious mare?"
They would never guess that I was just
a simple pony from little old Ponyville.
Why, I would cause such a sensation...
...that I would be invited for an
audience with Princess Celestia herself!
And the Princess would be so taken
with the style and elegance...
...that she would introduce me to HIM!
Her nephew!
The most handsome, eligible
unicorn stallion in Canterlot!
Our eyes would meet, our hearts would melt...
Our courtship would be magnificent.
He would ask for my hoof in marriage
and of course I would say...
YES!!!
We would have a royal wedding,
befitting a princess...
...which is what I would
become upon marrying him.
The stallion of my dreams.
Twilight! I simply cannot believe you would
invite Pinkie Pie, so she could party...
...and prevent me from meeting my true love!
How could you?!
Hey!
Angel! These are perfect!
Listen guys, I haven't decided
who to give the extra ticket to.
You haven't?!
Um... Excuse me...
Twilight, I would just like to ask...
I mean, if it would be all right...
...if you haven't given it to someone else...
You?! You want to go to the Gala?
Oh... no.
I mean... yes. Or actually, kind of. You see...
It's not so much the Grand Galloping Gala...
...as it is the wondrous private gated
garden that surrounds the dance.
The flowers are said the be the most
beautiful and fragrant in all of Equestria!
For the night of the Gala and that night
alone will they all be in bloom.
And that's just the flora!
Don't get me started on the fauna.
There's loons and toucans and bitterns, oh my!
Hummingbirds that can really hum!
And buzzards that can really buzz!
And blue jays and red jays and green
jays, pink jays and pink flamingos.
Gee, Fluttershy, it sounds... beautiful.
-Wait just a minute!
-Rainbow Dash!
Were you following me?
No... I mean, yes... I mean, maybe.
Look, it doesn't matter!
I couldn't risk a goody four-shoes like you
giving that ticket away to just anybody.
-Wait just another minute!
-Applejack! Were you following me too?
No. I was following this one to make
sure she didn't try any funny business.
-Still tryin' to take my ticket.
-YOUR ticket?!
But Twilight's taking me!
QUIET!
...and then I said "Oatmeal? Are you craz..." Oh.
Girls! There's no use in arguing!
But Twilight...!
This is my decision and I'm
gonna make it on my own...
...and I certainly can't think
straight with all this noise!
Not to mention hunger.
Now go on! Shoo!
And don't worry, I'll figure this out!
Somehow.
Oh Spike. What am I gonna do?
All five of my best friends have
really good reasons to go to the Gala.
Applejack, Rainbow Dash,
Pinkie Pie or Fluttershy, Rarity...
Oh, who should go with me?
Have you made your decision?
I CAN'T DECIDE!
Twilight, he just wants to take your order.
Oh. I would love a daffodil and daisy sandwich.
Do you have any rubies?
No? Okay, I'll have the hay fries. Extra crispy.
What do you think, Spike?
I think we have to try another restaurant.
I mean, I like grass just fine, but would
it hurt anybody to offer some gemstones?
I mean about the Gala
and the ticket and who I should take!
-Oh, you're still on THAT?
-Spike, listen!
How do I choose? And when I do choose,
will the other four be mad at me?
I mean, I could give up
my ticket and give away two...
...but that would still leave three
disappointed ponies. What if I...
Ah, your food.
Oh, thank you. This looks so good. I'm sure
everything will be much clearer once I eat.
Um, Madame? Are you going to
eat your food in ze rain?
It's not raining.
What's going on?
Hi there, best friend forever I've ever ever had?
Enjoying the sunny weather?
Rainbow Dash, what are you doing?
Whadya mean? I just saw the smartest,
most generous pony about to get rained on...
...so I though I'd kick a hole
in the clouds to keep her dry...
...so she can dine at peace. That's all.
Rainbow. You're not trying to get extra
consideration for the extra ticket...
...by doing the extra special favors, are you?
Me? No no no, of course not!
Seriously, I'd do it for anypony.
Rainbow, I am not comfortable
accepting unwanted favors.
So I'd appreciate if you closed up
that rain cloud right now.
Fine.
That's better.
-Twilight! It's raining.
-No. Really?
Come with me before you catch a cold!
Oops. Sorry.
Oh no! It's quite all right.
After all, we are THE BEST OF FRIENDS,
are we not?
And you know what the best of friends do?
Makeover!
Ugh... Rarity...
There! Oh, you're simply darling!
Yeah... It is kinda pretty, isn't it?
And you! Oh, Spike. I have a dandy
little outfit for the dashing gent.
-Oh, Spike.
-Now you just need a hat!
I told you! I don't want any part of this girly
gala gunk. See you back at the library!
Oh, who needs him anyway?
This is all about you!
And how fabulous you'll look
at the Grand Galloping Gala.
Wait. The Grand...
And, oh my goodness, what a coincidence!
I happen to have an ensemble
of my own that matches yours to a tee.
We would be the belles of the ball, you and I.
Everyone would be clamoring for our attention.
All eyes would be on us. And then everyone
would finally know, the most beautiful...
...most talented, most sophisticated
pony in all of Equestria...
...is Rarity the Unicorn!
And Twilight Sparkle, of course.
I see what's going on. You're just
buttering me up so I give you the extra ticket.
Well, it's not gonna work!
You're going to have to wait for my
decision just like everyone else.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've been
trying all day just to get some lunch!
Did somepony say lunch?
You've got to be kidding me!
I got apple pie, apple fritters, apple tarts,
apple dumplings, apple crisps, apple crumbles...
...aaand apple Brown Betty!
The dessert. Not my auntie.
What'd ya say there, best friend?
Is that a yes?
No! NO!
I don't know who I'm giving the ticket to!
And all these favors aren't
making it any easier to decide.
In fact, I'm less sure now
than I was this morning! Aaargh!
So... that's a maybe?
I never thought being showered with
favors would be so aggravating.
Fluttershy! Not you too...
Oh! Well, hello, Twilight.
I hope you don't mind but we're all
doing a little spring cleaning for you.
It's summer.
Oh. Well... better late than never, right?
It was Angel's idea.
You're not doing this for the ticket, are you?
Oh, no! I'm doing this because you're
my very best friend! Right, Angel?
Yes. We are just doing this for the ticket.
No no NO!
Well, this is all very nice of you and Angel...
...but I'm not accepting any extra favors
until I've made my final decision.
So I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
SURPRISE!
Twilight is my bestest friend, whoopee! Whoopee!
-Pinkie...
She's the cutest, smartest, all-around best pony! Pony!
-Pinkie...!
I bet if I throw a super-duper fun party! Party!
-Pinkie!
She'll give her extra ticket to the Gala to meee!
-PINKIEEE!!!
Yes, Twilight?
At least the other ponies *try*
to be subtle about the ticket!
-Wait... What ticket? What gala?
-Oh, you didn't know?
Twilight has an extra ticket
to the Grand Galloping Gala!
THE GRAND GALLOPING GALA?!
Have I ever told you how much
I love your mane?
I'll wash your dishes!
-Would you like any help with your gardening?
-I have a cartload of extra carrots.
What are we gonna do?
We're... gonna... RUUUUN!!!
Warn me next time you're gonna do that.
I didn't even know it was gonna happen!
Not quick, lock the doors!
I can't decide, I just can't decide!
It's important to all of you and I just
can't stand to disappoint any of you...
...and giving me gifts and doing me
favors won't make any difference.
Because you're all my friends and I wanna
make you all happy and I can't! I JUST CAN'T!
Twilight, sugar... I didn't mean to
put so much pressure on you.
And if it helps, I don't want the ticket anymore.
You can give it to somepony else.
I won't feel bad, I promise.
Me too. I feel just awful
that I made you feel so awful.
And me too. It's no fun upsetting your friends!
Twilight, it was unfair of me
to try to force you as I did.
YES! That means, the ticket is mine!
I've got the ticket, I've got the ticket...
You know... I haven't perfected my signature
moves for the Wonderbolts anyway.
I don't need that ticket either.
We all got so gung-ho about
going to the Gala...
...that we couldn't see how
ungung-ho we were makin' you.
We're sorry, Twilight!
Spike, take down a note.
Dear Princess Celestia. I've learned that one of
the joys of friendship is sharing your blessings.
But when it's not enough
blessings to go around...
...having more than your friends
can make you feel pretty awful.
So, though I appreciate the invitation...
...I will be returning both tickets
to the Grand Galloping Gala.
WHAT?!
If my friends can't all go,
I don't wanna go either.
Twilight, you don't have to do that!
Nope, I've made up my mind.
Spike, you can send the letter now.
Now you won't get to go to the Gala either.
It's okay, girls. I couldn't possibly enjoy
myself without my best friends there with me.
So I'd rather not go at all.
Well, wallop my withers, Spike. Isn't that just like
a boy. Can't handle the least bit of sentiment.
Whoah, Nelly!
A letter from the Princess? That was fast!
My faithful student Twilight.
Why didn't you just say so in the first place?
Six tickets to the Grand Galloping Gala!
Now we can all go!
Allow us to treat you to dinner.
What a great way to apologise!
And to celebrate! Come on, everyone!
The cupcakes are on me.
How come I don't get a ticket to the Gala?
And one for you, Spike.
I mean... gross! I have to go too?
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000