Spike! Wake up! Wake up, wake up,
it's Winter Wrap Up Day!
-Mommy...?
-Winter Wrap Up!
You're not mommy!
Spike! The first day of spring is tomorrow!
So everypony in Ponyville needs to clean up
winter. Now help me get ready.
Clean up winter? Who cleans up winter?
Don't they just use magic to change
the seasons like we do in Canterlot?
No, Spike. Ponyville was
started by earth ponies...
...so for hundreds of years they've
never used magic to clean up winter.
It's traditional!
It's ridiculous!
No magic, pfuh...
Okay, let's see. Scarf: Check.
Saddle: Check. Boots: Check.
Spike refusing to get up and
going back to sleep: Check.
It's a good thing I'm so organized.
I'm ready! Bright and early!
Oh... Maybe a little too early.
Those must be the team vests Rarity designed.
Blue for the weather team...
...green for the plant team...
...and tan for the animal team.
I wonder which team vest I'll be wearing.
I'll take a blue vest.
The same color as my blanket.
Which I think I hear calling my name.
"Spike! Spike! Come to bed!"
Ugh... It's too early.
Thank you, everypony, for being
here bright and early.
We need every single pony's help to
wrap up winter and bring in spring.
Now, all of you have your vests and
have been assigned to your teams...
...so let's do even better than last year and
have the quickest Winter Wrap Up ever!
Oh, this is so exciting!
All right, everypony, find your team leader...
...and let's get galloping!
Oh gosh! Where should I go?
I'm not sure where I'd fit in.
What exactly does everypony do?
Three months of winter coolness
and awesome holidays.
We've kept our hoofsies warm at home,
time off from work to play.
But the food we've stored is runnin' out
and we can't grow in this cold.
And even though I love my boots,
this fashion's getting old.
The time has come to welcome spring
and all things warm and green,
But it's also time to say goodbye,
it's winter we must clean.
How can I help? I'm new, you'll see.
What does everypony do?
How do I fit in without magic?
I haven't got a clue.
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Let's finish our holiday cheer!
Cause tomorrow spring is here!
Bringing home the southern birds,
a pegasus job begins.
And clearing all the gloomy skies
to let the sunshine in.
We move the clouds
and we melt the white snow.
When the sun comes up,
its warmth and beauty will glow!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Let's finish our holiday cheer!
Cause tomorrow spring is here!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Little critters hibernate
under the snow and ice.
We wake up all their sleepy heads
so quietly and nice.
We help them gather up their food,
fix their homes below.
We welcome back the southern birds,
so their families can grow!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Let's finish our holiday cheer!
Cause tomorrow spring is here!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
No easy task to clear the ground,
plant our tiny seeds.
With proper care and sunshine,
everyone it feeds.
Apples, carrots, celery stalks,
colorful flowers too.
We must work so very hard.
It's just so much to do!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Let's finish our holiday cheer!
Cause tomorrow spring is here!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Now that I know what they all do,
I have to find my place.
And help with all of my heart,
tough task ahead I face.
How will I do without my magic,
help the earth pony way.
I wanna belong so I must
do my best today! Do my best today!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Let's finish our holiday cheer!
Cause tomorrow spring is here!
Winter Wrap Up, Winter Wrap Up!
Everypony belongs to a team.
What should I do? Where should I go?
All right, team! You're cleared for takeoff!
-Rainbow Dash!
-Oh, hey Twilight! What's up?
What are you doing?
Sending off one of my flight crews to retrieve
the birds that have flown south for the winter.
Oh! Can I help?
How about if I help clear out the clouds?
Um...
Right. No wings.
Sorry, Twilight.
Great! Now what do we do?
I don't know about you but I'm gonna be napping.
Come on, Spike! This is serious business!
Winter needs to be wrapped up.
And I'm determined to do my part!
Somehow.
Rarity, please tell me there's something...
anything I can help you with!
Well, how would you like to help create
Ponyville's finest birds' nests?
Birds' nests?
Why, yes! When the weather team guides
the birds back north for the spring...
...they'll need a place
to live and lay their eggs.
Wow, Rarity, that one's really beautiful!
Oh, why, thank you most sincerely.
Would you like to try your hoof at a nest?
Would I? Yes! Where do I begin?
Okay now. Uh... Take some of that straw and
hay over there and a little bit of branch.
Now weave them through there... Yes!
Uh... Take some ribbon, yes... oh uh n...
not there... oohhh... yes...
Tuck it in over there. Uh...
but be careful not to...
Oh no no, I... I guess that will do... Oh dear.
There!
It looks just like... yours. Oh my.
That nest needs to be condemned!
Oh, Spike. It's not so bad.
Maybe the birds can use it as a...
An outhouse?
Spike. It's just fine. It's just a little
rough aroung the edges.
Let me lend you a hoof.
Let's just untie this ribbon and if we take
out these sticks here, we'll shape this...
I think we lost her.
...and we need to weave the string in here...
Hellooo, Twilight!
Wow, Pinkie Pie, you're quite a skater.
Probably the best skater I've ever seen.
Thanks, Twilight! I've been doing this since I
was an itty-bitty little-wittle Twinkie-Pinkie!
This comes naturally.
Which is probably why they
designated me the lake scorer.
I cut lines in the lake with my skates.
That way, when the rest of the weather
team comes here to break the ice...
...it will be easy as pie!
How clever! When the thick ice begins
to melt, it will break along the lines.
Well, you sure have a lot of work ahead of you.
There's quite a few lakes in Ponyville.
Huh... Tell me about it!
Hey, Twilight! Wanna help me out?
Would I?
Come on, put on those skates over there.
I bet you'll be a natural too!
Okay.
Maybe on second thought...
What are you talking about?
You said you wanted to be helpful.
Now get out there!
Twilight! Steer! Steer!
Oh boy!
You ARE a natural, Twilight! Natural disaster!
Twilight, you did a great
job your first time around.
I'm sure my first time was just as wobbly
and bobbling and crasherrific as yours.
Really?
...No.
But did I make you feel better?
Yeah... I guess.
I bet you'll be super awesome at something
that keeps your hooves on the ground.
I know! Fluttershy could probably
use your help with the critters.
Well, I'm pretty good with little animals.
Yeah! I'll go help her!
It's... that way.
Wake up, little sleepy heads!
Hope you had some wonderful
dreams and restful hibernation.
But it's time to up now! Spring is coming!
Awww, how cute!
Aren't they? This is my
favorite task the whole season.
When I get to see all my
little animal friends again.
Uh... what's "hibernation"?
It's like a long sleep.
Long sleep?
Yes.
Wake up, little porcupines!
Animals often hibernate through the winter
to save their energy and eat less food.
I definitely like the idea of hibernation.
Uh... except for the "eat less food" part.
Oh, but just look at all these warrens and dens.
I'm worried that I won't be able to wake up
every animal before spring comes.
Well, I'll help, Fluttershy!
Oh, you will? Oh, that would be wonderful!
Okay!
Let's start there!
Hello! Wake up, little friends!
Wherever you are. Spring is coming!
I wonder which cute little
furry creatures I've awoken!
Aaa! Snakes! Snaaakes!
Good morning, friends!
All this Winter Wrap Up stuff
is a lot harder than it looks.
Right. Because there's no magic.
Why don't you just use magic,
Twilight, and get it done the right way?
No, Spike. I have to do it the traditional way.
Ponyville has never needed
magic to wrap up winter.
But they never had you here before, either.
Think of how much quicker they could
wrap up winter with your magic!
No, no, NO! I'm gonna find some other
way that I can help out if it kills me!
Keep pushin', Caramel! That's it, Bumpkin!
I know it's hard work, but you
guys are doin' great! YEEHAW!
Hey, Applejack! How's everything going?
Oh, just dandy. A little slow startin'
but peachy all the same.
There's a lotta groung to clear, ya hear?
We can't ever start the
plantin' and the waterin'...
...until we get all these heap
o' snow hightailed outta here.
Well, I'd like to help.
Well... I... I don't know, Twilight.
Just give me a chance!
Well, I never turn down a hard worker, but...
"Think of how much quicker they could
wrap up winter with your magic!"
I could use a come-to-life spell...
Here goes.
She's awful strong for such a little pony.
That's my girl! Following my advice.
And what in tarnation does that mean?
Slow down! SLOW DOWN!
What's goin' on?
What'd you do?
You used magic, didn't you?!
Nuts, Twilight! You used magic!
The nerve, can you believe her?
That's not how we do it round here, Twilight.
And especially not on my farm!
Well, see... I just wanted to...
Oh!
Come on, Twilight. Come on out!
I'm a winter mess up.
Oh, you're good at a lot of things.
Just not nest making, ice skating,
animal waking, snow clearing...
Huh, thanks a lot for making
me feel sooo much better.
That's what I'm here for, sister.
Rainbow Dash, y'all on the weather team
need to melt the rest of this snow here...
...on the ground and the trees pronto.
Got it!
You can't! My poor little animals' homes
will get flooded if the snow melts too fast.
Got it.
I'm tellin' you, Rainbow.
You gotta melt that snow now!
No! You simply must wait!
Okay...
-Go.
-Stop.
-Go!
-Stop!
-GO!
-STOP!
Urgh! Make up your minds!
Oh! What in Equestria are
all you arguing about?
This sort of sillyness is why we
were late for spring last year.
And the year before that.
And the year before that!
Did she say late?
I was hoping my amazingly inspirational speech
would urge everyone to do better than last year.
But now it looks like we're
going to be later than ever!
I mean just look at this catastrophe.
The ice scorers made the ice
chunks too big to melt.
The nest designer's horrendously behind.
We need several hundred
and she's only made one.
And don't get me started on all the clouds still
in the sky, the icicles on the trees...
Oh, this isn't good. Not at all!
And it's gonna be all to pieces disastrous
if we can't get our seeds all planted.
Chillax, Applejack. We're busting
our chops as fast as we can.
No, not fast! You have to wake animals slowly.
Uh, AJ?
Oh, good gravy! Caramel lost the
grass seeds again, didn't he?
Ey-yup.
Ditzy-Doo accidentally went north
to get the southern birds!
Oh, that featherbrain! Didn't she learn
her lesson last year, when she went west?
Stop this at once! We don't have time to argue!
It's almost sundown.
Spring is going to be late again.
Another year of scandal and shame!
If only we could be more organized...
Spike! Get my checklist and clipboard.
-Stat!
-Eh... Yes, m'am.
Stop everypony!
Stop!
Sorry.
I know you all want to
complete your jobs on time.
But arguing is no way to go about it!
What you need is...
Organization!
And I'm just the pony for the job.
I can't believe it. Spring is here! On time!
And we have you to thank for it.
If it weren't for your organizing
skills, we would still be arguing.
Ey-yup.
It was a team effort.
And since you helped every team,
we have an official vest for you.
We give you the title "All-Team Organizer"!
Gosh... I don't even know what to say.
Thank you, everypony!
And hereby I declare that winter is...
...wrapped up on time!
Spike sure gonna be in for a hog-sized
surprise when that last piece a' ice melts.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"Winter Wrap Up was one of the most special
things I've ever been a part of here in Ponyville."
"It helped me to learn that we all have hidden
talents and if we're patient and diligent..."
"...we're sure to find them."
"And as always, with good friendship and
teamwork, ponies can accomplish anything."
How's that, Spike?
Spike?
Oh, Spike...
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000