I can't believe we're going
to the Appleoosa County Fair!
Animal shows,
carnival rides...
And all kinds of
food on a stick!
Speaking of food, did you
pack snacks for the train?
For there AND back.
And our train
tickets are all set.
And I've got our whole
itinerary planned!
Are you sure you're
not Twilight's sister?
Weeks of planning has
all come down to this.
All we have to do now is wait
for our chaperone to get here.
Mm hm!
♪ [musical clock ticking] ♪
So when's Rainbow
Dash coming?
I thought you were
gonna ask Applejack.
I don't suppose
you asked Rarity?
You mean we spent all
this time planning a trip
and none of us asked
anypony to take us!?
In our defense, every
other part of the trip
was planned really well...
We really did think
of everything,
except finding
somepony to take us
and the fair is
only today!
I'm sorry, darlings, but I
can't possibly go to Appleoosa.
I promised to deliver a new
design to Fancy Pants for his
Monocle and Top Hat
Appreciation Society Soiree.
Can't you finish
it tomorrow?
Well, I could, but you'll
learn as you get older
how important it is to
keep your promises,
especially when
running a business.
Maybe we should just
go by ourselves?
WHAT? Oh, my dear, no!
Appleoosa is far too long a
train ride for young foals
without accompaniment!
You could end up in the
wrong place entirely.
Why don't you see if
Rainbow Dash is free?
Sorry, but I just heard from
Spitfire that a whole bunch of
storm clouds got loose
from the cloud factory
and she needs every
Wonderbolt to help bust 'em.
Aw, come on Rainbow Dash,
they won't miss ONE pony
and we really want
to go to the fair!
Apparently, we're too
young to go alone..
Well, duh.
Young ponies like
you could get lost
and never find
your way back,
but I still can't go.
Being a Wonderbolt isn't
just about showing off,
it's also a
responsibility.
You'll understand
when you get older.
I'm sure you'll find
somepony else to take you.
I wish I could, sugarcube.
But Big Mac's not
feeling well today.
Aww!
But Big Mac's old enough
to take care of himself
and we'd all have so
much fun together..
Sometimes taking
care of somepony
is more important
than having fun.
Speaking of which, don't
you even THINK about
trying to go without a grown
pony there to take care of YOU.
You could end up in
hot water, or worse.
We know...
The fair could be over before
we find somepony to take us!
But then we thought of YOU!
Since the fair will
be full of all sorts
of animals and creatures....!
I'm sorry, but Twilight
has an important
magical research project and
she's asked for my help.
I guess that means
Twilight's busy too?
I'm afraid I am. Starswirl
sent me this enchanted flower
and it isn't doing well.
If I figure out its
magical properties,
maybe we can save it.
So that's a "no" on going
with us to the fair?
We've already asked
Applejack, Rainbow Dash,
and Rarity and none
of them can come!
And everypony
made it clear
we're too young
to go on our own...
Oh, definitely.
You could take the wrong
train or miss your stop...
Or get lost in a
strange town and end up
in a dangerous situation
with nopony to help you!
We know!
I know it's hard,
but sometimes
you just can't do
what you want.
I'm pretty sure if YOU wanted
to go to the fair you could...
Sure, grownups can do a lot
of things that foals can't,
but there's plenty
we can't do either.
Like right now, I can't
find a SINGLE reference
to this flower!
None of the birds or
insects I've talked to
have heard of it either.
I wonder if there's anything
in Shadetail Evergreen's
Tome of Flora and Fauna?
That book's pretty
out of date,
but it might be
worth a try.
I think there's a copy in
the library filed under
"Discontinued But Still
Potentially Useful
Ancient Texts."
Unless I put it under
"Hokum With A Slight Chance
of Practical Applications."
I guess this flower is
the most interesting thing
we're gonna see today..
Unless you count watching
Twilight struggle to remember
how she organizes her books.
I bet every pony in Equestria
is in Appleoosa right now!
Every pony but US.
I wish we didn't have
to wait to grow up.
I wish it would
happen all at once.
Then we'd know everything
we'd need to get to the fair
and back with no problem.
I just wish we were
as old as our sisters!
Then nopony could
tell us what to do,
and we'd be able to
take care of ourselves!
♪ [chimes] ♪
Hey, Sweetie Belle, why's
your face all lit up?
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Do you know what this means!?
WE CAN GO TO THE FAIR!
I hope you brought
the tickets!
We've gotta hurry if we're
going to make the train.
I think we'll be fine.
Check out how
fast we're going!
Grownup legs are strong!
You're not kidding!
I don't know how much of
this my scooter can take!
And nopony yelled at us
to slow down even once!
Ha! Being a grownup is great!
♪♪
We made it!
Of course we did!
We're grownup ponies
now. We can do anything!
And all those worries
Twilight and the others had
don't apply anymore
because we're big!
And being big is all it takes!
♪ Woke up this morning
feeling tired and small ♪
♪ But look at us now! We
must be ninety feet tall. ♪
♪ Don't have to worry
'bout making mistakes ♪
♪ because being big
is all it takes! ♪
♪ A tiny twist of fate
brought on this big change. ♪
♪ Give me room, gotta zoom! ♪
♪ I've got plans to arrange ♪
♪ Can do what I want, be
it run, trot, or traipse, ♪
♪ 'cause being big
is all it takes. ♪
♪ Being big isn't
just a size. ♪
♪ At bedtime we don't even
have to close our eyes. ♪
♪ We're in control now,
for goodness sake ♪
♪ 'cause being big
is all it takes! ♪
♪ Leaving behind the
little pony you've known, ♪
♪ steppin' out, growin' up,
makin' moves of my own. ♪
♪ You can't tell me no. ♪
♪ There's no place I can't go: ♪
♪ mountains, cities,
jungles, or lakes, ♪
♪ 'cause being big
is all it takes. ♪
♪ Being big isn't just a size ♪
♪ We'll tell you our opinion
'cause we're oh so wise ♪
♪ We're in control now,
for goodness sake ♪
♪ 'cause being big
is all it takes! ♪
♪ I can eat all the snacks cause
that's for me to decide. ♪
♪ We know how it all works,
even what we ain't tried! ♪
♪ Facts don't matter now
cause it's not what we know ♪
♪ We can win any
argument with ♪
♪ "Because I say so!" ♪
♪ Can't stop us now, don't
try to stand in our way! ♪
♪ We're awake, gonna take ♪
♪ All we can from today ♪
♪ Once we had to listen now
you'll hear what we say ♪
♪ Everything is always OK! ♪
♪ Cause being big is all
it takes! All it takes! ♪
I think I ate
too many snacks...
Uh, this doesn't
look like Appleoosa.
[nasty gravelly voice]
That's because it isn't!
♪ [eerie music] ♪
You all heard that, right?
Uh... Hello? Do you think
we got on the wrong train?
I thought trains just took
you where you wanted to go.
Sorry. I don't mean to laugh,
but you three must
not travel much.
This is Hayseed Junction.
The train to Appleoosa
isn't for a few hours..
Or, you could
set off on hoof.
It's treacherous
and confusing,
unfit for the
young or timid..
But you three are
grownups. You'll be fine.
I'll write down
some directions.
Maybe we should
wait for the train.
And miss the fair?
We already ended up
in the wrong place,
which is exactly what
we were warned about!
And.. what if we can't
follow the directions?
Come on! We didn't come
all this way for nothing.
Besides, I've been through
a swamp as a young pony,
as a grownup, it'll be a snap!
Grownups always
know the way!
Because being big
is all it takes!
Sorry. I've got kind
of a throat thing.
♪ [rhythmic piano] ♪
♪♪
Ah! [splash]
Sweetie Belle, are you
sure this is the right way?
♪ [scary music] ♪
Sweetie Belle?
Scootaloo?
Don't DO that!
Apple Bloom: Girls?
Maybe we should head
back to the station..
I'm not sure we can.
I think we're lost.
Just like Twilight
and the others said!
Well, where were you when I was
feeding and caring for him?
AHHH! Wild swamp ponies!
Hmph!
We're not wild swamp ponies,
we're just grownups!
And we are
definitely NOT lost.
OK. But that swamp
is pretty confusing
if you're not from
around here.
I'm Spur and this is Biscuit.
I'm Apple Bloom, nice to meet
you, but.. we're not confused.
We're just... exploring
new ways to Appleoosa!
Hey, that's where
we're going!
No. It isn't!
Uh, which is it?
Biscuit thinks he can
just take Bloofy, here,
to the fair.
Why not? It's just up the
road and Bloofy's MY pet too.
Since when? Bloofy's
never even seen a CROWD,
which you'd know if you
ever took care of him...
Did you ever think
meeting all those ponies
might be good for him?
He seems OK meeting us.
See? They're grownups
and THEY get it.
Bloofy should totally come
to the fair with me, right?
Y'all don't really
think that, do ya?
Um. Hold on, us
grownups need to confer.
What do you girls think?
If they go to the
fair, we can tag along!
And Spur probably
should share Bloofy.
I mean, that's something a
grownup would say, right?
As grownup ponies, we think
you should SHARE Bloofy
and let Biscuit take
him to the fair.
That is some quality
grownup advice!
But Bloofy's never been around
anything that exciting!
What if something
goes wrong!?
We're headed to
the fair too.
Since we're such
great advice givers,
feel free to ask
us for more.
♪♪
Oh! Ho ho! It's everything
I thought it'd be!
Well, my goodness, what
an interesting critter!
You should enter him
in the animal showcase.
You'd be sure to win most
interesting creature!
Animals showcase? That's
exactly what we should do!
That seems like a bad idea.
What do you grownups think?
♪ [upbeat music] ♪
♪♪
Whoo hoo!
What happened to being
able to ask your advice!?
You ran off the
second we got here!
Where's Biscuit
and Bloofy?
That's why I came
to find you!
♪ [fanfare] ♪
Spur: It's one thing to
bring Bloofy to the fair,
but it's another to
stick him in a showcase!
What's the big deal?
You're supposed
to be sharing him.
Yeah, I'm with Biscuit. The
showcase looks like fun.
Sorry if I think
taking care of Bloofy
is more important
than having fun.
Bloofy's just excited!
He probably just
wants to get out.
♪ [delicate music] ♪
♪♪
Are you sure you're not just
upset you have to share him?
What if you took
a little break?
You mean, like, leave?
If sharing him is too hard,
that might be the best thing.
Take our word for
it. We are grownups..
I don't know what
Spur's so worried about;
Bloofy and Biscuit
are having fun.
Yeah. What could
go wrong?
♪♪
♪ [dramatic music] ♪
Me and my big grownup mouth.
♪ [tense music] ♪
♪♪
Do you think this
qualifies as getting into
a dangerous situation with
no grown pony to help us?
I think WE'RE the grown ponies
that need to be helping today!
♪♪
BLOOFY! TREATS, TREATS,
TREATS! Who wants a treat?
♪♪
What do we do now!?
RUN!
♪♪
I hope you're right about
the girls coming here.
Well, once we read Shadetail
Evergreen's warning
that the flower grants
wishes, it wasn't a stretch
to think they wished
themselves to the fair.
It's all they were
talking about.
Or maybe since we told them
they were too young to come,
they wished to become
grownups, then came here
and caused some
kind of trouble
that led to a
town-wide panic!
Yeah. Or that.
Twilight! Fluttershy!
Oh, thank goodness!
I know you're not
gonna believe it,
but it's me, Apple Bloom.
And I'm Scootaloo! We kinda
got turned into grownups!
And we thought we could
take the train here,
since we were old enough, but
we ended up in the wrong place,
just like you said we would!
And got lost.
Just like you said we would.
Then we met these foals
who led us to the fair
and we tried to give them
some grownup-style advice,
but it turned their
pet into a tornado
that might destroy
the whole town!
Goodness! A Whirling Mungtooth.
They are very rare, and just
the cutest little things
when they're not excited.
This one's excited.
Scootaloo: How do we calm him down!?
When they're young, a
Mungtooth forms a tight bond
with its caretaker.
They're the only ones who can
get them to stop spinning.
Spur's the one who really
took care of Bloofy.
We have to find her!
You all go look
for Spur.
Fluttershy and I
will do our best
to keep everypony
here safe.
♪♪
THAT'S Bloofy!?
I'm so sorry, Spur.
You knew what was best
for him all along.
And even though we
seem like grownups,
you were way more
responsible than us.
What do you mean
"seem" like grownups?
Uh, we don't have
time to explain.
Right now, we have
to stop this
and you're the only
one who can do it.
How!?
I'll show you. He mostly
just needs to see you.
Hey, there Bloofy-boo.
It's OK..!
♪♪
How did you know
what to do?
After years of
experience with animals,
I've picked up
a few things.
Well, one thing's
for sure.
Bloofy definitely earned
the most interesting
creature prize.
I'm sorry I didn't
listen to you.
We all are.
I guess grownups
aren't always perfect.
They sure aren't.
But young foals
pretending to be grownups
are even less so.
What do you mean?
There's only one petal left,
but I think the three of
you know what to wish for
and I'm pretty sure
Starswirl won't mind.
We wish we were foals again.
Hold on. You three are
actually younger than us!?
The flower turned
us into grownups,
so we figured we could
do whatever we wanted,
but I guess that's
not exactly true.
We did everything real
grownups told us not to
and caused all
kinds of trouble.
And things could have
been a lot worse.
I guess we were
pretty selfish...
I'm glad you
learned something.
That's what growing up is,
which is why you probably
shouldn't skip any of it.
I know we didn't make
the best impression,
but we sure would like to
visit you and Bloofy someday.
I guess that'd be
OK, on one condition:
You get a REAL
grownup to bring you.
DEAL!