Once upon a time,
in a magical land of Equestria...
...there were two regal sisters
who ruled together...
...and created harmony for all the land.
To do this, the eldest used her unicorn
powers to raise the sun at dawn...
...the younger brought out
the moon to begin the night.
Thus, the two sisters maintained balance
for their kingdom and their subjects:
All the different types of ponies.
But as time went on,
the younger sister became resentful.
The ponies relished and played in the day
her elder sister brought forth...
...but shunned and slept
through her beautiful night.
One fateful day, the younger unicorn refused
to lower the moon to make way for the dawn.
The elder sister tried to reason with her...
...but the bitterness in the young one's heart...
...had transformed her into a
wicked mare of darkness:
Nightmare Moon.
She vowed that she would shroud
the land in eternal night.
Reluctantly, the elder sister harnessed
the most powerful magic known to ponydom:
The Elements of Harmony!
Using the magic of the Elements of Harmony,
she defeated her younger sister...
...and banished her permanently in the moon.
The elder sister took on responsibility
for both sun and moon....
...and harmony has been maintained
in Equestria for generations since.
Hm... Elements of Harmony.
I know I've heard of those before.
But where?
My Little Pony, My Little Pony...
Aaaaah...
My Little Pony
I used to wonder what friendship could be.
Until you all shared its magic with me.
Big adventure
Tons of fun
A beautiful heart
Faithful and strong
Sharing kindness
It's an easy feat
And magic makes it all complete!
You have My Little Pony...
Do you know you are my very best friends?
There you are, Twilight!
Moondancer is having a little get-together
in the west castle courtyard.
You wanna come?
Oh, sorry girls. I got a lot
of studying to catch up on.
Does that pony do anything except study?
I think she's more interested
in books than friends.
I know I've heard of the Elements of Harmony.
Spike! Spike!!!
Spike?
There you are.
Quick, find me that old copy of
"Predictions and prophecies".
What's that for?
Well, it was a gift for Moondancer, but...
Oh, Spike. You know we don't
have time for that sort of thing.
But we're on a break!
No... no, no, no no no!
SPIKE!!!
It's over here!
Elements... elements, e e e... Aha!
Elements of Harmony... See: Mare in the Moon?
Mare in the Moon?
But that's just an old ponies' tale.
Mare... mare... AHA!
"The Mare in the Moon - myth
from olden pony times..."
"...a powerful pony, who
wanted to rule Equestria..."
"...defeated by the Elements of Harmony
and imprisoned in the moon."
"Legend has it that on the longest
day of the thousandth year..."
"...the stars will aid in her escape and
she will bring about nighttime eternal."
Spike! Do you know what this means?
No.
Take a note, please. To the Princess.
Okie dokie.
"My dearest teacher. My continuing studies
of pony magic have led me to discover..."
-"...that we're on the precipice of disaster."
-Hold on!
Preci... preci...
-Threshold.
-Threee...
Uh... Brink?
That something really bad is about to happen!
"For you see, the mythical Mare in
the Moon is in fact Nightmare Moon..."
"...and she's about to return to Equestria
and bring with her eternal night."
"Something must be done to make sure this
terrible prophecy does not come true."
"I await your quick response.
Your faithful student, Twilight Sparkle."
Twilight. Sparkle. Got it!
Great! Send it.
-Now?
-Of course!
I don't know, Twilight.
Princess Celestia is a little busy getting
ready for the Summer Sun Celebration.
And it's, like, the day after tomorrow.
That's just it, Spike.
The day after tomorrow is the thousandth
year of the Summer Sun Celebration.
It's imperative that
the Princess is told right away.
Impera... impera...
Important!
Okay, okay.
There! It's on its way.
But I wouldn't hold your breath.
Oh, I'm not worried, Spike.
The Princess trusts me completely.
In all the years she's been my mentor,
she's never once doubted me.
See? I knew she would wanna
take immediate action.
"My dearest, most faithful student, Twilight."
"You know that I value your diligence
and that I trust you completely."
"But you simply must stop
reading those dusty old books."
"My Dear Twilight. There is more to
a young pony's life than studying."
"So I'm sending you
to supervise the preparations..."
"...for the Summer Sun Celebration in
this year's location, Ponyville."
"And I have an even more essential
task for you to complete."
"Make some friends!"
Look on the bright side, Twilight.
The Princess arranged for you to stay in a library.
Doesn't that make you happy?
Yes! Yes it does. You know why?
Because I'm right.
I'll check on the preparations
as fast as I can...
...then get to the library and find
some proof of Nightmare Moon's return.
Then when will you make friends,
like the Princess said?
She said to check on preparations.
I am her student and I'll do my royal duty.
But the fate of Equestria does
not rest on me making friends.
Thank you, sirs.
Maybe the ponies in Ponyville have
interesting things to talk about?
Come on, Twilight. Just try.
Hello?
Well, that was interesting, all right.
Summer Sun Celebration:
Official Overseer's Checklist.
Number 1: Banquet preparations.
Sweet Apple Acres.
YEEHAW!
Let's get this over with.
Good afternoon. My name is Twilight Sparkle...
Well, howdy-do, miss Twilight?
A pleasure makin' your acquaintance.
I'm Applejack. We here at Sweet Apple Acres
sure do like makin' new friends.
Friends? Actually... I...
So, what can I do you for?
Well, I am in fact here to supervise
preparations for the Summer Sun Celebration.
And you're in charge of the food?
We sure as sugar are.
Would you care to sample some?
As long as it doesn't take too long.
Soup's on, everypony!
Now, why don't I introduce
y'all to the Apple family?
Thanks, but I really need to hurry.
This here's Apple Fritter,
Apple Bumpkin, Red Gala...
...Red Delicious, Golden Delicious, Caramel
Apple, Apple Strudel, Apple Tart, Baked Apple,
Apple Brioche, Apple Cinnamon Crisp...
Big Macintosh, Apple Bloom
aaaand Granny Smith.
Up and at 'em Granny Smith. We got guests.
Wha...? Soup's on?
I'm up, here I come, I'm comin'...
Why, I'd say they're already part of the family.
Okay. Well, I can see the food situation
is handled, so we'll be on our way.
Aren't you gonna to stay for brunch?
Sorry, but we have an awful lot to do...
Fine.
Food's all taken care of. Next is weather.
Ugh... I ate too much pie.
There's supposed to be a pegasus pony
named Rainbow Dash clearing the clouds.
Well, she's not doing a very good job, is she?
Uh... Excuse me?
Let me help you.
Oops. I guess I overdid it.
Um... uh, how about this?
My very own patented Rain-Blow Dry.
No no, don't thank me. You're quite welcome.
Let me guess, you're Rainbow Dash.
The one and only!
Why? You heard of me?
I heard you're supposed
to be keeping the sky clear.
I'm Twilight Sparkle and the Princess
sent me to check on the weather.
Yeah, yeah. That'll be a snap.
I'll do it in a jiffy. Just as soon
as I'm done practicing.
Practicing for what?
The Wonderbolts!
They're gonna perform at
the celebration tomorrow.
And I'm gonna show 'em my stuff.
-*The* Wonderbolts?
-Yup.
The most talented flyers in all of Equestria?
That's them!
Pfft... Please.
They'd never accept a pegasus who can't
even keep the sky clear for one measly day.
Hey. I could clear the sky in ten seconds flat.
Prove it.
Loop-de-loop around and WHAM!
What'd I say. Ten. Seconds. Flat.
I'd never leave Ponyville hanging.
You should see the look on your face.
You're a laugh, Twilight Sparkle.
I can't wait to hang out some more.
Wow. She's amazing!
Wait! It's kinda pretty once you get used to it.
Decorations. Beautiful...
Yes. The decor's coming along nicely.
This oughta be quick.
I'll be at the library in no time.
Beautiful indeed.
Not the decor. Her!
No, no, no... Oh my goodness no.
How are my spines? Are they straight?
Good afternoon.
Just a moment, please.
I'm in the zone as it were.
Oh yes! Sparkle always does
the trick, does it not?
Why, Rarity, you are a talent!
Now... um, how can I help youuuuaAARGH!
Oh my stars, darling! What ever
happened to your coiffure?
Oh, you mean my mane? Well, it's a long story.
I'm just here to check on the decorations
and then I'll be out of your hair.
Out of MY hair? What about YOUR hair?
Wait! Where are we going? HELP!
No, no, uh-uh.
Too green. Too yellow. Too puffy.
Not puffy enough. Too frilly. Too shiny.
Now go on, my dear.
You were telling me where you're from.
I've... urgh... been... sent...
from... Canterlot... to...
Canterlot?!
Oh, I am so envious. The glamor, the sophistication.
I've always dreamed of living there!
I can't wait to hear all about it.
We are gonna be the best of friends, you and I.
Emerald?! What was I thinking?
Let me get you some rubies!
Quick! Before she decides
to dye my coat a new color.
Wasn't she wonderful?
Focus, Casanova. What's next on the list?
Oh. Music. It's the last one.
Oh my. Um... Stop, please, everyone.
Excuse me, sir. I mean, no offense.
But your rhythm is just a teeny, tiny bit off.
Now follow me, please. A one.
A two. A one-two-three...
Hello!
Oh my. I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to frighten your birds.
I'm just here to check up on the music
and it's sounding beautiful.
I'm Twilight Sparkle.
What's your name?
Um... I'm Fluttershy...
I'm sorry, what was that?
My name is ...
Didn't quite catch that.
Well, um, it looks like your birds are back,
so I guess everything's in order.
Keep up the good work!
Ooookay.
Well, that was easy.
A BABY DRAGON!
Oh, I've never seen a baby dragon before.
He's so cute!
Well well well.
Oh my, he talks.
I didn't know dragons could talk.
That's just so incredibly wonderful. I...
I just don't even know what to say.
Well, in that case we better be going.
Wait, wait! What's his name?
I'm Spike.
Hi, Spike. I'm Fluttershy.
Wow! A talking dragon!
And what do dragons talk about?
-Well, what do you wanna know?
-Absolutely everything!
Well, I started out as a cute
little purple-and-green egg...
...and that's the story of my whole entire life.
Well, up until today.
Do you wanna hear about today?
Oh yes, please!
I am so sorry! How did we get here so fast?
This is where I'm staying while in Ponyville.
-And my poor baby dragon needs his sleep.
-No, I don't!
Awww, wook at that. He's so sweepy, he
can't even keep his wittle bawance.
Poor thing. You simply must get into bed!
Yes yes. We'll get right on that.
Well, goodnight!
Huh. Rude much?
Sorry, Spike. But I have to convince the
Princess that Nightmare Moon is coming...
...and we're running out of time!
I just need to be alone, so I can study...
...without a bunch of crazy ponies
trying to make friends all the time.
Now where's the light?
SURPRISE!
Surprise!
Hi! I'm Pinkie Pie and I threw
this party just for you!
Were you surprised, were you, were you?
Huh huh huh?
Very surprised.
Libraries are supposed to be quiet.
That's silly! What kind of welcome
party would this be if it were quiet?
I mean, DUH! BORING!
YouseeIsawyouwhenyoufirstgothereremember?
YouwereallhelloandIwasallGASPremember?
YouseeIneversawyoubeforeandifInever
sawyoubeforethatmeansyourenew!
Cause I know everypony,
and I mean everypony in Ponyville!
Andifyourenewthenyouhaventmetanyoneyetandifyou
haventmetanyoneyetyoumustnothaveanyfriends.
Andifyoudonthaveanyfriendsthenyoumustbelonely
andthatmademesosadandIhadanideaandthatswhyIGASP!
Illjustthrowagreatbigginormoussuperduperspectacular
welcomepartyandinviteeveryoneinPonyville!
See? And now you have lots and lots of friends!
Are you alright, sugar cube?
Awww, she's so happy, she's crying!
Hot sauce.
What? It's good!
Hey, Twilight! Pinkie Pie started
Pin the Tail on the Pony. Wanna play?
No! All the ponies in this town are CRAZY!
Do you know what time it is?
It's the eve of the Summer Sun Celebration.
Everypony has to stay up or they'll
miss the Princess raise the sun.
You really should lighten up Twilight.
It's a party!
Here I thought I'd have time to learn
more about the Elements of Harmony.
But, silly me, all this ridiculous
friendmaking has kept me from it!
"Legend has it that in the longest day
of the thousandth year..."
"...the stars will aid in her escape and
she will bring about everlasting night."
I hope the Princess was right.
I hope it really is just an old pony tale.
Come on, Twilight!
It's time to watch the sun rise!
Isn't this exciting?
AreyouexcitedcauseImexcited
Iveneverbeensoexcitedwell...
...exceptforthattimethatIsawyouwalking
intothistownandIwentGASP
But, I mean, really, who can top that?
Fillies and gentlecolts.
As mayor of Ponyville,
it is my great pleasure...
...to announce the beginning
of the Summer Sun Celebration!
In just a few moments our town will
witness the magic of the sunrise.
And celebrate this, the longest day of the year!
And now it is my great honor to
introduce to you the ruler of our land.
The very pony, who gives us the sun
and the moon each and every day.
The good, the wise, the bringer
of harmony to all of Equestria...
Ready?
...Princess Celestia!
This can't be good.
Remain calm, everypony.
There must be a reasonable explanation.
I love guessing games! Is she hiding?
She's gone!
She's good!
Oh no...
Nightmare Moon!
Oh, my beloved subjects!
It's been so long since I've seen your
precious little sun-loving faces.
What did you do with our Princess?!
Whoa there, Nelly...!
Why, am I not royal enough for you?
Don't you know who I am?
More guessing games!
Um... Pokey Smokes!
How about Queen Meanie?
No! Black Snooty, Black Snooty...!
Does my crown no longer count now that
I have been imprisoned for a thousand years?
Did you not recall the legend?
Did you not see the signs?
I did! And I know who you are!
You're the Mare in the Moon.
Nightmare Moon.
Well well well. Somepony who remembers me.
Then you also know why I'm here.
You're here to... to...
Remember this day, little ponies,
for it was your last.
From this moment forth...
THE NIGHT WILL LAST FOREVER!
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000