It is gorgeous out.
Just gorgeous!
Twilight! I... have...
lemme just...
Dear Twilight,
I am sure you are as excited as I am
about the upcoming wedding in Canterlot.
Wedding?!
I will be presiding over the ceremony,
but would very much like you and your friends
to help with the preparations
for this wonderful occasion.
Fluttershy, I would like you and your
songbird choir to provide the music.
Oh my goodness! What an honor!
Pinkie Pie, I can think of no one more
qualified than you to host the reception.
Applejack, you will be in charge
of the catering for the reception.
Well, color me pleased as punch!
Rainbow Dash, I would very much
appreciate it if you could perform
a sonic rainboom as the bride
and groom complete their I do's.
Yes!
Rarity, you will be responsible
for designing the dresses
for the bride and her bridesmaids.
Princess Celestia wants me to...
...wedding dress?
For a Canterlot wedding...
And as for you, Twilight, you will be
playing the most important role of all:
making sure that everything
goes as planned.
See you all very soon.
Yours, Princess Celestia.
But... I don't understand.
Who's getting married?
Oh, wait!
I was probably supposed
to give you this one first.
Princess Celestia cordially
invites you to the wedding of
Princess Mi Amore Cadenza,
and...
my brother?!
Season 2 | Episode 25
A Canterlot Wedding, part 1
Subbed and Synced by GrayJeager
GrayJeager@gmail.com
Fr.Jeager@gmail.com
http://www.youtube.com/user/GrayJeager3
http://grayjeager.blogspot.fr (french)
Your brother's getting married?
Congratulations, Twilight,
that's great news!
Yeah, great news... that I just got
from a wedding invitation!
Not from my brother,
but from a piece of paper!
Thanks a lot, Shining Armor.
I mean, really,
he couldn't tell me personally?
Hey, Twilight,
just thought you should know...
I'm making a really big decision
that changes everything.
Oh, nevermind, you'll hear about it
when you get the invitation.
Princess Mi Amore Cadenza?
Who in the hoof is that?!
Twilight? Are you okay?
Sorry, it's just that Shining Armor
and I have always been so close.
He's my B.B.B.F.F!
Big Brother Best Friend Forever?
Before I came here and learned
the importance of friendship,
Shining Armor was the only pony
I ever really accepted as a friend.
When I was just a filly,
I found it rather silly
To see how many other ponies I could meet
I had my books to read,
didn't know that I would ever need
Other ponies to make my life complete
But there was one colt that I cared for
I knew he would be there for me
My big brother,
best friend forever
Like two peas in a pod,
we did everything together
He taught me how to fly a kite
(Best friend forever)
We never had a single fight
(We did everything together)
We shared our hopes,
we shared our dreams
I miss him more than I realized
It seems...
Your big brother,
best friend forever
Like two peas in a pod,
you did everything together
And though he's so far away,
I hoped that he would stay
My Big Brother Best Friend
Forever
Forever...
As one of your PFFs...
Pony Friends Forever...
I wanna tell you that I think your
brother sounds like a real good guy.
He is pretty special.
I mean, they don't let just anypony
be Captain of the Royal Guard.
So let me get this straight.
We're helping out with the
wedding of not only a princess,
but a Captain of the Royal Guard?
I guess we are.
A sonic rainboom? At a wedding?!
Can you say "best wedding ever"!
Best wedding ever!
So you all get to help with
the big fancy wedding,
but I'm the one who gets
to host the bachelor party!
I have just one question,
what's a bachelor party?
Why the long face, sugarcube?
I'm just thinking about Shining Armor.
Ever since I moved to Ponyville,
we've been seeing each other less and less.
And now that he's starting
a new family with this...
"Princess Mi Amore Cal-whatshername",
we'll probably never see each other.
Come on, now. You're his sister.
He'll always make time for you.
Couldn't seem to make time
to tell me he was getting married.
What's with all the guards?
I'm sure they're just taking
the necessary precautions.
Royal weddings do bring out
the strangest ponies.
Now let's get going,
we've got work to do!
And you've got a big brother
to go congratulate.
Yeah. Congratulate.
And then give him a piece of my mind.
I've got something
to say to you, mister.
Twilie!
I've missed, you, kid.
How was the train ride, I-
How dare you not tell me in person
that you were getting married!
I'm your sister, for pony's sake!
It's not my fault!
Princess Celestia has requested
a major increase in security.
Didn't you see all the guards
at the train station?
Yeah, there's a big wedding coming up.
Maybe you heard about it?
It has nothing to do
with the wedding.
A threat has been made
against Canterlot.
We don't know who's responsible for it,
but Princess Celestia asked that
I help provide additional protection.
This, you need to see.
The burden of keeping Canterlot safe
and secure rests squarely on my shoulders.
Staying focused on the task at hand
has been my top priority.
Okay, okay, I get it.
You've got a really important job
protecting all of Canterlot
with a force field only you
can conjure up.
But still... how could you not tell me
about something as big as your wedding?
Am I not that important
to you any more?
Hey. You're my little sister.
Of course you're important to me.
But I'd understand if you didn't
want to be my best mare now.
You want me to be your best mare?
Well... yeah.
I'd be honored!
But I'm still pretty ticked you're marrying
somepony I don't even know!
When did you even meet this
"Princess Mi Amore Cadenza"?
Twilie, Princess Mi Amore Cadenza
is Cadance.
Your old foalsitter.
Cadance? As in the Cadance?
As in the greatest foalsitter
in all the history of foalsitters?!
You tell me, she was your foalsitter.
Ohmygoshohmygosh!
Cadance is only the
most amazing pony ever!
She's beautiful, she's caring,
she's kind...
I am so lucky to have you
as my foalsitter!
I'm the one who's lucky, Twilight.
You're a princess.
I'm just a regular old unicorn.
You are anything but
a regular old unicorn.
Sunshine, sunshine, ladybugs awake,
clap your hooves and do a little shake!
I am going for a hooficure
and that is that!
- You are not going.
- I am. I am...
How many unicorns can just
spread love wherever they go?
I only know of one!
And you're marrying her!
You're marrying Cadance,
you're marrying Cadance!
I hope I'm not interrupting
anything important.
Cadance!
Sunshine, sunshine, ladybugs awake,
clap your hooves and do a little shake!
What are you doing?
Cadance, it's me, Twilight!
I've gotta get back to my station.
But Cadance will be checking in with
all of you to see how things are going.
I think I speak for both of us when I say
we couldn't be more excited to have you here.
Right, dear?
Absolutely.
Well, we'll let you get to it.
Cake, check.
Ice sculpture, check.
Best darn bitesize apple fritter
you ever tasted...
Check.
I do. Do you?
I do!
Hiya, Princess!
Please, call me
Princess Mi Amore Cadenza.
Hiya, Princess Mi Amore Cadenza.
You come to check out what's
on the menu for your big day?
I have!
Delicious! I love, love, love them.
Aw, shucks. Why don't
you take a few to go?
I know how you brides can be.
So busy, you forget to get
a little somethin' in your belly.
Did... you see what she...
Oh, you should have seen
how she acted back there.
I don't know when she changed,
but she changed!
"Please, call me
Princess Mi Amore Cadenza."
Did I hear someone say my name?
Your highness!
Let me just start by saying
what an honor it is to play a role
in such a momentous occasion.
Is my dress ready?
Yes, of course.
I've been working on it ever since
I was given the assignment.
And I think you'll be pleased
with the results!
I was hoping for something with
more beading and a longer train.
Yes, of course.
And those should be a different color.
I think they're lovely.
Me too.
I love them.
Make them a different color.
Gee, maybe her name should be
"Princess Demandy-pants."
Okay, let me see.
We've been over the games...
The dances...
I think this reception is gonna
be perfect! Don't you?
Perfect!
...if we were celebrating
a six-year-old's birthday party.
Thank you!
Rest, my sister.
As always, I will guard the night.
Bet I can guess what
you're all thinking!
Cadance is the absolute
worst bride-to-be ever.
Who, me?
Spike! That goes on the cake.
Twilight, whatever are you talking about?
Cadance is an absolute gem!
Rarity, she was so demanding!
Well of course she was!
Why shouldn't she expect
the very best on her wedding day?
Applejack, did you know that after she told
you how much she just 'love-love-loved'
your hors-d'oeuvres,
she threw them in the trash?
Aw, she was probably just
trying to spare my feelings.
No, she was just being fake,
and totally insincere!
She did raise her voice at one of
my birds during rehearsal.
See? Rude!
But... he was singing really off-key.
Pinkie Pie, you had to have noticed
how Cadance treated-
Nevermind.
Rainbow Dash, you're with me, right?
Sorry Twi, been too busy prepping
for my sonic rainboom
to pay much attention to
the bride's bad attitude.
The princess is about to get married.
I'm sure any negative behavior
she might be displaying
is simply the result of nerves.
And I'm sure it's the result
of being an awful pony
who doesn't deserve to even know
Shining Armor let alone marry him!
Think maybe you're being just a tiny bit
possessive of your brother?
I am not being possessive!
And I am not taking it out on Cadance!
You're all just too caught up
in your wedding planning
to notice that maybe there
shouldn't even be a wedding!
Twilie!
Your big brother's looking
pretty good, don't you think?
Everything okay?
We need to talk.
I think you're making a big-
Oh, hi, sweetie.
She sure has a way
of sneaking up on people.
Could I speak to you for a moment,
dear?
Better see what she wants.
Look, we need to talk.
I'm here to talk.
- Look, she's okay-
- Just listen to me.
I'm listening, I'm listening...
I thought I made it perfectly clear
I didn't want you to wear that.
This was my favorite uncle's.
And...?
And I think I should wear it.
Are you disagreeing with me?
I guess I am!
Oh dear, are you getting
another one of your headaches?
Feeling better?
She isn't just unpleasant and rude,
she's downright evil!
Twilight!
Let her go.
It seemed like she had something else
she wanted to tell me.
Who goes there?
Stay indoors, Twilight Sparkle.
Shining Armor's in real trouble!
You have to help-
Dresses?
What are you...?
Can you believe it?
We're gonna be Princess Mi Amore
Cadenza's new bridesmaids!
"New" bridesmaids?
What happened to her "old" bridesmaids?!
She didn't say.
But she did tell us that she would
love love love it if we'd fill in for them.
Seeing as we've been working
so hard and everything.
And you had your doubts about her.
Told you she was an absolute gem!
You sure this is what I should wear?
Doesn't seem all that aerodynamic.
I'll see what I can do.
This is so exciting!
I know! This is awesome!
Looks like I really am on my own.
Perfect, girls. No need to rush!
Then of course, Cadance will enter.
I'll say a few words,
and then we'll begin with the vows.
Shining Armor, you'll get
the ring from your Best Mare.
Do you?
I do!
Hey... has anypony seen Twilight?
I'm here!
I'm not gonna stand next to her.
And neither should you!
I'm sorry, I don't know
why she's acting like this.
Maybe we should just ignore her.
You have to listen to me!
Oh goodness! Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Ya sure about that?
I've got something to say!
She's evil!
She's been horrible to my friends...
She's obviously done something
to her bridesmaids...
And if that wasn't enough,
I saw her put a spell on my brother
that made his eyes go all...!
Why are you doing this to me?!
Because you're evil!
Evil! And if I don't stop you,
you're gonna ruin my brother's life!
You want to know why my eyes went all...?
Because ever since I started having
to perform my protection spell,
I've been getting terrible migraines.
Cadance hasn't been casting spells on me,
she's been using her magic to heal me!
And she decided to
replace her bridesmaids
because she found out the only reason
they wanted to be in the wedding
was so that they could
meet Canterlot royalty!
And if she hasn't been on her
best behavior with your friends,
it's because with me being so busy,
she's had to make all the decisions
about the wedding!
I was just trying to-
She's completely stressed out
because it's really important to her
that her big day be perfect!
Something that obviously
wasn't important to you.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to go and comfort my bride.
And you can forget about
being my best mare.
In fact, if I were you, I wouldn't
show up to the wedding at all.
C'mon, y'all.
Let's go check on the princess.
- I was...
- You have a lot to think about.
Maybe I was being overprotective.
I could've gained a sister.
But instead... I just lost a brother.
He was my Big Brother,
Best Friend
Forever...
And now, we'll never do anything
Together...
I'm sorry!
You will be.