♪♪
Ahem! Where
ya goin?
Since you three were unable to
retrieve my Bewitching Bell,
we need another source
of great magical power
to defeat Twilight
and her friends.
♪ [plodding music] ♪
He's gone!
I don't trust him.
None of us do.
Which is why double-crossing
him with his own bell
will be so satisfying.
If we can figure
out how to use it.
Hmmm.
Twilight Sparkle
may be the worst....
But she does know stuff.
She once said the
archives in Canterlot
has a restricted area.
Celestia and Luna love
to hoard information
for themselves. If there's
an answer, it's there.
My triumphant
return to Canterlot?
I like the sound of that...
Oh my gosh! Road trip!
♪♪
Sorry to interrupt. We
know you're busy planning
The Summer Sun Celebration
as we requested. But..
Oh! Things seem...
calmer
than we would
have expected.
No complaints here.
With the exception of
the odd trivia night,
I've made a lot
of progress
since the Royal
Swanifying Ceremony.
You may not know this about me,
but I occasionally freak out!
That was a joke. I
wanted to show you
with the Summer
Sun Celebration
how much I've improved.
So I focused on delegating
and trusting others!
It's been GREAT!
That's.. actually what we
came to talk to you about.
This may be the last
Summer Sun Celebration
you'll need to plan.
Did I do something wrong?
Of course not. It's just
that the Celebration
has always been about
us. My defeat of Luna...
And, thanks to you
and your friends,
my reunion with
my sister.
Now that we're leaving,
we don't see a need
for the holiday any longer.
Now that you're...?
My sister and I have decided
the time for us to retire
is upon us. You and
your friends have proven
you are ready to
lead Equestria.
So let this be the last
Summer Sun Celebration
as Equestria leaves behind
the old to embrace the new.
My goodness! How are YOU
feeling about all this?
Something like this could
definitely send you
into full
freaky-outy mode.
I'm actually fine. But if
this is going to be the last
Summer Sun Celebration,
I want to make sure
it's the best
Celebration ever.
Please don't give
us more work...
us more work.....
So even though
everything was done,
I thought of a few
last-minute changes
I could use
your help with.
Gah! I knew it!
Discord: Oh! The end
of a beloved holiday?
Last-minute changes
to a celebration?
That sounds positively...
Chaotic!
What are YOU doing here?
I've known Celestia and Luna
longer than any of you!
I terrorized them; they
turned me into stone...
If this is the last
Summer Sun Situation,
I simply can't miss it.
Well, I see I've arrived
just in time for the
"Twilight gives her
friends an impossibly long
and overly detailed
list" predicament!
I guess some-draconequis
isn't the know-it-all
he thinks he is!
♪♪
This is it?
What?
We were kinda with
Discord on this one...
No more crazy lists.
No more freaking out.
With your help, I
know we've got this.
Oh! Character
growth is so boring.
Do I at least get
my own note card?
There. Now, I need to
go rewrite my speech,
but if you all look at
your cards, you'll see-
Can't talk now! Have so much
to get done before sunrise!
Why are so many ponies up
in the middle of the night?
It's that silly sun holiday.
How many holidays do you
ponies HAVE? No matter.
Getting into the castle
won't be a problem.
Are you sure
about that?
♪ [sting] ♪
Oh. Those are
new. But even so...
♪ [military snare drum] ♪
Transfer. Have to
head inside. Open up.
♪ [military snare drum] ♪
♪ [chimes] ♪
Right. Of course. Heh.
Uh, do yours get glitchy, too?
More medallions, more
problems. Am I right?
They've increased
security into the castle.
This is going to be more
challenging than I thought.
Could you NOT go popping us
all over the place please?
Time is of the
essence! Let's.. go team!
We need to know what we're
doing before we go and do it.
Pinkie, you and I
are givin' Braeburn
and the Appleoosan ponies
some adjustments to the menu.
Fluttershy and I are meeting
the pegasi from Cloudsdale
to give them changes
to the weather.
Spike, we're going to update
The Flaming Sky Firework
unicorn troupe with
Twilight's new vision.
And I'm supposed to...
Make sure Discord doesn't
do anything.. Discord-y!?
Well, that's
annoyingly specific...
Increased security on a
crowded holiday with Twilight
and their friends bumbling
around? This is impossible!
Oh, no. This is perfect!
We need a distraction
and those ridiculous
ponies just gave it to us!
Now, do exactly
as I tell you...
♪♪
Step away from the wagons!
Official food tasters here
on official
food-tasting business!
Huh. It ain't gonna be easy,
but I think we can whip
up these new cookies
Twilight wants
before sunrise.
If anypony can handle some
last-minute bakin', Braeburn,
it's y'all.
We brought plenty
for the celebration,
but if she keeps testin',
we might be in trouble.
But I see a
suspicious-looking COOKIE!!
♪ [scary music] ♪
You OK?
I feel... weak
all of a sudden.
♪♪
Is somepony back there?
What is it!?
Everypony! Get
away from the food
till we figure out
what's goin' on!
The princess
wants WHAT!?
Just what's on that
little card. No big deal.
No big dea..!? It's a much more
aggressive weather pattern
then what was
originally ordered!
This is very irregular!
We'll need to-
No! First we must...
Wait! We, Oh..!
Take a breath!
Let it out slowly.
Tell the princess
we will do our best.
We're sure you're
doing an excellent job.
Oh! Yeah. Totally.
You're not gonna panic
and screw it up at all.
I-I-I'm not built for
high pressure situations!
Golly. Sounds like
you need some help.
Who are you?
Somepony who's organized
enough to handle
the small stuff so you can
focus on the BIG picture!
The big...? YES!
That sounds right!
Ha, ha. This kind of weather
has to be handled delicately.
Good thing I'm here. I'll
take care of everything.
♪ [fanfare] ♪
Whoa!
The Flaming Sky Firework
Troupe is a marvel.
We take pride in what we do.
These last-minute changes
aren't too challenging,
are they?
Ha! The more challenging, the
better! We aim to astound.
Now, if you don't mind, we DO
have a new routine to prepare.
Horns at the ready!
♪♪
Very impressive!
Thank you. Unfortunately,
we have no room
for anypony else at
this time. Ahem. I'm sorry?
Crackle Cossette.
And I don't want to join
your silly little troupe.
Pardon me?
Oh! I meant no offense! It
just seems a pity for unicorns
to waste their talents on
something so... inconsequential.
Unicorns wield magic.
We are the most POWERFUL
ponies in the land.
Don't you ever feel you're
destined for more than...
...performances?
It's all coming together!
I really think this is
going to be the best
Summer Sun
Celebration EVER!
You've done an
outstanding job!
We've ALL done an
And what about me?
You'll be happy to know that
I have been watching myself
all night and I have yet
to do ONE Discord-y thing!
Luna: Now that truly
is amazing.
Twilight, we know you
had, uh, difficulties
using the amulet to
raise the sun and moon.
We thought perhaps
a practice session
before the festivities
might be in order?
That's... a good idea.
Thank you all. So much.
♪♪
I sure am
proud'a her.
Yeah! She
finally realizes
things will turn
out fine,
even when she isn't
micromanaging
every little detail.
Braeburn?! What's wrong!?
Earth ponies. Sick. Food
missin'. Can't.... bake... anything...
Something's wrong
with the weather!
Storms, hurricanes,
fog! You name it.
It's a disaster
out there!
Rarity! Please
inform Her Highness
that we will not
be performing.
A simple fireworks
show is beneath us!
We're BETTER than that.
What the...? Everything
was fine a minute ago.
Apparently, a lot can
change in a minute.
♪♪
It's total chaos
out there!
Don't look
at me!
What are we gonna do!?
Twilight: Do about what?
Ah! What are YOU doing here!?
I forgot these.
You guys OK?
Twilight, we're
sorry but-
But! Er. We don't
know what to do,
now that everything's
all ready!
Ha ha ha!
I guess I was
TOO organized!
I'll try to come up with
a few last-minute errands
for you before
sunrise.
Well, that's a relief!
Explain to me why we
didn't tell her the truth?
Twilight is finally learning
not to let her stress
get the better of her!
If she finds out
everything went wrong,
it could be
devastating!
She would be
so upset!
She'll totally
freak out!
Well, what do
y'all suggest?
Oo-oo-ooh! Let's just fix it
all before she notices!
No lying necessary!
I guess...
We'd need a miracle.
We HAVE a miracle!
Don't we?
I suppose I COULD
fix everything...
But isn't the
real miracle here
the miracle of teamwork
and character growth?
Oh, come on!
Discord is right.
Twilight needs US.
Whatever happened,
we can fix this.
What DID happen?
Best. Road trip. EVER!
♪♪
Even if I was an
actual doctor,
I would have no
idea what's wrong.
There's gotta
be a reason.
Something got
'em all sick.
Maybe the food?
I ate the food too! Does
that mean I'm sick? Oh, no!
Nope. I feel fine.
♪ [mysterious music] ♪
♪♪
♪ [heroic music] ♪
I don't know how
this happened!
I'm going to be
FIRED for sure!
Rainbow Dash and
the Wonderbolts
will have ALL the weather
rounded up any minute.
AHHHH! [thud]
Or not!
Not here.
The Archives are in a
different part of the castle.
What about aiming
for perfection?
We've set our
sights higher.
Higher than perfection?
Higher than putting
on a silly little show
for the other ponies.
But you were so excited
before! What changed!?
♪♪
You two just enjoy
the festivities!
I have a few surprises
in store for-
Yes, Discord?
Oh! Well, don't mind me. I'm
just here for the chaos.
Oh-oh-oh. And here we go!
What is Rainbow Dash doing?
Pinkie? Is
this soup?
Yes! I... was
really hungry?
Nopony understands
wanting to take pride
in your work
more than I do!
You could do more
with your magic
than make frilly
dresses!
Pfft! Nopony makes
frills anymore!
This season is actually
all about simplicity and-
Not the point, Rarity!
Princess!
I BEG your forgiveness.
It's entirely MY fault!
What is?
That!
Oh...um! Just a slight hiccup
in the weather! Ha, ha.
♪♪
Applejack? What
is going on?
I TOLD y'all this
was a bad idea
but nopony ever
LISTENS TO ME!
That's IT!
Ooof!
I thought everything was
fine! What is going on!?
Everything was going fine.
Until it totally wasn't.
We tried to fix
it ourselves...
Why didn't
you tell me!?
We didn't want
you to freak out.
And you thought NOT
telling me everything
was a total disaster
would avoid a freak-out!?
When you say it like that, it
sounds like a really bad plan.
Here it comes...
I know how I used to react.
But I really have changed!
Panicking won't
solve anything.
But we can handle whatever
problems come our way,
as long as we handle
them... together!
Celestia: Spoken like a
true leader.
How can we help?
I love a good to-do list!
So tell me exactly
what happened
so we can figure out exactly
what to do to fix it!
♪ [military snare drum] ♪
♪♪
♪ [royal fanfare] ♪
This celebration has
always been a reminder
not to fear the night,
for there is always a new
day to look forward to.
But as we look towards
Equestria's future,
I am sad to say that
today will be the last
Summer Sun Celebration.
...because there is something
even more important
to celebrate.
There are two ponies
who have watched over us
night and day for as
long as we can remember.
We will no longer commemorate
their battle or their reunion.
Instead, we will take
this day to celebrate
how much they mean
to all of us.
From this day forward
today will be known as..
The Festival of
the Two Sisters!
We don't know
what to say...
♪♪
Hee hee! A brand-new holiday?
You're my kinda princess!
I'm just glad we
pulled it off.
About that... We just wanted
to say.. we're real sorry.
You did tell us
you'd changed.
As your friends, we
should have trusted you.
Next time you say you're
not gonna freak out,
we'll believe you.
Good. Because I'm sure there's
going to plenty of things
I'll need my best
friends' help with.
Whee!
Whoa!
You know, it really does seem
like you just might be ready
for whatever comes
next, Your Majesty.
So...? Did you find what
you were looking for?
Once again, I've found success
where you all find failure!
I have located
what I sought
and tomorrow I will set
out to retrieve it.
When I return,
Equestria will finally
be ours for the taking.
Hmph!
Oh, stop pouting.
You knew you couldn't
stay that buff.
You had to return all the life
force to those earth ponies
so Grogar doesn't
suspect anything.
I don't have to like it.
Well, I don't like
that we worked so hard
to destroy their party and
they still pulled it off,
but you don't see
ME complaining!
Our goal wasn't to destroy;
it was to distract.
And now we have
exactly what we need.
And no time to waste.
We have to master the Bell
before Grogar returns.
We've managed to stay one step
ahead of everypony so far...
You know.. It really was
super-easy to get all those
earth ponies and
pegasi and unicorns
to turn on each other.
It was, wasn't it. Now that
is something to think about...