I still can't believe you're
letting me stay here.
As your pupil.
Shining Armor's a
father! I'm an aunt!
Your first friendship
lesson is going to be...
reuniting with Sunburst!
And yes, that's me. Yep.
Ha ha. Important wizard.
The baby is an alicorn!?
So, she could be a
super strong flyer
and have crazy baby magic.
Without the Heart, the Crystal
Empire is about to be buried
under a mountain
of ice and snow!
Regular subtitles
by YayPonies
Eat all muffins!
http://yayponies.eu/
So, not only can
we not take part
in a fabulous,
ancient ceremony,
but we're also about
to be frozen solid!
Without the Crystal Heart's
magical protection,
the entire city is about to
become a winter wasteland.
But what about
when King Sombra
ruled the
Crystal Empire
and the Crystal
Heart was missing?
The city wasn't
covered in snow then.
The Heart wasn't missing.
It was still in the Castle.
King Sombra had
just hidden it.
I'm afraid Twilight
is correct.
And the storm clouds
are already forming.
I can totally fly up there
and bust those puppies.
No problem.
I wouldn't advise it,
Rainbow Dash.
Those storm clouds are not
like the ones you know.
This far north, the weather
has a will of its own
and now it will
only grow stronger,
enveloping everything
in its path.
Including the
Crystal Empire.
And us along with it
There's gotta be something.
I know Princess Twilight
is keen on the two of us
rekindling our friendship,
but it's been so long.
I don't see how anything on
that list is going to help.
I know, right? It's not
like there's some spell
that would magically compel us
to pick up where we left off.
Oh, actually, there's several.
Mistmane's Material Amity,
Rockhoof's Rapport,
Flashprance's Fellowship...
But I get the
feeling the Princess
isn't looking for a spell.
Definitely not.
Got it!
"...and if all else
fails, ask them to share
an embarrassing moment
from their past,
maybe even something
they regret."
Uh, I don't see how
that would help.
Uh, yeah. We should just
get out of your mane.
It's pretty obvious this isn't
going how Twilight hoped
and I'm sure you have plenty
of important work to do.
What? Oh. Right. Yes.
No rest for the wizardly.
Come on, Spike.
There must be a spell that can
restore the Crystal Heart.
Perhaps.
But it isn't something
that either of us know.
The library here at the
Castle is nearly as extensive
as the one in Canterlot.
There's a good chance we
can find something there.
Can you hold off the storm?
Yes, for a time, but even our
magic will eventually succumb
to the power of
the Frozen North.
We will do what we can,
but you must hurry.
I don't know how long it will
take to find the right spell,
but you should probably
tell the crowd outside
to get somewhere warm.
And try not to mention
the Crystal Heart.
We don't want to start a panic.
Yes, ma'am!
Come on, girls!
I'm going to need
all of your help;
the Crystal library
is enormous.
You can count on us, Twiley!
AHHHHHHH!
Where'd she go?
This way!
Well, Spike, looks like my
biggest fears came true.
I wouldn't be surprised
if Twilight decides
to give up on me entirely.
It's not your fault.
I'm the one who said all
we needed was this list.
It's not the list, Spike.
Or you. Or Twilight.
I'm the one Sunburst doesn't
want to be friends with.
I don't remember him saying
he didn't want to be friends.
He didn't have to say it.
Well, Twilight obviously thinks
you're worth being
friends with and I do too.
Aw thanks, Spike. At
least I have two friends,
even if one of them
has dragon breath.
Um, that's not dragon
breath. It's freezing!
Oh. You're right!
But I thought the Crystal
Heart was supposed to keep
the cold weather out.
It is, unless something's
happened! Come on!
We're just saying that it
might not be the best idea
to stay outside.
I camped out all
night for this spot.
I'm not about to
just give it up.
Still, when you think about it,
the view is just as good
a little further back,
like inside your house.
The Crystalling ceremony
is one of our most
sacred traditions
and when that foal is held
before the Crystal Heart,
I plan to be as close to
the action as possible.
Honestly, I don't know
if there's gonna
be a Crystalling.
The truth is the
baby's an alicorn
and her magic's plum crazy
so you might not want to
be that close after all.
A baby alicorn? Wow. I
can't wait to see that!
Oh, those little wings
are probably so cute!
I know, right?
Look, I am 100% sure the
Crystalling isn't happening.
No Crystalling, huh?
Then why are they
starting a fireworks show?
WOO-HOO!
Young filly!
Whee!
Come back here!
Come to your Auntie Pinkie Pie!
Bridlebuck's Boat Chants,
Hayhoof's Intonements,
Mystic Maps and Mazes.
Anything up there?
Not yet. I'm not even sure
how these are organized.
Geeeeya!
Shining Armor, I thought you
were taking care of the baby.
I'm trying!
Whoo hoo hoo!
Gotcha!
Or not.
Whee!
What is going on!
You want the long or
the short version?
Short?
The baby's an alicorn and
she accidentally destroyed
the Crystal Heart so Twilight
and Cadance are looking
for a spell to put
it back together
and save the Crystal Empire
from turning into a giant
wasteland of ice and snow.
Oh.
What about this? Trotter's
Tome of Reliquary?
I think this is it!
Spell of Relic Reconstitution!
I can't believe we found it.
It's a good thing too.
Without this, I don't
know what we'd do.
Oops.
That spell was the only thing
we found in the whole library
that was even close
to what we needed.
I'm so sorry,
Twilight!
It's not your fault, Starlight.
None of us were
expecting any of this.
Do you think you can
remember the spell?
I only read it through once!
Well, if anypony can
exactly remember something
she read for the first
time two minutes ago,
it's you, Twilight.
I'll try, but I'm not
sure how long it'll take.
Is quickly an option?
I'll help if I can.
But we should evacuate
the city just in case.
You need to lead everypony
to the train station
before the tracks freeze over.
We will. But between
you and Twilight,
I'm sure you'll
remember the spell.
I only hope this spell
is the one we need.
Is there anything I can do?
I don't think so. I'm just
sorry about your lesson.
That doesn't matter now.
Sunburst and I don't have
anything in common anyway.
He's a big important wizard
and I'm relearning everything
I ever thought I knew.
Sunburst? I don't
recognize the name,
but if he's an
important wizard,
you should
bring him here.
Maybe he'll know what to
do if the spell fails.
Of course!
You better go with her, Spike.
Sunburst! Haven't
you looked outside?
Snow? That's not right.
The Crystal Heart...
...is gone. The baby...
Shining Armor and Cadance's
baby. It's an alicorn.
Really!?
Really! And her magic
is a little berserk
and, well, I guess she
destroyed the Heart.
But Twilight thinks
she can fix it
and Princess Cadance
thought you could help.
Me?
Of course! You're an important
wizard in the Crystal Empire.
It just makes sense.
Right.
Right, right, right, right.
You know, I'd like to
help. I-I really would.
I-I just have so much, um...
important wizard work
to do around here.
Huh?
You can't stay here!
Did I mention this was
a Royal Crystalling?
When the Crystaller holds
the young one aloft,
all of the Empire will
share their joy and light
and the Crystal Heart
will beat stronger
than it ever has before.
It really is a moving ceremony.
I really don't think
it's going to happen.
Come on! It's freezing out here!
Uh, this is the Crystal Empire.
We've seen snow before.
Not like this!
We don't have time to argue.
Princess Cadance has decided
to evacuate the city.
But the Crystalling!
I don't know if we'll
ever have another
Crystalling again.
The Crystal Heart is shattered.
It's not safe here!
That's what we've been
trying to tell you!
Sunburst, I know you're busy,
but did you hear what I said?
Oh, I heard you,
but-but like I said,
when you're an important
wizard the work just piles up.
Sunburst!
Look, Starlight, I
want to help, I do.
But I can't. I wish I could.
What do you mean?
Fixing an ancient relic?
I-I can't even come close to
doing something like that!
But I thought you were
an important wizard.
Well, you were wrong! OK?
I'm not an important wizard!
I'm not even a wizard at all!
I know it's hard for
you to understand,
but not all of us end
up achieving greatness!
What? Why wouldn't
I understand that?
Really? You're the protégé of
the Princess of Friendship.
I don't think she picks
just anypony for that.
Technically, she's more of
a student than a protégé.
Whatever. I'm sorry I'm not
the big, important wizard
you were expecting.
Sunburst! I don't care if
you're a wizard or not.
I'm just surprised. You always
knew so much about magic.
I mean, look at all these books!
Yeah, well, reading
about magic is one thing,
but you don't know what it
was like at Magic School,
to know so much and not
be able to do any of it!
Well, you don't know what it
was like to be left behind!
And then getting so bitter
that you steal the cutie marks
from an entire village
and then get defeated
by Twilight and her friends.
So you travel through
time to get back at them,
but they beat you again and
teach you about friendship,
but you're so terrified ponies
will find out what you did
that you can't make any friends!
Did you really
travel through time?
See? I told you
he'd be impressed.
I'm sorry we lost touch.
Maybe if I had reached out,
you could have helped
me at Magic School
and I could have
helped you to...
Not become totally evil?
Let's just say
I know what it's like
to have something you're
not exactly proud of.
You showed up thinking
I was some big wizard.
I'm sorry. I should
have told you the truth.
It's fine. At least
we worked it all out.
I think Twilight
would be proud of us.
Well, if you ever want
to tell her about it,
we should probably leave now!
I forgot to tell you,
they're evacuating the city!
You need to get to
the train station,
unless you've got a spell here
that will drive back
the Frozen North
and fix the Crystal Heart
so the baby can have
her Crystalling?
The Crystalling. Of course!
Push them back, my sister!
This way!
Just a little bit
further, y'all!
The station's just ahead!
We have to go back!
I know how to stop this!
Uh, I think that's everything.
It looks right to me,
but there's only
one way to find out.
The spell failed. I don't
know what else to do.
An old student of
mine believes he does.
The baby did this!?
I tried putting it
back together with...
...the Spell of Relic
Reconstitution.
That won't do it.
The Crystal Heart's been
around for millennia.
Restoring a relic like this is
magic way beyond one spell.
You'd need to combine
it with something else,
something unique to
the relic itself,
something that strengthens it
and provides it with power.
The Crystalling!
Combining that spell
with the light and love
of everypony gathered for the
ceremony, together with...
Somnambula's Weather Abjuration
to clear away the snow and...
A little Fledgling's
Forbearance for the parents.
That should curb the little
one's power fluctuations.
You must be Sunburst.
Starlight said you
were a powerful wizard.
Oh, I'm no wizard.
Huh? What?
But he studied magic
his whole life!
You should see his house!
And since no pony
has any better ideas,
what do we have to lose?
I had planned on asking
Twilight to be our Crystaller,
but since it seems
like she'll be busy...
I'd be honored.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Citizens, may I present
the newest member
of the Crystal Empire!
She's beautiful.
Oh! It's just so moving.
Best. Crystalling. Ever!
For a Pony who isn't great at
magic, you did pretty well.
Indeed.
I'm glad to see
you've found a way
to share your unique
gift, Sunburst.
You may be more of a
wizard than you think.
You would not believe
the crazy weather
that delayed our train!
Came out of nowhere!
But it was all worth it to see
this peaceful little angel.
Aww so sweet, come
to your grandmare.
Yeah. Peaceful now, anyway.
I suppose that spell
really did the trick.
Aaaah!
Achoo!
We have Sunburst
to thank for that.
I hope he takes his role
as Crystaller seriously.
Something tells me the baby
will need a pony like him
to look to for magical advice.
Cadence, darling,
aren't we going to name
the poor little dear or
are we going to spend
the entire visit just
calling her "the baby?"
We were thinking, Flurry Heart.
You know, to remember
the occasion.
Oh goodness! How
could anypony forget?
I think it's lovely.
Well, I think you're
the Crystal Empire's
big, important wizard,
whether you like it or not.
I don't know if I'll have
time for any wizarding.
I'm a Crystaller now.
That's a big responsibility.
I can't think of
anypony more qualified.
Just promise you'll
stay in touch?
Like I'd ever lose touch
with my oldest friend.
What's wrong, Twilight?
I don't know, Spike.
I think I have a lot to
learn about being a teacher.
What are you talking about?
Your lesson went perfectly.
Starlight and Sunburst
got over their past
and rekindled their friendship.
No thanks to me.
I know a lot happened; I
just wish I could have given
my pupil the attention
she deserves.
Well, I know she needed to
be put on the right path,
but giving her the space
to make her own decisions
worked pretty well.
Isn't that how
Celestia taught you?
You know, I never thought
about it, but I guess it is.
Maybe you're a better
teacher than you thought.