Not too fast now, Angel bunny.
You don't wanna get a tummy ache.
You really should eat more
than that, don't you think?
It's not playtime yet.
I know you wanna run, but...
...just three more bites.
Two more bites?
One more bite?
Pretty please.
Oh... goodness.
Are you okay?
Are you coughing because there's
a carrot stuck in your throat?
Because you need some water?
Because of that giant cloud
of scary black smoke?
I'll take that as a yes.
Help! Help!
Please? Help?
There's... there's a horrible cloud of smoke.
It's headed this way and...
Don't be such a scaredy-pony. It's just me.
Future Equestria ball-bouncing record holder.
246... 247...
This calls for a celebration!
Oh... No, Pinkie Pie.
This is no time for celebration.
This is a time for panic. For...
I'm gonna need balloons!
One for everypony in Ponyville.
There's... there's smoke.
And... and where there's
smoke, there's fire. And...
Let's see...
-That's 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6...
-...254, 255...
No, wait.
7!
Pinkie Pie! Now I have to start over.
We're all gonna have to start over.
In a new village. Because ours is gonna be...
Hey Rainbow Dash! Wait up!
Oh, please. This is an emergency.
I need everypony to...
Listen up!
Smoke is spreading over all of Equestria.
That's what I've been trying to...
But don't worry.
I've just received a letter from Princess Celestia
informing me that it is not coming from a fire.
Oh, thank goodness.
It's coming from a dragon.
A... d-d-d-dragon...?
What in the name of all things cinnamon swirled
is a full-grown dragon doin' here in Equestria?
Sleeping.
According to Princess Celestia,
he's taking a nap.
His snoring is what's causing all the smoke.
He should really see a doctor.
That doesn't sound healthy at all.
Well, at least he's not snoring fire.
What are we meant to do about it?
I'll tell you what we're meant to do.
Give 'im a boot. Take that!
And that!
We need to encourage him
to take a nap somewhere else.
Princess Celestia has given us
this mission and we must not fail.
If we do, Equestria will be covered in smoke
for the next one hundred years.
Huh. Talk about getting your beauty sleep.
All right, everypony.
I need you to gather supplies quickly.
We've got a long journey ahead of us.
Let's meet back here in less than an hour.
Okay, girls! You heard her.
The fate of Equestria is in our hoofs.
Do we have what it takes?
We can do it!
Um... Actually...
Oh... I mean...
Much better! Onward!
Let's go!
Um... let's not?
All right, girls. Listen up.
I'm mapping out the fastest route...
...but we've all got to keep a good pace if we
expect to make it up the mountain by nightfall.
M-m-mountain?
The dragon is in that cave at the very top.
Look pretty cold up there.
You bet it is. The higher you go,
the chillier it gets.
Good thing I've brought my scarf.
Ooo... Pretty.
Oh, yeah. That'll keep you nice and cozy.
Um... excuse me. Twilight?
-I know you're busy, but...
-Uh-huh.
Oh, we could go this way.
-But if I could just have a second...
-Uh-huh.
Now, we wanna avoid that.
So, um... I was thinking that...
Um... maybe I should just stay here at Ponyville.
-Uh-huh.
-Oh! Good.
I'll stay here and...
Wait! You have to come.
Your way with wild animals
will surely come in handy.
I don't think I...
Oh, and don't worry about your
little friends in the meadow.
Spike's got it covered while you're gone.
You can count on me.
Hey! Hey! Wait!
I don't know I think he's up to the task. Maybe...
But... but...
Are you sure you want
Fluttershy to come along?
I mean, that pony is afraid of her own shadow.
She's just gonna slow us down.
Oh, she's just a little nervous.
Once we get going, I'm sure she'll be fine.
All right, girls!
Move out!
But... but...
Wow... What was that?
That is what it sound like
when a dragon snores.
It's... it's so...
...high.
Well, it IS a mountain.
I'm gonna fly up there and check it out!
Hold on now. I think
we should all go up together.
Safety in numbers and all.
Oh, all right.
I hear the only thing that sparkles
more than the dragon's scales...
...are the jewels they use to build their nests.
If I play my cards right, I might be
able to convince him to part with a few.
Welcome to my cave, Rarity?
Care for a diamond?
Girls! This is no laughing matter!
Fluttershy, you're the expert on wild creatures.
What do you think the dragon will be like?
Fluttershy?
Hey! What are you waiting for?
An invitation?
Ooo! I think I have one in my bag!
It... it's so... so...
...steep.
Well, it IS a cliff.
You could just... oh, I don't know, fly up here?
Come on, Fluttershy, you can do it.
Flap those wings.
O... okay.
We don't have time for this.
What are you doing?
I'll need this if I'm gonna take her
around the mountain another way.
Uh... Around the mountain?!
That's gonna take them forever.
Don't worry, Twi. We'll be there lickety split.
WOOHOO! I win again!
Ugh... That's thirty-five games in a row.
Best of seventy-one?
We... made... it...
Told you it was gonna take them forever.
Your turn, Fluttershy.
But it's so wide.
Come on, Fluttershy.
We should be much farther along by now.
You could just leap on over.
I...
I don't know.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
It's just a hop, skip and a jump.
See?
It's not very far
just move your little rump
You can make it if you try
with a hop, skip and jump
We don't have time for this.
A hop, skip and jump
just move your little rump
Ahopskipandjump
Ahopskipandjump!
Okay. Here I go.
A hop...
-That's it!
-You're almost there.
...skip...
Just don't look down.
I guess I forgot to jump.
Let's keep it down.
According to my map, we're
entering an avalanche zone.
The smallest peep could
cause a huge rockslide.
An... an ava... ava...
Shhh!
AVALA...
Oh no! Help!
Everypony okay?
Thanks to you I am.
Let's do it again!
This is why a girl always
packs extra accessories.
Oh, please tell me I brought
a tiara that goes with this.
I think we've got bigger problems than making
sure our hair bows match our horseshoes.
Sorry.
Oh, no big whoop, sugar cube.
Yeah! We'll just have to...
...climb over.
My apologies.
Not *your* fault.
Still think it was a good idea
to bring Fluttershy along?
We're about to find out.
We're here.
Rainbow Dash, you'll use
your wings to clear the smoke.
Rarity and Pinkie Pie...
...you create a diversion to distract
the dragon if things get a little hairy in there.
Applejack, you're ready with
the apples in case he decides to attack.
But it shouldn't come to that...
...because Fluttershy will do what
she needs to do to wake him up...
...and between the two of us, we should be able
to get him to understand why he needs to go.
Is everypony ready?
Okay then. We're going in.
So, what is the best way to wake up
a sleeping dragon without upsetting him?
Fluttershy?
Oh, come on.
Come on!
We have to do this.
Now!
Every... second longer that dragon...
sleeps is another...
...acre of Equestria that is covered in... smoke.
I... I... I can't go in the cave.
Oh great. She's scared of caves now too.
I'm not scared of caves. I'm scared of...
What's that, sugar cube?
I'm scared of d...
What?
I'm scared of dragons!
But Fluttershy. You have a wonderful
talent dealing with all kinds of animals.
Yes, because they're not dragons.
Oh, come on! We've seen you walk right up
to a horrible manticore like it was nothing.
Yes, because he wasn't a dragon.
Spike is a dragon. You're not scared of him.
Yes, because he's not a huge, gigantic,
terrifying, enormous, teeth-gnashing...
...sharp-scale-having, horn-wearing,
smoke-snoring, could-eat-a-pony-in-one-bite...
...totally all grown up dragon.
But if you're so afraid of dragons...
...why didn't you say something
before we came all the way up here?
I was afraid to.
All of us are scared of that dragon.
I'm not.
Almost all of us are scared of that dragon.
But we've got a job to do.
So get in there with Twilight and
show her what you're made of.
I... I...
I just...
...can't.
Oh, Fluttershy.
I'm going in.
He probably just doesn't
realize what he's doing.
Right?
Mister dragon.
Excuse me.
Oh, good. You're awake.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Twilight...
...Sparkle and my friends and I are
residents here in Equestria...
...Ponyville to be exact.
We come here to ask that you find
another spot to take your nap.
It' just that you seem to be
doing an awful lot of snoring...
...and every time you do, you
send out a terrible cloud of smoke...
Equestria simply can't survive
a hundred years in a dark haze.
You understand, don't you?
So you'll find another place to sleep?
So much for... persuading him.
Now what?
Obviously, this situation just
calls for a little "pony charm".
Allow me, girls.
I'm so sorry to interru-hupt...
...but I couldn't possibly head back home without
mentioning what handsome scales you have.
And those scales have to be hidden away
in some silly cave for a hundred years?
Personally, I think you should skip the snoozing
and be out there. Showing them off.
Obviously, I would be more than happy to
keep an eye on your jewels while you're gone.
I was this close to getting that diamond.
You mean... getting rid of that dragon?
Oh... yeah. Sure.
What in tarnation...?
Darling, you look ridiculous.
Exactly!
Sharing a laugh is a sure-fire way
to get someone on your side.
Hi!
Apparently he doesn't like laughing, heh.
Or sharing.
Alright, that's it.
We've tried persuasion, charm...
...whatever it is Pinkie Pie does...
It's time to stop wasting time!
I'm going in.
Rainbow! No!
GET OUT!
Sorry.
How dare you?
HOW DARE YOU?!
Listen here, mister!
Just because you're big
doesn't mean you get to be a bully.
You may have huge teeth and sharp scales
and snore-smoke and breathe fire...
...but you do not, I repeat, YOU DO NOT...
HURT. MY. FRIENDS!
You got that?
Well?
BUT THAT RAINBOW ONE KICKED ME.
And I am very sorry about that.
But you're bigger than she is
and you should know better.
You should also know better
than to take a nap...
...where your snoring can become
a health hazard to other creatures.
BUT I...
Don't you "but I" me, mister.
Now what do you have to say for yourself?
I said...
What do you have to say for yourself?!
There, there. No need to cry.
You're not a bad dragon.
You've just made a bad decision.
Now go pack your things. You'll just need
to find a new place to sleep. That's all.
You did it! I knew you could do it!
I said, come back here!
How does Fluttershy put up
with you furry little things?
Spike.
Take a letter.
With pleasure.
"Dear Princess Celestia."
"I am happy to report that the dragon
has departed our fair country..."
"...and that it was my good friend Fluttershy,
who convinced him to go."
"This adventure has taught me to
never lose faith in your friends."
"They can be an amazing source of strength..."
"...and can help you overcome
even your greatest fears."
"Always your faithful student,
Twilight Sparkle."
Twilight! You gotta come see this!
She's just five away from a new pony record.
247... 248...
DRAGON!
Why are you laughing?!
That awful dragon is back!
Pinkie Pie, you scared me.
I mean... uh, you broke my concentration.
It's okay, Rainbow Dash.
Not everypony can be as brave as me.
Synced by Nathan2000
http://mlp.wikia.com/wiki/User:Nathan2000