Twilight: Whoo hoo hoo!
Whoa!
♪ Tada! ♪
OK, Spike. Now
let's try a flip.
Remember, two flaps
then straight up.
Got it!
You're doing great, Spike.
Now let's see the big finish!
Ahhhhh!
[sigh] I don't know about
big, but I am definitely finished.
Maybe I should
get Rainbow Dash.
She's the one who taught me
advanced flying techniques.
No thanks.
If I'm going to mess up I'd
rather do it in front of you.
I just don't understand why
none of your advice is helping.
Because she's teaching
you to fly like a pony
instead of a dragon.
What's the difference?
Well, we don't have
feathers for starters.
Yeah-heh-heh!
Wow! Thank
you so much!
How did you know I just
needed to bend my wings?
Honestly, this is Dragon 101.
Usually dragon parents
teach this stuff.
Spike?
I've been thinking
about our flying lesson.
Spike: Uh huh?
I can't believe I overlooked
something as simple as feathers.
It's no wonder you
were having trouble.
I wish I had more dragon-ish
knowledge to give you.
Do you think being
raised by ponies
has affected you
in other ways?
Spike?
Did you say something, Twilight?
Sorry. I'm just finishing
up this "Thank You"
throw pillow for Smolder.
And you know how I get when
I'm in the embroidery zone.
It's a pillow. But
not for your head.
Although it could be.
It's a throw pillow.
They're more casual. You
can use them anywhere.
You don't like it.
Uh it's not that. It's just,
dragons don't
really use pillows.
At all.
What?
Hey, what's that?
I don't know, but it's
HEADING RIGHT FOR US!
OK. Now I REALLY owe
you for the lesson.
Heh heh. Hey there,
young dragons.
Name's Sludge.
How are your
tails shaking?
Oooh!
Are you all right?
Yeah. What
happened?
To what?
[crash]
Oh.
I don't need to explain myself
to a couple of baby dragons.
[crash] Ow!
Maybe not, but you're
hurt and need help,
so I'm taking you to
Twilight's Castle
whether you like it or not.
Castle, eh? [moan]
I'm glad Spike brought
you here, Sludge.
I understand you made quite
an impression in town.
Literally. There's a
hole and everything!
Well, I hope you're not
expecting me to fix it.
It doesn't look like you're
in much shape to do anything.
I'll manage. Dragons
take care of themselves.
I don't need help from a
bunch of castle-living ponies.
Darling, do be careful.
I'm [groan] fine.
I can't watch!
You're not the first stubborn,
dragon we've met, you know.
And sometimes even
dragons need help.
I promise, my friends and
I will only do enough
to get you back on your claws.
I know you had
your reservations,
but it's good to see
you feeling better.
Thanks? I guess?
That's what friends
are for, darling!
You're pretty lucky to have
friends like these, kid.
Actually I was orphaned as an
egg and Twilight raised me,
so these ponies are
more than my friends.
They're my family.
We try our best, but sometimes I
worry maybe Spike is--
--missing something deep
down and dragonish.
Really? Wow.
I can't tell you how
glad I am to hear that.
Why in Equestria would
you be glad to hear that?
I wasn't going
to say anything,
since your life
seems so perfect,
but I have a
confession to make.
Coming to Ponyville
wasn't an accident.
I was looking for you.
Spike, [sigh] I'm your father.
Sorry!
So, you crashed in
Ponyville on purpose?
Well, the crash part wasn't on
purpose, but heading here was.
I've been searching
everywhere for you, kid.
Did you ask in the
Crystal Empire?
I'm kind of well
known there.
Actually, Spike's
well known everywhere.
Not a lot of dragons
were hatched by the
Princess of Friendship.
Mm hm.
You make it sound so simple.
I wish you'd been there
to help me search.
I can't believe it...
I have so many questions!
Well, ask away!
Answering questions
is what dads are for!
I guess my biggest
question is simple.
Why was I an
orphaned egg?
Uh! You sure you don't wanna
ask something else?
It's a lot of painful memories.
Your mother was the best
dragon I'd ever met.
The Dragon Lord even
picked her to scout for the Great Migration
and.. and even though she'd
just laid your egg,
we knew she'd have to go.
But finding the Migration
route could take a lifetime
and you deserved a chance
to know your mother.
So I went looking for her,
carried your egg to places
no dragon, or pony,
has ever been.
Past Mount Aris, the abandoned
home of the Hippogriffs.
Oooh!
Did you visit Klugetown?
You've been to Klugetown?
All: Uh huh!
Also, the Hypogriffs
returned to Mount Aris
after we helped them
defeat the Storm King.
Oh well, have you heard of the
Land of the.. Scale Collectors?
Uh uh.
Because, that's where your
mother's trail finally led
to a prison world
of dragon hunters,
where I was forced
to choose between
surrendering myself or
surrendering your egg.
Of course, there was no way
I was gonna sacrifice my boy,
so they took me instead
and that's where I've
been ever since.
Locked up somewhere
not even the
Princess of Friendship
has heard of.
Whoa!
How did you know I was a boy?
What ever happened
to Spike's mom?
And how did the egg make it all
the way back to Equestria
by itself?
-Hm?
I wish I had all the answers!
Well, that's all
in the past.
The only thing that matters
now is that we're together,
and I'm gonna make
up for lost time.
I hope you don't mind,
but I have a list
of all the things
I always wanted to
do with my dad.
Mind?
Spike, my boy, with
you by my side,
I feel like we can do anything!
What do you
wanna do first?
Well, I've kind of been working
on the list for a long time.
Oh! You wanna do all of this?
Oh, I mean, we
don't have to...
If you think doing everything
on this incredibly long list
is gonna fill the hole where
your dragonishness should be,
then that is exactly
what we're gonna do!
Oh yeah!
I can't believe we
got so many things done!
But this is all my stuff...
Is there anything you
always wanted to do with me?
Not really.
Er.. I-I mean, I'm happy to
do whatever you want,
but.. if I had a castle like
this, with all this stuff,
I'd probably just
lay around all day
doing nothing like
a real dragon.
Like a real dragon?
Sure. I'm not surprised
you don't know any better.
Twilight basically
raised you as a pony.
You're barely a dragon at all...!
Huh!?
Hey, Spike.
How are things
going with Sludge?
Honestly, I thought
having him around
would make me feel
more dragonish,
but I kinda feel less.
Oh I'm sorry. I wish
I could help.
Sludge: Aw, shucks.
I guess I shouldn't
have said anything
about you being more
pony than dragon.
I just wish we had
more in common.
Maybe you two can come up with
ways to turn up Spike's..
uh- dragonishness!
You think that's
something we can do?
You know what, son?
I think it is!
Spike, I'm gonna teach
you a thing or two
about being a dragon.
So listen up, my boy, because
I'm only gonna say this once.
♪ Look at this castle
where you live! ♪
It's pretty sweet, right?
♪ You can't be a dragon here! ♪
Uh, I can't?
♪ Look at these books
up on the wall. ♪
Hey, I just finished
organizing those!
♪ This treasure pile's
not right, I fear. ♪
Trust me, I got ya
covered here.
You see all this soft, pony
stuff you're surrounded with?
This has got to be
the first thing to go!
♪ Nothing 'bout this
place is dragon den, ♪
♪ theres too much fluff! ♪
♪ All these fancy
robes toss in a pile. ♪
♪ Take those goblets,
dishes; is that gold? ♪
♪ Still not enough! ♪
♪ De-ponyfying might
just take a while. ♪
♪ Sure this place
is grandiose. ♪
♪ But to a dragon,
it's just gross! ♪
♪ Time we make the
lot all disappear. ♪
♪ Reality you need a dose. ♪
♪ To all these ponies
you're too close, ♪
♪ You just can't be a
dragon here. ♪
Good job my boy, but this
is still just the beginning!
♪ Each and every dragon
has a swagger of his own, ♪
♪ watch and I'll show
you what I mean! ♪
♪ You can't move like this with
so much stuff to way ya down! ♪
♪ A dragon always
keeps it lean. ♪
Lose this, this,
ooh this is nice...
♪ Your life is soft, your
scales are coiffed. ♪
♪ These pillows, beds
and sheets are washed. ♪
♪ A delight but its just not
right what's underneath. ♪
♪ Every dragon must be free! ♪
♪ Look at you, then
look at me. ♪
♪ Since when do dragons
brush their teeth? ♪
Hah, please.
♪ Sure this place
is grandiose, ♪
♪ but to a dragon
it's just gross! ♪
♪ Time we make the
lot all disappear! ♪
But what do I do?
♪ Just grab it all
and give to me, ♪
♪ after that then
you'll be free. ♪
♪ You just can't be
a dragon... here! ♪
Hah, you're right!
I feel better already!
See, what did
I tell you?
You're very lucky
that I found you!
Now go get me
some more.
You got it!
I'm gonna go get you all the
cushy pony stuff I've got...
...Dad.
Great, go get 'em!
...Son.
♪ Cause this dragon just
can't wait to live here! ♪
[knocking] Spike?
I just thought I'd check
to see if you and Sludge
had any luck turning up
your dragonishness.
It's hard not to
feel like somehow
I let you down
all these years.
Oh! I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to
barge in on you.
Don't worry about it.
Mi castle es su castle!
Right.... well, I'll just get
out of your way.
Oh! Spike.
I am so sorry.
My morning is not going well.
What is all this?
Why'd you leave the
Castle so early?
I didn't leave, I spent
the night outdoors
to get in touch with
my dragon side.
Outdoors?
Yeah! And Sludge
asked me to bring him
the best breakfast
Ponyville has to offer
so he can show me how
a real dragon would eat it.
See you later!
[door slams]
And that's why I thought we
could use the map to--
Hey, gang.
Dad was just showing me how
a real dragon would act
in the throne room.
Dragons like to sprawl when
they get their claws done.
Now, if you'll all excuse
me, it's time for my bath.
[sigh] Isn't he the best!?
I'm not sure that's exactly
the word I would use.
Um, Spike?
The bath isn't gonna
fill itself, son.
Be right there, Dad!
I'm glad you're not spending
the night outside again.
Oh, I am. I'm
just looking for
a good bedtime story to
read to my dad first.
It's nice that you have somepony
to show you dragon culture,
but are you sure that's
what Sludge is doing?
What do you mean?
Well, taking over your room,
making a mess of things...
Pffft.
That is dragon culture.
You never acted like that.
That's because you raised me.
Now I finally have a chance
to see how I'm supposed to be.
I don't think you're
supposed to be any different
than who you are.
Maybe you just don't like
that I have a real parent now.
That's not true...
I'm glad Sludge is here.
I just wish he wasn't such a...
Dragon? Of all ponies,
I can't believe you
would have a problem with that.
Oh..
What happened to you?
Just sleeping outside
like we're meant to.
It's not like dragons are
supposed to live in castles.
I guess not.
But I live in
the school.
Nothing says we have
to live outside.
[sigh] I'm so confused.
It's been great having Sludge
show me how to be a real dragon,
but Twilight just
doesn't get it.
What do you mean?
She can't handle how good
at being a dragon Sludge is.
Maybe someday I'll be able to
lay around doing nothing
as well as he does.
What?
Well, not now, of course.
I'm too busy bringing
him pony stuff
so he can show me what a
dragon would do with it.
So, Sludge just lays around
while you wait on
him claw and tail?
Uh, dragons are
rude and rebellious,
but they aren't lazy lumps who
take advantage of their kids.
Huh. Now I'm really confused.
Me too.
Why don't you tell me
everything Sludge said
about being a dragon.
Hey!
What's going on, son?
Twilight doesn't like having
real dragons in the castle
so I told her we're moving out.
You what!?
Spike!
I found the perfect cave
where you two can live.
There aren't even any
comfortable rocks inside.
That does
sound perfect!
No, it doesn't!
I-I-I mean, I'm not sure I've fully
demonstrated all the ways
a dragon would live here.
But we're not gonna live here
anymore, so it doesn't matter.
It matters to me!
I..... I want to make sure you have
all the knowledge you need.
But I do!
Dad, you've already
shared so much.
♪ This bed is much too soft. ♪
♪ Just take that
silk robe off. ♪
♪ We can't be dragons
living here! ♪
ARGH! Stop!
I'm not your father!
-What?
I just said that to get in
on this sweet castle life.
So... you pretended to be my dad?
Na nana. Don't look at
me like that, kid.
I did what any dragon would do.
No, you didn't.
Hey, I saw an opportunity
and I took it.
That's what dragons do.
No. It isn't.
You know what? I
don't need this.
I'm out of here.
Enjoy livin' in pony town...!
I'm taking this pillow.
I can't believe I thought
somepony like that
could show me how
to be.. anything.
[sigh] It must be hard growing up not
really knowing who you are.
That's the thing.
I know exactly who I am,
and how I got that way.
Um, Twilight?
Oh. Hi. Where's
your.. father?
He's gone.
Turns out he wasn't what a real
dragon should be after all.
He also wasn't my real dad.
Oh, Spike... I'm so sorry.
I'm the one who's sorry.
You were just worried about
me and I lost my temper.
Sludge was just a
great big phony.
I have to say, I'm not surprised.
There's no way a dragon like
that was related to you.
But if you still want to
search for your real family,
I'd understand if you spent
more time in the Dragonlands.
I don't think so.
I already know who
my real family is.
Oooh! It's me, right?
Mm hm! Besides...
There's no way I'm
living without pillows.