Ha! Straight to the
changeling hive.
I told you I could do it.
Well, not exactly
"straight" Starlight.
We've been popping
all around Equestria
and we still
have to walk.
Pfft. It's like twelve
steps away.
Before Chrysalis'
throne was destroyed,
the closest magic would have
gotten us was waaay over there.
On a scale of one-to-ten, how
happy do you think Thorax
is going to be about
our surprise visit?
Definitely ten.
I mean, who wouldn't be happy
at the chance to marvel
at the overwhelming
talent that is...
the Great and Powerful Trixie?
Trixie, we're coming
to offer Thorax
encouragement
and support.
His letters make it seem like
the responsibilities of being
the changeling leader are
a little overwhelming.
Yeah, I know.
That's basically what I said.
He's dealing with the wants
and needs of his subjects,
redesigning the hive,
a Dread Maulwurf
wreaking havoc outside.
It does sound
like a lot, but...
are you sure that
last thing is real?
The Dread Maulwurf?
Sure it is.
Thorax said it's like
half-bear, half-mole,
half-raging pile of claws.
But now that the changelings
don't feed on the love of
everything around them, plants
have started to grow back.
But this Maulwurf keeps
eating them all up.
Maulwurf. Uh-huh.
You're just trying
to scare me.
But it won't work
because not only am I
the Great and Powerful, I am
also the Unscareable Trixie!
Rahr!
[gasp] Please tell me Thorax also
mentioned a terrifying-looking
changeling who greets visitors
but is actually nice?
Nope.
And I'm not nice.
Starlight, you got us
here, I'll take us home.
Teleportation spell, go!
Trixie: Did I save us?
Starlight: Nope.
What are you
waiting for?
Use some magic to
get us out of here!
Calm down,
Unscareable Trixie.
Huh. We have to find out
what's going on.
Thorax might
need our help.
We need our help!
Teleportation spell, go!
Teleportation spell...
Ugh. Why do you keep
doing that?
You know it doesn't
work that way.
I know! But this
is my process.
Gah!
I captured these
trespassers.
Thorax: Starlight?
Trixie?
It's OK, Pharynx.
You can let them go.
But they were lurking
on our grounds!
In the old days, I would have
already feasted on their love.
Well, that's why they're
called the old days.
Because they're old.
We don't do that anymore.
Ugh. I liked the old days better.
What are you
two doing here?
We wanted to
surprise you.
Surprise..!
Well, it's great to see you.
I'm sorry about the
welcome committee.
I thought Ember helped
you get more assertive
so you could deal with all
the renegade changelings
who didn't want to change?
Oh, she did. Really helpful.
I was able to convince
all of them to change...
except one of them.
My brother.
Your brother?
Yep. Pharynx is my
elder brood mate.
Oh, yeah.
You guys have the same...
...eye shape?
What a ridiculous comparison.
We are nothing alike.
Stop doing that!
The hive looked
better with holes...
Uh. Well, how about I show
you the rest of the hive
where it's less
loud and bang-y?
There've been a lot of changes
since you were here last.
I'm trying to start some new
activities since the only thing
we did before was
hunt and patrol.
There's theater...
...swing dancing,
a once-a-week
potluck lunch...
Ooh! And who can change shape
and organize craft time?
This guy!
I am really impressed, Thorax.
The hive, all the activities...
Agh! He did it again!
Pharynx dumped an entire
can of black paint on me!
He said my fuchsia color wasn't
"intimidating to our enemies."
What enemies!?
I am so sorry.
I promise I'll
talk to him.
You're the ruler of
the hive, Thorax.
You need to do
more than talk!
Well.. maybe not everything
here is amazing.
Seriously, Thorax.
What is up with your brother?
[sigh] Pharynx used to
be Head of Patrol.
But now we're peaceful and
there's no need to patrol,
so he just stalks around the
hive making everyone miserable.
The other changelings are sick
of it and if I can't get him
to accept love and friendship
and change like the rest of us,
everything I've done
here is at risk.
Uh uh!
Mmmmm....?
[sigh] Uh huh...
We know a thing or two about
what it's like to be outsiders.
Maybe we could talk
to him for you.
Do you really
think you could help?
Thorax, if there's anypony
who can help your brother...
it's me.
And with Starlight helping, it
might take slightly longer,
but I guarantee
you we can do it.
Thorax, we're ready to start
work on the trail of plants
to lead the Maulwurf away.
Oh. I have to head outside.
You're sure you're
OK handling Pharynx?
Absolutely!
Yeah. We totally
got this!
So. How do you
want to play this?
I'm thinking good
pony/bad pony.
You yell and blast
him with magic,
while my natural charisma
will convince him that--
Starlight?
Hey, Pharynx.
I know when we first met,
it didn't go so well...
I put you in a bag.
I thought it went great.
Yah!
Right. [ahem]
So... not a big fan
of the vines, huh?
They're a safety hazard.
An enemy could hide in them
or use them as weapons.
I don't even know
why they're here.
Because they're pretty?
That's ridiculous.
Oh. Totally.
We get you.
But ahem.. maybe don't express how
you feel by destroying them?
I don't take advice
from ponies.
The only thing I take
from you is breakfast.
At least I used to.
You know, you're a
lot like us.
Doubt it.
Trixie: It's true.
Do you know who
Twilight Sparkle is?
No.
Well, she's the most
well-liked, studious,
do-goodiest pony
in Equestria.
Ugh. She sounds awful.
Oh, you'd hate
her. I used to.
She made me unsure about
my place in the world,
which led me to act
out against her.
And I used to be a dictator who
ran a village with an iron hoof!
Really? Hmm. Maybe you
two do understand me.
Yes! We do!
But now, Trixie has come to
terms with being second-best...
And I no longer control
ponies against their will.
And our lives are so
much better for it.
Wow. So you're both losers.
Stay away from me or I'll do
to you what I did to the vines.
Well, operation Lead Maulwurf
away is coming along.
How'd it go with Pharynx?
Your brother is...um,
challenging.
Oh. That bad, huh?
It wasn't great.
You want to talk it out?
You can come with me
to the Feelings Forum.
The Feeling what, now?
Oh. It's a place for changelings
to express their feelings
so we all gain a better
understanding of each other.
It's really helped bring
the hive closer together.
Sometimes I feel like
I'm a blue changeling.
I'm a purple changeling.
But here I am,
a green one.
You can be anything
you want to be.
Be blue one day and
purple the next.
Be both on the same day!
But then I feel like
I'd be living a lie.
It's very brave of you to
share something so personal.
Does anyone else have
similar concerns?
I used to, but craft time has
given me such a creative outlet
I feel great now.
Everyone loves craft time.
Well...
everyone except
for you-know-who.
Yeah. You-know-who spends all
his craft time making spears.
He's scary and intimidating.
You-know-who makes
me uncomfortable.
He makes us all
uncomfortable!
Everyone, please, I
understand Pharynx
can be challenging
at times--
That's an
understatement.
He lined the
hallway with thorns!
He teaches little changelings
to growl and hiss!
My soup's too hot!
What?
I thought the Feelings Forum
was for sharing our problems?
It sounds like your lame
Feelings Forum is for talking
about me behind my back.
The Feelings Forum is for
talking about anything
that's bothering you.
Is there something you'd
like to share, Pharynx?
Actually, there is.
The changelings used
to be a fearsome swarm.
Now we sit around talking about
our feelings so much
you can't even stop
a Maulwurf
from eating all
your pretty plants.
I could've sent that
thing packing before,
but I guess now, we'll
just try to lead it away
and hope that keeps us safe!
I don't feel safe
with him around.
I'd feel safer
if he were gone.
I can't do that.
We want him banished!
Hey! My soup's cooled down!
These Feelings Forums are
great for solving problems!
Everyone, please, if we are
interrupting each other,
we are not affirming
each other.
That's it! Feelings
Forum is over!
I....whew. I want to say something,
but it goes against everything
I've been taught as
Twilight's pupil.
Oooh. Then by all
means, say it.
I think Pharynx is
a lost cause.
Mm. I'm all for second
chances, third even,
but he just seems
like a bad bug.
And Thorax has a duty
to the whole hive,
not just his brother.
If he keeps sticking
up for Pharynx,
the hive might decide they don't
want Thorax as their leader.
I think he might have
to kick Pharynx out,
but I don't want to be the
one to tell Thorax that.
Me neither! But somepony
probably should.
I nominate you!
Ugh..
Thorax... we have
something to tell you.
It's about Pharynx, isn't it?
Mmmmmmmmaybe?
Look, I know he's an
aggressive warrior type,
but when I was little,
every young changeling
wanted to be like that.
Every young
changeling except me.
The others would pick on me
for not wanting to fight.
Look at the little grub
playing with his dollies.
Step away from
my brother.
But Pharynx never
let them hurt me.
Heh heh.. We were just
complimenting his dollies.
Thanks, Pharynx.
Why are you
hitting yourself?
Stop hitting yourself.
Why are you
hitting yourself?
Ow! Ouch!
Cut it out, Pharynx!
They're right, you know.
You need to have
tougher skin.
Awwww. That was a really sweet
story...until the end.
I know Pharynx loved
me, in his own way.
And I know there's
still good in him.
That's why I keep
sticking up for him.
Anyway, what did you
want to talk to me about?
Me? No...
But Starlight has
something she'd--
Actually, Thorax, um...
never mind.
Come on, Trixie, we've
got a... thing to do.
What are you doing?
I thought we agreed
you'd tell Thorax
he had to kick his
brother out of the hive.
Maybe we don't have to.
Get Pharynx and meet me
at the hive entrance.
I'll explain everything.
And how am I supposed to
know where Pharynx is?
I just saw
Pharynx.
Oh. Well, that was easy.
We'll just use one
problem to solve another.
I switched the trail
of plants around
to lure the Maulwurf here.
The changelings may not be
able to stop it anymore,
but Pharynx certainly can.
When it attacks, he'll
save his brother,
showing everypony
his good side.
The others will accept him
and Pharynx will finally
let love and friendship into
his life and transform!
Wow.
I know, right?
Great idea.
Where's Pharynx?
He's gone.
Gone like gone to
the throne room?
Gone like gone.
One of the changelings said
Pharynx left the hive for good.
[gasp] Then who's going to stop the
Dread Maulwurf I'm leading here!?
Thorax! There you are!
Pharynx is missing!
Wait for it...
--and the Dread Maulwurf
is coming this way!
Told ya.
That doesn't make any sense.
The trail of plants should have
lead the Dread Maulwurf away.
Heh... I might have re-laid them to
lead it back toward the hive.
Why would you do that!?
I thought if Pharynx saw you
were in danger, the loving,
caring side of him would come
out when he protected you.
But instead he's
out there alone
somewhere between us and
that rampaging monster?
I have to save him.
I'm coming with you.
Of course you are.
This is all your fault.
Oh, don't be too
hard on Starlight.
Her heart was in
the right place.
You're coming too!
Oh. Right.
I mean, I was gonna
volunteer anyway...
Who else is coming?
Ugh. Fine.
Oh, sure, you could
all stay here.
Not help Pharynx and he
won't bother you anymore.
It's your choice.
But remember when you
didn't have a choice.
When you were forced
to obey Chrysalis.
You might have been unstoppable,
but you weren't free to choose.
And now you are.
Because of Thorax.
Well, it's his
brother out there.
And now it's your chance to
prove you're just as strong
embracing love as you
were feeding on it.
Now is your chance to show what
changelings can really be.
Not because you have to,
but because you choose to!
That was an amazingly
epic speech, Starlight.
I just can't believe not
a single changeling
was moved by it.
I can't blame them.
If he wasn't my brother, I
don't think I'd be here.
We're going to have to face
the Maulwurf by ourselves.
Maybe it'll be long gone
and we'll find Pharynx
out here alone.
Or maybe not.
Pharynx!
What are you doing here?
I'm here to save you!
Get out of here!
Let me handle this!
We're not leaving you!
Ahh. I may have forgot to mention in
my letters that Maulwurfs
have really thick hides.
I thought you said you
could beat this thing!
Yeah, with the
rest of the swarm.
Not alone!
Changeling: Good thing you're not alone!
I told you it was
an epic speech.
It's no use!
We're out of practice
and he's too tough!
And strong.
Too bad we can't get
it to fight itself.
That's it!
Thorax! Remember
when we were young
and I made you hit yourself?
Now is not the time to
make fun of me, Pharynx!
Oh! Right! Of course!
Why are you
hitting yourself?
Yeah, Maulwurf.
Why are you hitting yourself?
Why are you hitting
yourself, huh? Huh? Huh?
Oooh. That looks
like it hurts.
We did it! It's gone!
What were you
doing out here?
Leaving. I'm done
with all of you.
Oh.
It's just, why bother
fighting the Maulwurf then?
You could have
left it alone.
Well, I couldn't just
let it attack you!
But I thought you were done
with us and you didn't care.
I never said that!
The hive is the thing
I care about most.
Well, you certainly
don't act like it.
Well, I'm sorry if I don't get
excited about pretty flowers
and Feelings Circles and-
It's a Feelings Forum.
Whatever. It
doesn't matter.
Even if I do care
about the hive,
I obviously don't have
a place there anymore.
Actually, you do.
Because we've been wrong.
Um. The hive may be a
gentler, nicer place...
But that doesn't mean we won't
have to defend ourselves.
Clearly.
And who better to help us do
that than the only changeling
who never stopped
protecting us?
You all... want
me to stay?
Unless you still want
to leave the hive.
Why would I want that?
I love the hive!
He did it!
He transformed!
I always knew you
had it in you!
Really? Because I thought you
said I was a lost cause
and you were going to tell
Thorax he should kick me out.
Oh! Starlight!
How could you say that?
Ah! Wha? That's...
I-I mean...
but you...
Lucky for us, you
weren't a lost cause.
Lucky for me, you
didn't give up on me.
So... Glad everything
worked out.
Yeah. Let's talk about how you
not only lead the Maulwurf
to the hive, but also drove
my brother away from it?
I am so sorry about that.
But I would like to point out
that my admittedly terrible plan
did bring everything
together in the end... huh?
Hey, do you guys want
to hear the story
about how I used to make
Thorax hit himself?
Oh! Absolutely. Yes. Right now!
Well, when we were young,
every changeling wanted
to be a warrior.
Except for Thorax...
He was a little weak..
but I had to protect...