Well, it's true that
of the five of us...
...only Minako hasn't had
her pure heart hunted.
But none of us are thinking that
Minako doesn't have a pure heart!
No, not at all!
So please calm down, Minako!
Sheesh, who said such a thing!?
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!!
Hello?
This is Eugeal.
Actually, I'm calling because
I noticed something strange...
Oh?
A human shadow appeared
amongst the data for the Grail.
Just as I thought...
That is the user of the Grail.
The user of the Grail...?
Yes.
If the Grail ends up in
hands that will aid us...
...the world of darkness that
we long for will be completed.
However, if someone who is against
our beliefs gets a hold of it...
...our objective will be crushed!
We must get a hold of it before
anyone else, no matter at what cost!
We must!!
Where is this... user of the Grail?
We must first get a hold of
the Grail... See you later.
By the way, Professor...
You broke the phone receiver
just now, didn't you?
I will have there pair costs
Deducted from your paycheck.
I want the Sailor Soldiers
to pay for it...
I'm done!
You did it! 23 minutes!
That's a new record!
These were really hard problems!
I'm so amazing!
You did it!
Congrats.
That was pretty well-done for Usagi.
Thanks!
It's all thanks to you guys!
Oh, wait.
The calculations are off right here.
So, the answer becomes... this.
Why? WHY!?
Usagi, you are doing what you can...
There, there...
I don't wanna do this anymore!
Don't cry each and every time!
But...
Although I said it's a mistake...
See, it's a simple one.
You just have to be careful next time.
I know I'm going to make a mistake
somewhere else next time!
I'm sick of all of this!
I don't want to go through such pain!!
So what about this much pain!?
Have you forgotten about when a Daimohn
took out your pure heart crystal!?
That's right.
Compared to the pain we felt back then,
studying can even be thought of as fun!
Let's do our best, Usagi!
All right... I understand...
It really was painful
back when it happened.
Yeah...
It felt as painful as when I chugged
down a 1.5-liter bottled soft drink!
That was it!?
Oh, maybe the pain was that
plus about 10 balls of rice!
Yeah!
I see...
Something wrong?
Hey, Artemis...
Why do you think Daimohn
don't come after me!?
Everyone other than me had the crystals
of their pure hearts sought after...
Maybe you're not pure...?
Oh, no, that can't possibly be it!
It can't, right?
Maybe because I quit playing
volleyball that I loved so much...
I'm not as focused on one thing...?
Are you worried about it?
Not really...
Usagi!
I'm sorry, did I hit you?
Are you all right?
I'm okay, I'm all right!
But enough of that.
Are YOU all right, Minako?
About what?
You know...
You mean how I'm the only one
that Daimohn hasn't come after?
Of course I'm not worried about that!
Geez!
Anyway you look at it...
...I'm not convinced that I'm the
only one without a pure heart!
Of course not!
This time, for sure...
Hey, are you REALLY
not worried about it?
Of course not!
Maybe you are thinking
too much, Artemis.
That's right! Minako wouldn't be
worried about something like that...
So what part of me isn't pure!?
Sheesh!
If they don't realize how pure I am,
the enemy really isn't that formidable.
Hello?
Minako...
You can't possibly be considering
getting yourself targeted, right, Minako?
You can't!
You absolutely can't do that!
It's better if you don't.
What would happen if they took
out your pure heart crystal!?
If that happens,
I'll get it back myself.
That's impossible!
You just CAN'T do that! Please!!
I was just kidding...
Now let me... go!
- You're kidding.
Hey, Minako.
You know, Usagi has
a pure love for Mamoru...
But she has a pure love for
eating and sleeping as well.
And she has a pure hatred for studying,
so she purely wants to ditch studying.
But if you're saying that
THAT is a pure heart...
...then you have to realize
that she's just an idiot.
Thanks a lot...
Even the enemy can't see through
to your true purity, Minako.
As I said, I'm not
worried about it! Sheesh!
Usagi...
Yeah?
I have a favor to ask you.
What?
Can you take half of these?
I kinda don't want to...
Let's leave her alone for a while...
You're right. Considering how Minako is,
she won't do anything too irrational.
You think so...?
A pure heart is...
A heart that deeply focuses
in on one thing at a time...
That's true, Usagi is
one who concentrates on...
...one thing at a time,
so much to be considered foolish.
Compared to that, I think about
so many aspects of things...
Maybe I'm more mature in that sense?
Hey.
Oh, hello.
Haruka, Michiru...
What do you think a pure heart is?
What are you talking about?
Can it be that she
knows about the talisman...!?
T-
T-!?
T-!!?
T-aking for instance,
is there something that...
...someone with a pure heart
is likely to be doing?
T-
T-?
T-ry doing something that
is for the good of others.
Doing something for
the good of others!?
Please help us with
the Blood Donation of Love.
We currently are short
on blood for transfusion.
- For instance, donating your blood...
- Thank you very much!
I guess we read too much into that.
Perhaps we are starting to be rushed...
But, she took us seriously, although
I said that off the top of my head...
A dangerous purity.
Um...
Take these!
They're tokens of my thanks.
I don't want this...
Donate blood! Donate blood!
Please go ahead!
Don't be bashful, you can
take as much as you want!
It's for the good of others,
for the good of the world!
Eugeal...
Have you found a new target?
Yes.
The owner of a pure heart type
that I can't yet figure out...
However, I feel that the Sailor Soldiers
will once again get in our way.
Well then, I shall prevent their...
...intrusion!
I will make a Daimohn to do just that!
I'm Minako Aino, and
I'm here to donate blood!
I may look young, but I'm 18!
So, you can go ahead and
take as much as you want!
I'm doing something for
the good of others...
I'm so pure...
I'm TOO pure...!
Yeah, and every day she lies about her age,
going from one donation area to the next!
I'm surprised she's
able to keep it up...
Well, just stay by her side
in case an enemy attacks her.
And make sure she's
getting proper nutrition.
Yeah, you're right...
Donate blood! Donate blood!
I still think we should stop her...
If Minako's heart crystal turns out to
be a talisman, it would be too dangerous.
But...
If that's the case,
she'll be targeted sooner or later...
That's true...
So, in the end, we have to
save her when that happens.
But, thinking about this...
Is Minako, who's running around donation
areas for her own pure heart, really pure?
T-That's...
Minako!
I got you Morimorin-C and Vitavitan-A!
Drink these, and do your best!
Thanks!
That hits the spot!
She's p-pure! Minako is pure too!
- Pure, pure, pure. So pure.
- Yeah, pure! She is pure.
Well, off to the next spot!
Captured!
Minako!
A pure heart...
It came out!
I'm glad for you, Minako...
Now, hurry up and put it back inside...
Impossible!
Minako! Wait!
Eugeal!?
- What does this mean!?
- Guys, hurry!
Artemis! There are
bottles at your feet!
- Artemis!
- I'm sorry...
W-What horribly strong mental powers...
Wait!
Don't come any closer to that girl!
What!?
How arrogant!
Come out, Daimohn!!
Doorknobder!
When going out, one word to
your neighbor, and lock the door!
Go lock up.
I will go lock up!
Completed!
Who is it?
Haruka, and Michiru too...?
If you didn't stick your nose into other
people's business, you'd live longer.
What should I do?
If I transformed here...
But...
We can't possibly transform here...
Hold it right there!
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!
What!?
So it WAS her!
Wanting to cherish a pure heart...
To come after the innocence of such
a maiden is something I can't forgive!
For love and justice...
...the pretty soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
Doorknobder, kill her!
- Huh?
- Don't give me "Huh?"!
I'm for locking up,
and not really good at combat...
- DO IT!
- Sure.
DOORKNOB RELUCTANCE ATTACK!
See, you can do it if you try. Now...
You can't!
I can't give you that.
Doorknobder, get rid of them first!
RELUCTANCE ATTACK...!
We have no choice.
I agree.
NEPTUNE PLANET POWER...
MAKE UP!
URANUS PLANET POWER...
Haruka... and Michiru were...
Three Sailor Soldiers...!?
WORLD...
...SHAKING!
Most unfortunate.
Wait, stop that, Michiru!
Please!
Please return that crystal!
This isn't a talisman.
What!?
BURNING MANDALA!
SPARKLING WIDE PRESSURE!
SHINE AQUA ILLUSION!
There are Sailor Soldiers
outside as well!?
Doorknobder!
Get every last one of them!!
DOORKNOB DESPARATION ATTACK!
DEEP...
...SUBMERGE!
I told you, I'm not good at combat!!
Now, Sailor Moon.
Yeah.
Y-You should get rid of HER first!
Out of my way!
MOON SPIRAL...
WITCHES EUGEAL...
HEA...
FI...
...RT ATTACK!
...RE BUSTER!!
LOVELY!
Don't move!
Even Sailor Moon's ultimate attack
was no match for this Fire Buster...
...which is currently being
registered as a practical model!
Now, all of you get
together into one bunch.
Otherwise, I'll make a roast
out of that girl lying right there.
I'll send all of you to
the afterlife in one group!
What!?
VENUS STAR POWER...
MAKE UP!
T-They're ALL Sailor Soldiers!?
VENUS...
...LOVE ME...
...CHAIN!
Dammit!
Just you wait and see!
I saw who you REALLY are!!
Backing up!
Wait!
Haruka... Michiru...
Please, tell me.
What is your real objective?
Why do you try to get the talismans,
even if it means sacrificing human lives?
Don't probe where you don't have to.
It's better if you don't
get too deeply involved.
But...
Enough!
Haruka and Michiru are
Sailor Uranus and Sailor Neptune...!?
Does that mean that
they really are enemies...?
I don't want to believe that...
They found out who we are.
We might have been foolish
to transform back there...
I don't regret it.
That so?
If we hadn't,
we wouldn't have survived...
And I wanted to save those girls.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com