If you have just a little bit of courage...
...people can really be soldiers.
If you have feelings for other people...
...anyone can become a messiah.
No matter how much you change...
...please don't forget that there
are people who care for you.
I'll make sure to save you!!
I'm sorry...
Chibiusa... I'm sorry...
She finally went away...
Hotaru!!
Give it up already!
She is no longer Hotaru!!
That's right...
Hotaru Tomoe died just now.
You're lying!!
The giant power that's fast
approaching through this Tau Nebula...
...is the master of
us Death Busters!
The ruler of silence, Pharaoh 90!
Now, if I can get a hold of the Grail...
...Pharaoh 90 will appear,
and the age of silence will begin!
Then, we will defeat you now!
Resign yourself!.
WORLD...
...SHAKING!
DEEP...
...SUBMERGE!
You can't!
Why, thank you.
You idiot!
Don't get in our way!
Shoot!
If you don't want these two killed right
before your eyes, hand over the Grail.
You can't!!
Shall I get rid of one of them first?
Wait!
I-If you hand the Grail over to her,
I will detest you!!
But...
Stop it!
Sailor Moon!
Stop it!!
Hotaru...
Hotaru's... dad?
It's me...
Your Papa...
Hotaru... you ended up
like this because of me...
The empty shell of Germatoid...?
You're just a shell!
Don't touch me! How filthy!
Stop it already!
Stop it...
Please...
Everyone, hang in there!
It's gaining power...
I won't lose!
We won't let this Daimohn
loose into the city!
Hotaru...
Papa...
Impossible!
Hotaru...
The body is rejecting me...?
This hurts, Papa...
Finish her, Sailor Moon!
No!
Because...
Hotaru is alive...
Don't be fooled!!
Hotaru, are you in pain...?
The Grail...
The Grail?
If I don't have the Grail...
I no longer...
Hang in there, Hotaru...
This Grail...
...where is it, Hotaru!?
Papa...?
Why, Sailor Moon!?
You're not the messiah or anything...
You have no right to do with
the Grail as you please!!
Hotaru is still alive...
She's alive!!
We can't save the world unless
innocent little Hotaru dies...!?
That just can't be true!!
Oh... is this...
Is that the Grail?
Please, can I...?
For Hotaru...?
Thank you...
Now, Hotaru...
The Grail... You want this?
Yes... Hurry...
Dammit!!
Sailor Moon...
After I greet Pharaoh 90, I will
give you a special choice...
...to continue living as
a body for a Daimohn.
Hotaru!
Hotaru, you can hear me, right!?
Hotaru!!
It's no use...
No matter what you do,
it's too late now.
Hotaru or this world...
I won't let either go as you please!!
Why don't you give up?
This Grail is an ultra-pure
crystal among all pure hearts.
Love, hate, happiness, anger, sadness...
elevated to the highest level.
To win against Pharaoh 90
after he takes in the Grail...
...you'd need to create a pure
heart crystal that surpasses it!
There's no way you can win!!
What!?
What's going on inside!?
Sailor Moon!
The Grail...!?
Yes, this way, Pharaoh 90!!
Look! This is the result of
your methods full of idealism!!
MOON COSMIC POWER!!
You, who cannot even undergo
the second transformation...
...cannot stop the silence!
The world for the master
and myself will now begin!
Impossible!!
Hotaru...
Papa...?
Hotaru?
Papa...
Hotaru...
Papa... where are you?
Where are you?
It's dark here...
I'm right here.
I have to save Chibiusa...
Papa, let me out of here...
I'm sorry...
I don't know what to do...
Forgive me...
If only I could go back...
to those days once more...
Papa!
Hotaru!
Sheesh, papa!
Papa...
I'm sorry...
Papa.
H-Hotaru...
Don't come here...
You little pest...
Hurry up and...
...begone!
Even if you live...
...your life is useless...
Do not get...
...in our way!
Begone! Be destroyed!
No!
I will definitely NOT!
Dammit...
I... I...
I have people dear to me!!
H-Hotaru...
The revival of the Warrior of Ruin...!?
You are...?
Chibiusa... You're all right now...
Sailor Saturn...!
Hotaru...?
Thank you, Chibiusa...
Thank you.
Pharaoh 90 is gaining power!
Now, we have no means
to stop the silence...
Hotaru!
In the end...
Everything we did goes to waste...?
This is the end.
Are you satisfied with
this, Sailor Moon!?
Answer me!!
Sailor Moon.
Thank you for protecting my body...
It's all thanks to you.
Sailor Saturn...
Hotaru?
Hotaru!!
I am no longer Hotaru.
The only one who can save
the world from silence now is me.
Leave everything else to me.
Wait! I'll go with you!
No...
To defeat Pharaoh 90, you need to enter
its core and make it all disappear at once...
I don't know about Super Sailor Moon,
but as you stand now...
...you can't even enter Pharaoh 90
now that it has the power of the Grail.
This is my job now.
When you defeat Pharaoh 90...
what will happen to you?
The reason I am called
the Warrior of Ruin...
...is because I am given enough
power to destroy a planet.
However...
...when I use that power,
I myself will also...
You can't!
Farewell...
Hotaru!
CRISIS MAKE UP!
Please, transform!!
CRISIS MAKE UP...
Sailor Moon...
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
Farewell...
If you are able to
meet the real Messiah...
The real... Messiah...!?
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com