Dobon, mahjong, and roll-of-the-dice.
Games are all fun,
but you shouldn't gamble!
Furthermore, to bet
people's lives is immoral!
If you're an ill-willed person
who wants to win by cheating...
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
This one...
I did it! I'm out!
It seems that the joker likes me.
The ace of hearts always
runs away from me...
Sheesh, Hotaru!
You're really good when it comes
to Memory! Don't say that!
All right!
We'll play Memory!
I won't lose this time!!
Finally, a Daimohn who's strong during
matches that really count will be born...
Oh, Professor?
It's almost time for tea!
Oh, that's right!
I'm in charge of getting
the snacks today, aren't I?
Yes!
Then, I'll go out to buy the snacks!
Be careful!
Sheesh, the professor is
too easy on things!
If you want to make it stronger, you have
to really get down and do it like this!
When it fails, I'm always the one
who takes responsibility for it...
So I want him to at least do this much!
T-This might not be so good...!?
I-I don't know anything about this!!
W-What...!?
Are you all right, Chibiusa?
Yeah...
I'm glad...
What's this!?
What IS this!?
Hotaru...
Hotaru...?
It looks like something really
out of the ordinary happened...
I know!
Everyone! Help me!
Huh? What's wrong, Chibiusa?
I don't know what's going on,
but Hotaru's house is in danger!
What's wrong, Hotaru!?
What in the world was that...?
In any case, we should head over!
Yeah...
Hotaru?
In my dresser...
...there are fish swimming...
Oh, no...
Then, the rest of the house...?
What should we do?
Hotaru!
I'm sure help is on the way,
so let's do our best until then!
Yeah...
Oh, boy, it looks like I'm a little late.
To think someone would
pull a prank on me...!!
Open up, you fool!
I am the master of the house!
I see! So that's how you
want to play it! Then, I'll...
It's here!
What in the world happened!?
It looks like this house got connected to an
alternate dimension due to some strong force.
You are...!?
Can it be...?
Have they realized who I really am...!?
Don't worry, Hotaru's dad!
We're not suspicious people!
A necessity for times in need!
Pretty soldiers with the Sailor emblem!
If you don't know us, we'll punish you!
What are you doing in
someone else's front yard!?
So embarrassing!
That's so cruel!
You didn't have to really hit me!!
It's all your fault for doing
something you didn't need to do!
What!?
- I must've over estimated them.
- It's something I have to do! I can't help it!
You'll rescue Hotaru...?
Yes! Leave it to us!
Now, let's hurry, Sailor Moon!
The house will be sucked into this alternate
dimension and disappear in just one hour!
Such a hard turn of events all of a sudden...!
I'm hot...!
Water...
I'm cold!!
Sheesh! What's up with all of this!!
All right, I'm leaving it up to you, Jupiter!
Wait a minute!
What are you planning to do, Sailor Moon?
What am I...?
Well, Jupiter first uses
the Wide Pressure, right?
Then, if that doesn't work, Mars can burn
the door down with Burning Mandala...
And, what are you going to do?
Me...?Just watch...
Just kidding!
Can I really trust all of you...?
Of course!
The only big fool who doesn't
understand the situation is this one girl!
What did you say!?
Anyway, if you try to forcefully
break open that door...
...the time-space balance will be broken,
and the entire house will...
- ...be sucked into the alternate dimension!
- See, did you hear that!?
You always end up being embarrassed
because you don't listen to what others say!
In any case!
We should go inside,
and open the door from the inside.
Um... and...
How are we going to go inside...?
Oh, come on! The only thing we
can do is the Sailor Teleport!
- Oh, brother...
- All right!
Then, let's go, guys!
Yeah, yeah... Fine, just fine!
SAILOR TELEPORT!
What!?
Did we make a mistake
in where we ended up!?
No!
This is inside Hotaru's house!
How ironic that I have to
rely on the Sailor Soldiers...
But...
I can't afford to lose Hotaru now...
Oh, I had forgotten...
I guess I'll have this tea while I wait.
Sheesh! Why is this place Hotaru's house!?
As I said, it's just that various pieces of
time and space are twisted together here!
The scenery keeps changing, but we haven't
moved one bit out of Hotaru's house!
So, Chibiusa and Hotaru
can't be too far away, either!
I'm getting dizzy.
It's been 20 minutes already...
I wonder if everyone is all right...
Hey.
How are things...?
Hotaru Tomoe seems to be
trapped in an alternate dimension...
In the worst case, Sailor Moon and her
gang might not be able to return as well...
It would be better if they
Just didn't come back.
Haruka!
I can't help it!
Hotaru Tomoe is a dangerous existence...
Everyone... hurry up and get here...
Chibiusa!
Are you all right...?
I'm fine, I'm all right! If
I exercise just a little bit...
It's safer if you didn't
move around too much!
I'm fine, it's nothing...
Chibiusa!
Hotaru!
Hotaru! That's enough!
You can let go of me!
No...!
Hotaru!
They're inside the next
dimension that we'll be entering!
Really...!?
No mistakes there!
It's going to shift...
One, two... three!
There they are!
Oh, no!!
VENUS LOVE ME CHAIN!
Venus!
Hurry! We have to pull them up!
Help me!
It's impossible to use the Sailor Teleport
if we have to take both Hotaru and Chibiusa.
Then, how are we...?
Can you save one of us, at least...?
If that's the case... please save Chibiusa!
I'll stay here...!!
Hotaru...!?
Please don't mind me...
I'm someone who should have
never been born, anyway...
Please! Save Chibiusa!
Hotaru.
It's all right!
We'll rescue both of you!
You're Chibiusa's friend, right?
If you say stuff like that,
Chibiusa will be sad!
I'm sure this young lady here will
find a way for all of us to go back!
Chibiusa's friend is our friend...
Let's all go back together.
Okay...
Sheesh...
They only have 30 minutes left...
We'll be connected to the exit!
Everyone... are you all right!?
Yeah...
I can't take this anymore!
Can we really get out of here...!?
We have the highest possibility here.
I have a bad feeling about this...
Just as I thought.
Welcome...
Welcome here!
I'm a strange Daimohn who lives
in this strange world, Ikasaman!
The energy for this alternate
dimension is all coming from her!!
That's correct...
I hope you enjoyed your epic adventure.
That means...
We can't get out of here
unless we defeat that thing!?
Hold on a moment!
I don't like violence...
I'm a pacifist, though I'm a villain.
What kind of villain is that!?
Well, you know...
I love to gamble.
If you play a game with me and you win,
I'll let you go back to your own world...
We don't have time for that!
BURNING--
Then...!
I guess I'll have you go to
some strange place again!
Fine!
But if even one person wins,
I want you to take us back to our world!
Nice!
I don't care what game we play!
But, if I win... I'll have you as my
gaming partners for eternity!
Now, let's begin!
All right! I'll go first against you!
A challenge!
Red... 16!
- You lose!
- You're a cheater!
There!
Now, it's your turn, right?
You lose!
Checkmate!
I win!
Oh! That square...
There! You lose!
Who's up next?
We are!
I'll show you that it's not for nothing that
I've been going to the arcades so much!
Bring it on!
You have to read the
directions well first, you know!
It's not always the case that
the car will move forward!
That's... impossible...!!
Was that all...?
Hold on just a minute!
We'll challenge you!
Chibiusa!
Okay...
What game will you like?
Old Maid!
Okay!
A challenge!
What is everyone doing...?
They have less than 1 0 minutes left...!
Now, it's your turn!
Then, I'll take a card!
Is it this one?
She's a child after all...
I can tell just by looking at her face...!
Or is it this one...?
Justas I thought! This one!
T-This is...!!
Hah! You fell for it!
Dammit! How dare you!?
I've been waiting for you to take that!
Really?
Oh, I'm so glad!
- If you're told that, you usually...
- Here, it's your turn, Chibiusa.
- ...would think that it was a joker!
- I did it! A match!
Here!
I did it! I win!
- You did it!
- Chibiusa!
Now, you promised!
Take us back to our world!
Not yet!
I won't let you go until SHE wins!
That can't be...
If you don't like it,
I won't let you through!
Well, you don't even have 5 minutes left...!
Fine!
Hotaru, stare at her face,
and decide which card you want to pick!
One is the joker,
and the other is the ace of hearts!
Ace of hearts...
I must make her pick the joker
at any cost... All right!
Now, even I don't know
which one the joker is!
Think hard, and flip over one card...
This will decide everyone's fate...
During that last moment...
...I put a small mark on the joker so
I would know which is which!
I can work on her for a bit...
...and since she's such an honest girl,
she'll pick the card that I want her to pick!
Oh? Do you really want to pick that card?
That's right, I think that's the better choice!
Hotaru!
It doesn't matter which!
Pick the one that you like!
Don't worry about which one!
Just let yourself go and pick one!
You'll do all right!
We all believe in you!
Why...?
Because we all like you so much!
Hotaru!
Just think of this as a game of Memory!
You did it, Hotaru!
Chibiusa...
Hotaru!
It's all right, she just passed out.
Now, you promised!
Take us back!
I forgot whether or not
I ever made that promise!
What did you say!?
You're so unfair!
Say what ever you like!
I can't forgive you any longer!
MOON PRISM POWER...
MAKE UP!
PINK SUGAR...
...HEART...
...ATTACK!
That's funny...
I really had my heart set on it today...
That was dangerous!
But... you were able to get out!
Oh, you're right!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEART ACHE!
I'm against violence!
Love-lovely!!
We're back!
You did it, Sailor Moon!
Hotaru!
Wait a minute!
It would be bad to stay in that outfit!
Oh, I get it...
Hotaru... Thank you!
Hotaru...!
Thank you...
I don't know how I can thank you...!
Someday, you'll regret that you
ever saved her, Sailor Soldiers...
It was too bad, Haruka.
Setsuna, Haruka believes in
Sailor Moon more than either of us.
Who ever said that?
We did it, Chibiusa, Hotaru!
Yeah...!
We really are the ultimate duo, Hotaru!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com