The tough battle has ended, and
peace has returned... or so I thought.
We're in ninth grade now!?
We have to study for
high school entrance exams!
And now there are new enemies
on top of all of this!
Sheesh!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you all!
Silence is approaching!
It's no good... I can't win!
Are you the Messiah?
Please help everyone!
Wait!
What's wrong, Rei?
You seemed to be having a nightmare.
Oh, um, sorry, it's nothing.
It's just that...
I had a strange dream...
A strange dream?
I had a weird dream, too.
I went to the hospital because
I ate too much ice cream.
And there...
Mamo-chan was brought in on a stretcher
because he ate too many mooncakes!
And we bumped into each other
in the kitchen of the hospital...
Isn't it funny?
It's funny...
But it's no time for us
to be having dreams like that.
Usagi, how did you do on
that exam we had two days ago?
Well, I don't think
I got zero points...
We're in ninth grade now!
We have less than a year before
high school entrance exams!
Yeah...
We have to catch up academically;
we're behind because of our battles!
They say, "Don't regret
the fish eggs from before."
Wait, Usagi. Don't memorize that.
It should be "No use
crying over spilt milk."
Oh yeah, you can say it that way, too.
But "the fish eggs from before"
sounds better to me...
Yeah.
Like when Artemis eats the fish eggs
I was looking forward to snacking on...
I think, why didn't I eat them earlier?
But you'd get it wrong on the exam.
Hey, Ami, how do you solve this?
For this problem, you do this...
Kaorinite.
Right here.
The Daimohn Egg has
finally been completed.
Daimohn selects humans with pure
hearts, and steals their hearts.
Pure hearts?
Yes!
The holy grail that allows the holder
to do anything they wish to this world!
It will appear when the three
talismans are gathered at one place!
The three talismans are
the crystallization of...
...the pure, yes, pure
hearts of the chosen ones!
Therefore, if we find the chosen ones,
and get a hold of the talismans--
We will have the holy grail,
and the world, in our hands!!
I'm at a loss!
This score is bad no matter
how you look at it...
I wonder what Mom and Dad
will say when they see this...
More over, what if Rei sees this...
And of course, I always bump
into Rei at times like this!
OW!
Usagi?
Sheesh, Usagi! You're just
standing there all spaced out!
You were all spaced out yourself, Rei!
Move over!
Well, I can't blame you for being
so down with a test score like that.
Well, excuse me!
But, Usagi, you have a lot of good traits
outside of studying, so don't worry.
Oh? You're not like how
you usually are, Rei.
You think so...?
Hey, what do you dream of
doing in the future, Usagi?
Dream...?
I don't know, everything
is so mixed up...
How about you, Rei?
Me?
A singer-songwriter, a model,
a wonderful voice actress, and...
And?
I can't!
A loving wife to someone I love!
I can't say that!
But you just did.
You're going to marry
Mamoru someday, right, Usagi?
Oh! You embarrass me!
So embarrassing! Embarrassing!
With a pathetic score like that, Mamoru
would be more embarrassed than you are.
That hurt.
Studying isn't everything,
but for the future...
Usagi, you have to try a little
harder for Mamoru's sake as well.
Well, I'll see you later.
Cheer up, Usagi.
That's really your only good trait.
Sheesh!
She talks tough, but she honestly wants
the best for me and all of our friends.
Thanks, Rei.
Hurry and appear...
...the one with a pure heart.
But what Rei says IS right...
If Mamo-chan saw a test
score like this...
This is horrible...
...he would say, I'm sure...
Such great weather out today!
Usako...
Well, so we're all getting
together at Rei's house to study!
Looks like you should do that...
Since we haven't been able to study much
due to all the fighting we've been doing.
Then, it will be a little lonely, but I
guess we won't be able to date for a bit.
Well, uh, I don't think...
you need to go... that far...
Now, go do your best.
Thanks.
See ya.
This is tough!
What was that dream last night...?
Rin-byou-tou-sha-kai-jin-retsu-zai-zen!
No good... I can't feel anything...
I wonder if it's nothing after all...
Number 27...
I hope that everyone will live happily
without anything bad happening...
What!?
MIKUJI!
W-What is this...?
I will have your pure heart
that worries about your friends!
Fighting here will get Grandpa
and the others involved too!
Your fortune today is VERY BAD.
Daimohn Mikuji.
There might be a talisman
hidden within this girl.
Take her pure heart.
Daimohn?
MIKUJI!
It is a matter of time
before we see results.
I shall go seek other humans that have
the possibility of holding talismans.
I'd rather go on a date with Mamo-chan
instead of studying after all...
You can't.
I'll go do that after all!
Now, Usagi! You promised everyone
that you would study, didn't you!?
BUT!
If you don't go, I'll--
All right!
Really, Luna, you don't
understand what a girl feels...
You mean how a sloth feels.
That's Rei's voice!
I wonder what's going on?
W-W-W-What is that!?
I don't know,
but you should transform.
MOON CRYSTAL POWER...
...MAKE UP!
Hold it right there!
For love and justice...
...the pretty soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon?
I can't for give you for harassing
my pure-hearted friend!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
She was targeted because
of her pure heart!
The target is a pure heart?
Your fortune is...
...VERY BAD!
What is that monster?
Another monster?
Let's transform and fight!
Your fortunes are...
BAD!
It's strong...
Several times stronger
than previous enemies...
How should I get rid of
these pesky interruptions?
Who is that!?
Ruffian who creates a storm of
riots in the warm sun of spring!
Retreat now!
Shall I tell your fortune too?
Now, Sailor Moon!
Okay!
MOON PRINCESS...
...HALATION!
Damn you!
VERY BAD TRIANGLE!
THE MOST UNLUCKY DAY!
Can such a thing...?
Sailor... Mo-
Usako!
Your fortune is...
BAD!
Tuxedo Mask!
I can't watch anymore.
Luna!
Damn you!
- Artemis!
- Luna!
Is that the last interruption?
Then, I shall take my time
to get the pure heart.
Stop!
Rei!
Rei!!
Rei! Hold yourself together!
Rei! Rei!!
What do you dream of doing
in the future, Usagi?
Me? A singer-songwriter, amodel,
a wonderful voiceactress, and...
I can't! A loving wife to someone
I love. I can't say that!
Cheer up, Usagi.
That's really your only good trait.
Usagi!
Rei...
There must be a talisman inside
this crystal of her pure heart.
Give that back!
Give that back to Rei!
I won't forgive you!
Humans...
Such pathetic creaturrrrrrr...
Wha--!?
What in the world is going on!?
EVIL WARD!
Rei! Rei!
Hold yourself together!
- Rei!
- REI!!
Rei!
Hold yourself together! Rei...
This is not a talisman!
Looks like they had the wrong target.
A trip wasted.
Rei...
Answer me!
Rei...?
She came to...
I...
Rei is back to normal!
I'm so glad!
Usagi...
Are you sure you're not hurt at all?
Yeah, I'm all right.
You don't feel pain?
No.
Do you itch anywhere?
- Do you have anything you want to eat?
- Those two...
Don't cry anymore.
Kaorinite. It seems the target
wasn't the holder of a talisman.
Correct. We also had an
uncalculated interruption.
I will be careful in the future.
The new enemy seems to be
after people with pure hearts.
They said something about
talismans being inside them...
And those two mysterious people...
A... new battle is about to begin...?
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com