Haruka, Michiru...
please undo your transformations!
Will we never understand each other?
We can't feel each other's warmth?
Are we going to bicker and
stay enemies until the end?
Uranus, Neptune...
undo your transformations!
Hotaru!!
Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon! Hang in there!
- Are you all right?
- Hold onto my shoulder...
Chibiusa...!
Usagi... Mamo-chan...
I'm so glad...
Hotaru... Where's Hotaru?
You're kidding...
you're kidding, right?
Hotaru came and visited me!
In my dream... she said thanks...
Chibiusa...
It's all right.
I'm sure she is alive.
Mamo-chan...
That's right!
Sailor Moon risked her life
to protect Hotaru back there!
I'm sure... that she's safe
somewhere out there.
Yeah, I know.
It's all right...
I won't cry anymore.
Usagi, you did your best, right?
Chibiusa...!
Chibiusa!
Good morning!
- Good morning!
- Now, hurry!
The bus is going to leave!
Chibiusa!
- I'll be going now!
- Hurry, hurry!
Usagi...
She's really trying too hard...
In reality, she's worried
sick about Hotaru...
Chibiusa is caring
about others, too.
Even if she cried over it,
all it would do is trouble you, Usagi.
We can't find Sailor Pluto's
whereabouts, nor Hotaru's...
Mina, Makoto, and the others are
doing their best to look for them!
But...
No, I won't give up...
Back then, I did feel Hotaru's warmth...
I still remember it clearly...
We'll see her again...
I'm sure of it!
I'll see you again, I'm sure...
You look so picturesque.
Perhaps it would be nice for the three of
us to live peacefully like this as a family.
Come on...!
Well, it's time.
Yes.
It's farewell, baby...
Ryouichi and Masako Hidaka,
please come to window 4...
Really, what a plump and cute baby!
I'm sure she'll grow up to
be a precocious little girl!
You have a visitor...
Mr. Tomoe.
Hotaru...
Mr. Soichi Tomoe's
amnesia is rather serious...
He has a severe mental trauma
on top of his head injuries...
Fortunately, he's recovering well, so he won't
face any problems returning to society...
But, most of his memory from the past
few years only remains in fragments.
Hm, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
It's strange...
It feels so lonely...
Let's go...
Before we leave that town,
we have one more thing to do.
Chibiusa!
What's wrong?
You don't look too cheerful.
No, I'm fine and full of energy!
Hey, let's go!
Go on ahead!
I'll catch right up with you!
Sure!
Plu...?
Plu!!
You did very well.
I want to hold you
and congratulate you.
But, I no longer have
a physical body in this world.
Plu! Don't say that, come back...
Hotaru isn't here, either...
I'm all alone now!
That is not true.
You have wonderful friends.
And, Sailor Saturn...
Hotaru... is she all right?
Is she alive!?
Within Hotaru, two personalities resided.
Sailor Saturn and...
...Mistress Nine of the Death Busters.
However, Hotaru was able to annihilate
Mistress Nine using Sailor Moon's help...
She has been reincarnated on this beautiful
planet and is about to relive a new life.
Don't go...!!
I will see you once again... someday.
My Small Lady... take care...
Don't go, Plu!!
Oh, is this yours?
Yes... I'm sorry to trouble you.
Hotaru's...
...dad...
Here.
T-Thank you...
Whoa there...
She likes you.
Isn't she cute?
She's my daughter.
What's her name?
Oh, her name is Hotaru.
Right, Hotaru?
Hotaru...
She has been reincarnated on this beautiful
planet and is about to relive a new life.
Mr. Tomoe!
Um...
I hope the baby stays healthy!
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
Hotaru...
I'm happy for you, Hotaru.
I'll see you again, right?
Until then...
Bye-bye...
No good.
The other dimension
is completely gone.
There isn't even a trace of it.
I thought we could get some clue...
Hey, how was it?
Nothing. It's just a normal
building after detonation.
Same here.
We walked all around town,
but we had no clues concerning Hotaru.
Hey, why are you depressed!?
Usagi, you did the best that you could!
Come on, cheer up!
Luna!
What's wrong...?
Don't come here...
Sailor Moon!
Usagi...
Your idealism is too painful to watch.
Michiru...?
Why yes, the world was saved.
But... we can't forgive
you for what you did!
Your idealism in protecting the Warrior
of Ruin almost destroyed this planet...
Usagi, you...
...have no qualifications
to be the future queen!
Oh, how horrible!
I thought we understood each other!
Haruka!
Wait, guys.
Just like we initially
thought these guys...
...are so hardheaded
that it's beyond our reach!
Will you try to bend
these tough heads?
Are you picking a fight!?
NEPTUNE PLANET POWER...
MAKE UP!
URANUS PLANET POWER...
Let's go!
JUPITER STAR POWER...
MARS STAR POWER...
Don't...!
VENUS STAR POWER...
MERCURY STAR POWER...
MAKE UP!
Uranus! Neptune!
I have no grudge against you,
but I can't tolerate you criticizing Usagi!
Sailor Moon fought to
the best of her ability!
Everyone, stop!!
I don't want everyone to fight...
Please stop...
You really are a hopeless idealist.
Usagi...?
Aren't you upset after
all that they've said!?
I'm not upset at all.
Because it's true.
I'm a crybaby... and naive...
But...
I don't think I've done anything wrong!
Sailor Saturn may have
been the Warrior of Ruin...
...but she is still one
of us Sailor Soldiers!
I was happy that we could understand
each other, to feel each other's warmth!
Haruka, Michiru,
please undo your transformations!
Everyone else, too!
Usagi...
If you want us to,
you have to force us to.
Unless you do,
we will be enemies forever...
Usagi...
All right...
Usagi!
Don't help me.
This is my responsibility...
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!
It's finally time for
the main character to appear.
We won't go easy on you.
DEEP...
...SUBMERGE!!
Sailor Moon!
Tuxedo Mask!
For two hearts to truly
understand each other...
...sometimes harsh
collisions are necessary.
No need to interrupt.
What's wrong?
Aren't you going to cry?
Princess Crybaby.
Undo... your transformations!
WORLD...
...SHAKING!
Where is she?
Behind you!
Please stop, Uranus!
Rather amazing.
Sailor Moon!
This is it, Sailor Moon!
What!?
Uranus, Neptune...?
Nothing less from the Princess...
No, the future Neo Queen Serenity.
We have been shown with your
true powers in the very end.
The very end...?
Everything we need to
do in this town is now over.
We found the true Messiah,
and the Earth has been saved.
Our mission has been completed.
The true Messiah... who is it?
Sheesh, there she goes again.
She even draws the
Warrior of Ruin onto her side.
Uranus!
Neptune!
Since we came to this town,
it's been a series of battles.
It was a rather tough everyday life,
right, Neptune?
But it was worth it.
Yeah... It wasn't just Sailor Saturn
that was saved by the messiah.
We were, as well.
I guess I should say... "Thank you"...
Wait... tell me one thing...
Is Hotaru... alive?
I'm sure you'll see her again.
So she's alive...!!
I'm so glad...!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com