Chibiusa, I hope you can
be friends with Hotaru.
Don't worry, you're pretty
wonderful yourself.
Hey, Daimohn!
Big Sister won't allow you to force
your friendship on someone else!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
Bye-bye! See you tomorrow!
Bye-bye, Chibiusa!
Small Lady...
Plu!
Hello, Small Lady.
Plu, you never come visit to play with me.
I thought that you forgot all about me!
Small Lady, in this world,
my name is Setsuna Meioh.
In that case, I'm Usagi, too, you know.
Call me Chibiusa!
Then, I'll call you Set-chan!
You are as you've always been, Small Lady.
It seems that you've made a lot of friends...
Is this day and age fun for you?
Yeah, it's fun! Everyone is very nice to me.
I see.
I'm sure Neo Queen Serenity
sent you to this particular era...
...because she wanted you to
make many friends as a normal girl.
I'm sure it will all be of help to you in
the future, when you become the Queen.
Hey, Plu...
I can see you whenever I
want to from now on, right?
Really?
Yes... I promise you.
Okay!
If I don't get home soon,
Mama-Ikuko will be worried.
Yes...
Bye-bye, Plu!
"I can see you whenever I
want to from now on, right, Plu?"
How cute...
But to think that little one is the
Princess who came from the future...
Small Lady is the official heir to
the throne of the Silver Millennium.
Yeah. I'll at least try to be
careful and not hurt her.
Anyway, we have to find the
Messiah as soon as possible.
The Grail has appeared.
To prevent the silence,
we must make sure that...
...it lands in the hands of
the holy messiah at any cost.
They are still collecting pure hearts.
If that's for them to awaken
the messiah as one of evil...
We must work to deal with that.
The Messiah of Silence...
...must not be born at any cost!
I'm sorry... I can't continue
lying to you anymore...
I can't be with you anymore.
Please forgive me.
Why...!? I love you so much...!
I'm sorry...
But I just can't forget about her...
Impossible!
I'm sorry, Hanako...
I won't forgive you, Yuu! You have me!
What's this about Hanako!?
Who is that woman!?
Yes, Mimet here! I'm currently busy...
It's me.
Oh, Professor!
How studious of you to
be so busy right now.
So, I can get the name
of the next target, right?
Yes, leave it to me.
I'm counting on you, Mimet.
Yuu Kazama... You are so cute that
this hatred grows a hundred fold!
I'll take your pure heart!
Oh, no!
I want to make this world mine quickly.
I want to make this world
beautiful with my own hands.
Please wait a little while longer.
Pure hearts...
Give me pure hearts quickly...
This again...
What have I been doing?
It's always like this after a bad seizure.
Hey, Luna-P, don't move.
Is Hotaru here?
Hotaru is currently resting.
I'm sorry, especially because
you took the time to come here.
Kaori...
It seemed like someone was here just now.
That girl who's always here was here.
And...?
Of course, I had her go back.
Why do you do that without asking!?
Hotaru.
Don't you think you are
acting a little too selfishly?
Because your father is nice, I'm sure
he's letting you do whatever you want.
But you, of all people, should know that your
body doesn't let you play around so much!
Such a scary face.
I wonder what's wrong with Hotaru...
I wonder if she's all right?
Chibiusa!
Hotaru!
Are you all right?
I'm glad... I finally found you.
Hotaru, you look like you're in pain.
I'm sorry about earlier.
Did Kaori say something mean to you?
I was just worried about that...
Hotaru!
I'm sorry...
Hotaru!!
Hotaru!
That's...?
Chibiusa...?
Chibiusa!
What's wrong!?
Usagi!
Hotaru!
Usagi! Save Hotaru!
Come on, Usagi!
Chibiusa...
Hotaru...
Hotaru is...!!
Chibiusa, calm down.
Ami...
My mother's hospital is nearby.
Let's take Hotaru there.
Hotaru...
If I didn't go visit your house,
this wouldn't have happened...
It's all my fault...
That's not true.
You are a dear friend for Hotaru as well...
That's why she overexerted
herself to come see you.
That's why you should be
at her side now, Chibiusa...
That way, Hotaru will be relieved, too.
She will be all right!
Who did this to my goldfish...?
Who...?
Oh, my, you're saying strange things...
This is something you did yourself.
Please hurry and clean it up.
I don't know about it!
Good morning...
What's wrong?
Did you get hurt? Are you all right?
She's the one who injured him.
That's so mean to ask what's wrong.
She's really scary.
She acts all prim and proper at school, too.
I...
Apparently, I hurt another friend again.
But, I really don't remember any of it.
It's all right, Hotaru.
Calm down.
You're not the bad one.
You're not bad at all.
I'm not able to make any friends!
There's a different person
hiding inside of me...
The part of me that hurts
the people I care about...
Mother will be coming by soon.
I'm glad.
It seems like her seizure has been
settled down. It's all right now...
Hotaru.
Chibiusa...
Hotaru! You shouldn't get up yet!
I'm fine...
You don't hurt anywhere?
You're not in pain at all?
I'm glad...
I'm so glad!
Chibiusa...
How is it? Feeling any better?
Yes.
I think you should lie
down for a while longer...
I'm all right. It's just one
of my regular seizures...
Are you really all right?
I'm sorry to have troubled you.
My mother, a doctor, will be here soon.
I'm sorry...
My family has strictly told me that I can't
have any outside doctors take a look at me.
So I'll go home now.
I'll see you later, Chibiusa. Thank you.
I'll walk you back.
I really thank you very much...
Hotaru.
The hotcakes that my mom
makes are really yummy.
Come visit us next time.
We'll treat you to them!
Sure!
That's a promise!
Little one!
Haruka...
Yo!
Where are you going?
If you want, I'll give you a ride...
Thank you, Haruka...
This is the right road?
Yes.
What's your name?
My name is Hotaru Tomoe.
By any chance, are you
Professor Soichi Tomoe's daughter?
Yes...
I see...
Hotaru...
Can I come visit your place again...?
Would it be bad? Am I just a nuisance?
No, you're not a nuisance...
I was really happy that you came.
Really?
Yeah...
I'm glad.
Yuu Kazama?
You're Yuu Kazama from
"Jump Out Friends," right?
Yeah...
It IS you!
I'm so thrilled!
I'm a huge fan of yours!
I see...
Actually, I have a question I want to ask you...
I have a friend over there
that is a HUGE fan of yours.
Can we spare a minute of your time?
You know...
- Please, just an autograph!!
- W-Wait a minute...
Right now... the wind was rustling...
Over there...
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry... I'm getting a little thirsty.
I'll go buy something over at that park.
Okay...
Can it be?
Hotaru...
Can you wait here just for a minute?
You know, I'm troubled by things like this.
Where is this friend of yours?
Actually, right here...
Are you mocking me?
It's your fault... for finding another woman...
You two-timer!
Appear, Daimohn!
Utomodachi!
A monster!
Let's spread this friendship to the world!
I want to be friends with you forever...
H-Hold on...
So... give me your pure heart!
Who is it!?
You can't win over a man's heart by force.
A Sailor Soldier!
Just as I thought...
Everyone, a Daimohn has appeared
at the park in the fourth block!
Got it!
All right!
MOON PRISM POWER...
MAKE UP!
Utomodachi!
Make her one of your friends, too!
Everyone is friendly to each other,
they're all a happy family!
Hey, Daimohn!
That's enough of that!
For love and justice...
...an apprentice to a pretty
soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
In the name of the future moon...
...I'll punish you!
That was perfect!
Idiot! Don't come over to a place like this!
Idiot!?
You want to be my friend, too?
You silly girl you...
Little girl, jump right in!
This is off-limits to kids!
I'm a soldier, too!
But we seem to be in trouble...
Is it my fault?
This again...
Don't be shy and be my friend!
Who would!?
Hold it right there!
A bad guy who hasn't given
up and is after pure hearts!
For love and justice!
The Sailor Team!
In the name of the moon...
...we'll punish you!
More interruptions! Utomodachi!
I'm leaving the rest to you!
Lady Mimet!!
I was going to be a good friend
with you, too! That's it! I quit!
You guys...
...I hate all of you!
What is that...?
Oh, no!
Hotaru is over there!
Out of the way, out of the way!
My body doesn't move...
What in the world are you...!?
T-This is...!?
Hotaru!
Sailor Moon!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEARTACHE!
Love-Lovely!!
Hotaru...
Hotaru! Hold yourself together!
Chibiusa.
Are you all right?
You shouldn't see me anymore...
At this rate, I'm sure I'll hurt you, Chibiusa.
Why?
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
Hotaru!
Sailor Moon.
Yes?
It's better to keep the little one...
...away from that girl for a while.
What do you mean by that?
Just make sure it gets through to her!
What does she mean by that!?
She's not a bad girl!
I wonder if it has something
to do with our enemy...?
I don't know...
Hotaru.
Chibiusa.
It would be nice if you could be
friends with that wonderful girl.
It's all right, Chibiusa,
we're behind you, too!
What's most important is the honest
feeling that you want to be friends with her!
Yeah!
All right, I'm going to do my best!
Next time, I'll go say hello to her father!
- Hey, I'll go with you.
- Me, too! Me, too!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com