The pure love of the
boy named Umino...
...tastes slightly
like a lemon.
Confess your feelings,
you fried shrimp.
And don't forget the julienne
cabbage on the side.
I won't forgive
you for stealing...
...such a delicious-sounding
pure heart of a boy!
I, Sailor Moon...
...will punish you in
the name of the moon!
Professor.
It's you, Kaorinite.
Yes.
A talisman is inside
lovers' pure hearts.
Professor?
A new Daimohn egg...
Kaorinite.
How many Daimohn eggs must we
waste to retrieve the talismans...?
What of the nuisances who call
themselves the Sailor Soldiers?
At this rate, I can't
expect any results...
...no matter how many
Daimohn eggs I throw out.
Then I will head out
personally this time.
All right.
Leave it to me.
Umino?
He's not here yet?
Usagi...
What do you want in
a place like this?
I have a secret to
talk to you about.
A secret?
Naru has been
acting weird lately.
Weird?
I can't put it
into words well...
N-No, nothing's wrong.
Umino... I'm sorry, but can
you go home without me?
It seems like she's
hiding something from me.
Stop it, I'm not
hiding anything.
I'm sure it's something
she can't tell me.
Maybe she has a
new boyfriend now!
Everyday, for Naru, I made
her favorite: fried shrimp!
Because I wanted
Naru to eat this!
This fried shrimp of
sweat, tears, and love!
Umino... Are you really
worried about all this?
In any case, I'll casually
bring it up with Naru later.
Usagi, I'm counting on you.
Hey, Naru.
What do you think
about Umino lately?
He's been acting
weird lately.
He gets really fidgety
when he's in front of me.
How to say it...? Maybe he's
keeping a secret from me.
What, you too, Naru?
Nothing. And what
about this secret?
Maybe he's got
a new girlfriend.
Considering it's Umino of all
people, I'm sure it's okay!
Y-You think so...?
Yeah! There's no way Umino
would be so popular with girls!
Well, excuse me!
He does have a lot of
good things about him!
Naru?
I've had enough.
I'm going home!
N-Naru...
So, Naru thinks
about Umino, too.
Oh, I get it!
This is so simple!
I just have to get rid of
their misunderstandings!
At times like this,
I can rely on...
Leave it to Rei for all
your romance problems!
Rei, of course!
...and that's how it is now.
Oh, if they care about
each other, it's easy.
All we need to do is
have them confirm...
...their feelings for
each other, right?
Yeah. It's just like you, Rei,
to say something good.
There's a perfect event
for such a situation!
Ta-dah!
Oh? Lovers' Park?
Yup! As part ofthe
grand opening...
...they're having
an affection contest.
If we can get Umino and
Naru to participate...
That's great! A great idea!
The winners get to
light a flame of love...
...in a heart-
shaped monument!
That's so lovely! I'd love
to do that with Mamo-chan!
Idiot! What are you going
to do by entering, Usagi?
Their love will deepen as
a result of the contest!
Then, Mamo-chan
and I could--
As I was saying,
if you win the contest...
...you'll ruin
their relationship!
Oh, I get it...
Rei, you're so smart!
It's first come, first serve,
so better apply early.
Yeah!
Hurry, hurry!
Where are you going, Usagi?
Don't worry about
that yet. Leave it to me!
Let's go!
Here!
T-That can't be...
- Usagi!
- Usagi...!
What's wrong?
I wanted you two to make up
by entering this contest...
- Usagi, actually...
See?
Umino!
Naru...
A-Actually, I wanted to
enter the contest with Naru....
Then you should
have said so earlier.
I thought so as well, but I
didn't quite get a chance to...
That's why you
were so fidgety.
Sheesh! You can
be such an idiot!
You say that...
...but you were feeling
the same way, Naru!
I-I wasn't as bad as Umino...
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
All right!
Ouch!
Now I'm perfectly ready
for tomorrow's contest!
I have to go to sleep early
tonight to prepare for it!
One sheep. Baa...
Two sheep.
Baa... Baa...
I can't be nervous.
I have to go to sleep.
Four sheep.
Oh, wait, the third
sheep got lost.
30,003 sheep.
Baa... Baa...
Baa! Baa!
I have to sleep!
I have to sleep soon!
Baa! Baa! BAA!
I feel an evil presence
in this park.
I'm sure there will be
a Daimohn around here.
I won't let them
have the talisman.
Now both of you, do your best.
Y-Yeah. We'll do our best.
Umino, are you all right?
- YES!
- He doesn't look all right...
Huh? Everyone!
Oh, there she is.
What are you
guys doing here?
To cheer those two on!
I'm wherever there is romance!
It seems a little fun, too.
I was thinking I could
make use of it someday...
For what?
D-Don't take me seriously.
It was just a play on words.
Huh? It's Haruka and Michiru.
Wonderful!
I wonder if they're in
the contest as well.
Two girls together?
But looking at them like this,
it's like they really were lovers...
Everyone, the affection
contest is about to begin!
Please gather at the stage!
Well, let's go cheer them on!
Everyone, are you
living full of love?
The couples here are
the selected people...
...who are overflowing in love!
And today, we'll
have these couples...
...compare how deep their
feelings of love are!
The winning couple will be
the couple with a pure heart...
...that love each
other the most!
Go for it, Naru!
Hold yourself together, Umino!
You look wonderful, Michiru!
Look over here, Haruka!
Come on...
Who did you come
here to cheer on?
That's what you call a
sudden change of heart.
- Oh, is that so?
- I'm sorry!
The first game is
just a small test.
Let's have them guess their lover's
hand that appears through the hole!
Begin, from those
that figured it out!
T-This sure was a fast one!
It's Haruka...
I wonder if they really are
in THAT kind of a relationship.
Now, scream out
your lover's name!
What!?
Can you tell us
your lover's name?
You sure want me to do
something really cheap.
I'm begging you. It's just
what the script says.
Michiru.
Success! A correct guess!
Now, let's keep
going at this pace!
- They did it!
- Next up is Umino!
Which one is
Naru's hand?
Here, Umino,
take a handkerchief.
Make sure to wipe
yourself dry.
T-That's it!
Naru's hand is...
...this one!
Now, call out your
girlfriend's name!
Naru, my angel...
You're wrong!
Sorry, you made a mistake.
Oh, well...
T-That can't be!
I'm sure Naru had
a Band-Aid on her finger...
What are you doing!?
That hurts!
Sheesh. There's no way I
would still have a wound...
...from six months ago
on my finger, Umino!
But he still remembered
something from that far back...
Are you all right?
Yes.
Nothing compared to the pain
Naru's heart is feeling!
Naru, please forgive me!!
Let's go to our
next contestant...
They sure try hard.
It's only a game.
It is, but...
I think being able to become
that serious is a wonderful thing.
It's not just
a game for him...
The three-legged race
of love! START!
The karaoke of love!
"A sea turtle's egg..."
Wrong song, Umino...
Pitiful.
But he has the best
heart of them all.
He's taking this
so seriously.
I'll admit to that.
It would be nice
if they could win...
Now, it's finally
the last game!
Even the ones who've been losing
have a shot at turning it around!
It's the Confess
Your Love Game!
You in the audience are
going to award them points!
We'll determine how many points
by the volume of the applause!
Are you ready!?
YEAH!
Starting with these two!
Now, a confession
from him to her!
Show is over.
I said the show is over.
We'll drop out of this one.
But...
We weren't taking this
seriously to begin with...
...and it looks like
we'd win at this rate.
True love is
what needs to win.
Love...
Love is everything!
So, with that...
Farewell!
Encore! Encore!
N-Now, the next
couple, please.
Hanako... Come with me.
Takao...
I'm so happy!
Hanako... You have bad
eyesight, don't you?
Love is, love is...
...a BATTLE!!
L-Love is to endure...
Red wins!
Now, it's finally time
for the last couple!
Come on!
- We've been waiting for this!
- Umino, do it well!
N-Naru!
Umino!
Is he all right...?
Umino...
Naru...
Naru, you're always
bright, just like the sun.
Umino...
I'm always being
such a klutz...
...and I might not be worthy
of someone like you, Naru.
Why do you continue to
see someone like me...?
Maybe it's just
a whim of God.
When I think that...
B-But!
I'm happy just by seeing
your smile, Naru.
For Naru's
angelic smile...
...and to protect
your beautiful smile...
I... I, Gurio Umino...
...can die!
U-Umino...
Umino...
Now, what do you
think of this couple?
Great!
You're the best in Japan!
Such an ovation!
By unanimous vote,
this couple is the winner!
Now, both of you,
light the flame of love!
Umino, we did it!
Y-Yes.
This is the proof of
Naru's and my love...
Naru's and my...
What?
What is it!?
DIE HEART!
Umino! Run!
The monument of the love
between us, Naru...!
Just hurry!
Inside the pure heart
which thinks of...
...one's lover,
we find a talisman.
Dammit!
Look out, Naru!
Umino!
- Umino!
MOON COSMIC POWER, MAKE UP!
MERCURY STAR POWER, MAKE UP!
MARS STAR POWER, MAKE UP!
JUPITER STAR POWER, MAKE UP!
VENUS STAR POWER, MAKE UP!
I've found it.
Hold it right there!
Who is it, HEART?
To ruin the light of love that
they finally got a hold of...!
Umino!
Even if the cupid of
love forgave you...
...I won't forgive you!
For love and justice, the pretty
soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
Likewise, Sailor Mars!
Sailor Mercury!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Jupiter!
In the name of the moon,
I punish you!
You're...!
Little ladies...
Girls should behave like girls.
LET'S DANCING!
W-Well, just for a little bit.
Your hand...
Sure...
Guided by a new era,
Sailor Uranus...
...acts with elegance!
Likewise, Sailor Neptune...
...acts with grace!
Die Heart, provide dance partners
for these girls as well.
DIE HEART!
I'll find my
own dance partner!
WORLD SHAKING!
DIE HEART!
It's no time to be
fooled by illusions.
R-Right!
No matter how
many you defeat...
...we can make more
and more Daimohn eggs.
Then we will defeat you!
We'll settle the score now.
Is that so?
You need 10 more years of
training to fight me!
See you.
Dammit!
Umino! Umino,
please, answer me!
Quick, the crystal!
DIE HEART!
It's not it...
It's not a talisman.
Who are you?
Take good care of him.
Umino! I'm so glad!
Naru?
DIE HEART!
That trick won't
work this time!
MOON SPIRAL HEART ATTACK!
LOVELY!
Now, turn the switches on!
Applause for
the happy couple!
I'm so happy for them.
Yeah, it's thanks
to you, Rei!
Umino looks happy.
He really did do his best.
I'm jealous.
I wish I could...
Even you, Umino the klutz,
did your best.
Y-Yeah...
By the way, what's
for lunch tomorrow?
I'm so happy, I'll be
making fried lobsters!
But is that yummy?
I don't know...
Sheesh, Umino!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com