A beautiful flower has thorns...
Just kidding -- I didn't mean me!
A rose always comes with thorns.
But the flower is beautiful
and calms the spirit down!
Hey, you over there who stomps
down on such feelings for flowers!
I, Sailor Moon, will punish you
in the name of the moon!
How about this?
It's cute!
Mamo-chan, thank you!
Why is Chibiusa the only
one who gets all the stuff!.?
I can't help it.
It's because she has a picnic.
Yeah, yeah!
Why are you agreeing, Luna?
Sheesh, it's no use taking
such a petty thing out on Luna...
That's right!
I'm not a backpack...
I know! Mamo-chan, let's go on
a picnic, too! Just the two of us!
Oh, come on... Come on!
No fair!
- Me, too, me, too! Me, too!!
- Let's go, Mamo-chan! Let's go, Mamo-chan!
Hey, now...
All right, all right!
Oh, Hotaru!
Wait, Hotaru!
Don't run away...
We're friends, right!?
Friends...?
That's right!
We are... right!?
Chibiusa...
That girl...
She must have some big
reason behind all this...
Haruka also said that I shouldn't
let Chibiusa near that girl, too...
But she's not a bad girl!
She can't be! Right?
Hotaru...
Release my powers!
Hurry!
Can you not hear the voices
of time calling for me!?
Let us hurry,
using the pure hearts of humans...
You are...?
Um... Please, give this to Hotaru!
Good-bye!
Kaori, that...?
It's that girl again...
She told me to give this to you, Hotaru...
"Hotaru, let's go on a picnic tomorrow."
"I'll make plenty of lunch!
So, Hotaru, you come with this backpack!
From Chibiusa."
So selfish...
She knows that you're a frail girl, too.
How wonderful!
Papa...
Since I can't spend much time
with you with all of my research...
You go and have as
much fun as you want.
We're going now!
Is this all food...?
Yeah! I got up early to make it all!
Will it fit in the trunk...?
Hotaru can't come after all, I guess...
Chibiusa!
Hotaru!
You can come to the picnic!
This place is huge!
Woohoo!
Hotaru! Usagi! Hurry, hurry!
Wait for me, Chibiusa!
Ready, set, toss!
Tie, set, toss!
I told them to not get near her...
Are you saying she has something to
do with our enemy, the Death Busters?
I'm not sure... but I have
a bad feeling about this.
I feel the presence of
something tremendously evil.
But... it looks fun...
Are you all right?
Y-Yes...
A graduate of my school works here.
He's a botanist, with his lifework
being his research on roses.
Wait, Chibiusa!
Catch me if you can, Usagi!
You're slower than a tortoise!
You did that on purpose, didn't you!?
Yes, Professor?
Mimet, what is your
favorite color for roses?
Oh, my...! If I could have any,
it would be a million red roses...!
Improving and breeding of roses is a job
that requires good sense and patience!
There apparently is a botanist with
good results in that field, I take it?
That MUST be an owner of a pure heart!
The target has been determined.
All right... Let me make a
Daimohn most suited for that man.
I'm counting on you.
Ubara!
- Amazing...
- This is beautiful!
There are so many of them!
Yo! Is that you, Mamoru?
Sir!
How've you been?
You've still got beautiful women with you!
"Still"...?
I-It's a joke!
Sir!
Papa!
Mama's lunch!
The main dish is a croquet?
- You're right!
- Correct!
So many...
There's even more of them...
Oh, Professor!
You have to use proper
sense to choose the targets!
And stop!
From here, you will help Mama back home!
Okay!
Don't trip!
Bye bye!
You're kidding...!
It's a croquet!
How goes the research
for new types of roses?
Oh, I think I'm almost there!
Hotaru, don't be bashful and eat up!
Okay.
Here!
Chibiusa! You have to eat
the bell peppers, too!
Mamo-chan isn't eating them, either!
What was that?
Mamo-chan! Eat! You have to eat!
But, you know...
EAT!
All right, I understand...
Now it's your turn, Chibiusa!
EAT!
A-All right!
Hotaru, you don't think the lunch is yummy?
It's not that...
I was just thinking how I haven't eaten
like this with Papa in quite a while...
There are times when
adults are hellishly busy.
It's more fun to spend that time playing with
your friends than to complain about it!
Right!?
What are you doing, Chibiusa...!?
Better! That guy is much better!!
Appear, Dai--
I'm counting on you, Mimet.
P-Professor!
Almost every variety of rose growing in
Japan are planted in this greenhouse!
Amazing... and they're all so beautiful!
Are you tired?
No...
They're beautiful, aren't they?
Other than these, many
different types of roses have...
...been grown thanks to
improvements made to them.
Improvements...!
It's hard to believe that an old man
like him improved these...
It would be better to just let it go free, and
let it bloom wherever it wanted to bloom...
Hotaru...
These are tropical plants.
Come over here.
Let's go!
I'm tired... You can go on ahead.
Um...
Can you tell me the name of this flower?
- Oh, I don't know...
- You should ask the researcher over there!
Oh, I totally thought that
HE was the researcher...
You look so intelligent!
If you don't mind, how about we
have a conversation in private?
I'm sorry...
But I'm here to spend time with my family.
O-Oh, are they your sisters?
No, they're my future wife and child.
Now, excuse me...
W-What was that!?
Fine, I will have to take
the pure heart by force...!
The heart of the botanist...
The heart--
The future wife... wife... wife... Wife, is it?
It's not something to be that thrilled
about now, after all this time...
I'll be with Hotaru!
Yeah... Be at her side.
Yeah.
I should go back...
before anything happens...
W-What is this?
It's hailing out of season?
It's coming down pretty hard...
Oh, no, this is bad!
Oh, no! We have a problem!
Let's help!
Yeah!
Hotaru!
Hotaru--!
Dammit!
Thanks!
It's all right...
I have to protect these
saplings, if nothing else...
I was finally able to make a species
that was strong against illness.
Strong against illness...?
Improvements aren't just
about making it more beautiful!
Are you all right?
Hold yourself steady...!
Who is it...!?
Work is work.
The path to the chief executive is
more important than romance!
I'll take the old man's pure heart!
Appear, Daimohn!
Ubara! Bara bara!
Petals with no luster...
Too much fertilizer.
S-Shut up!
Hurry up and finish your job!
W-What are you doing!?
Hey, stop it!
It's a Daimohn!
MOON PRISM POWER...
MAKE UP!
Those who don't take good care of flowers!
That's the type of people
who will ruin the Earth!
For love and justice, an apprentice
to a pretty soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
In the name of the future moon...
...I'll punish you!
A pesky little girl!
Ubara!
Ubara! Bara bara!
Attacking with a rose is a move
that I use as a last resort.
I am troubled by copycats.
D-Damn you!
It's too early to be so angry.
The main event finally appears.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
For love and justice...
...the pretty solder in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon, I'll punish you!
Ubara, kill every last one of them!
THE RED ROSE OF PASSION!
PINK SUGAR...
...HEART...
...ATTACK!
What are you doing,
losing to a little girl like that!?
Beautiful roses are full of thorns!
EMBRACE OF ROSES!
Give them a good squeeze!
Oh, no!
Take this!
Are you all right?
What are you doing!?
There's no way you would
lose to girls like them!
Damn you...!
Jealousy is the meaning
behind yellow roses!!
W-What is this!?
Oh... Tuxedo Mask!!
T-This hurts!
I did it! I finally did it!
I'm withering!
What's wrong, Ubara?
Now, Sailor Moon!
Yeah!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEART ACHE!
I'm already withered!
Bara bara!
That's why I wasn't too
thrilled about doing this!
What was that?
I felt a strong power for a moment...
It's an eerie pulse of darkness...!
Please be careful, Small Lady...
Hotaru!
I'm so glad!
Chibiusa...?
Papa! Are you all right?
Oh, I'm fine! I'm fine!
But... did I have a dream?
It was a terrible storm!
But let's come here again!
Yes...
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com