I see, so this is Chibiusa's
new friend Hotaru Tomoe...
Hey, she's pretty cute!
Elegant, and somewhat fragile...
Totally different from you!
Make sure you aren't rude to her!
If you do cause her any trouble...
In the name of the moon, I'll punish you!
Oh, Chibiusa, you seem to
be in a rather good mood.
I have a new friend!
Oh?
Come on, tell me,
what kinda person? A boy?
How far into the relationship
are you? Tell me!
I won't tell klutz Usagi anything!
How dare you!
What are you doing, Usagi, you idiot!
We have been waiting for you, Mamoru...
No, Sir Endymion.
The warriors of the Silver Millenium,
from the distant past...
And... ones summoned from the future.
URANUS PLANET POWER...
MAKE UP!
NEPTUNE PLANET POWER...
PLUTO PLANET POWER...
MAKE UP!
Sailor Uranus, guarded by Uranus,
the star of the wind.
Sailor Neptune, guarded by Neptune,
the star of the ocean.
Sailor Pluto, guarded by Pluto,
the star of the afterlife.
We are the three warriors
of the outer solar system!
The outer solar system...
Unlike the previous Sailor Soldiers,
we were given even stronger powers.
From the distant past, our duty has
been to protect the Silver Millennium...
...from enemies who intrude
from outside the solar system.
But, when we awakened in this age...
...the enemy had already quietly
nested deep down on this Earth.
We had overlooked it. The intrusion of
the enemy this time is our mistake.
Those are the Death Busters...
Our new enemy...!
But why don't you try to join your
forces with Sailor Moon's group?
They only get in our way...
What?
This battle... is too much for Sailor Moon...
...and for Mars, Venus, and the others.
Defeating the Death Busters,
the largest and strongest enemies...
...is the job of us three.
Eh? Chibiusa went to
all of your places, too?
Yeah. She was saying how she was invited to
a new friend's house for the very first time...
A formal dress? No, no.
As long as you look tidy, you're totally okay!
Don't you want to play to your heart's content?
She came to me, too, saying she
wanted to give something as a gift...
Hmm... I don't think you
need to bring anything...
But how about a book?
Your friend will know what kind of books
you like to read as well, Chibiusa.
She sure has that friend on her mind,
don't you think? Right?
Although they go to different schools,
I heard that her friend is a very quiet person.
So she's visiting a friend
for the first time, huh?
I just baked some cookies,
so I'll wrap you some.
You can take them to your friend's place.
If I'd known, I'd have baked cookies with a
more extravagant way to express her feelings.
H-Huh?
Extravagant cookies...?
I'm a little scared...
She doesn't know any bounds lately...
Who--
Chibiusa came to my place, too...
Rei...?
Let's see... greetings when
you're invited somewhere...
I, Usagi, will lecture you on
things like that right on the spot!
Usagi!
What are you saying, Usagi!
You have a study group to attend!
Oh! Michael!
Where? Where, where?
My Michael!
Oh, Michael...
Usagi...
Sheesh...
I'm telling you, you should bring
a more serious book if it's a gift...
No. I was finally able to buy
one that's always sold out.
I wanted the new Ukon Katakuri book...
No!
By the way, Usagi, are you
serious about tagging along?
Well, I am curious.
What kind of person
your friend is, and such...
My friend is cute...
...although a little frail, it seems.
I feel a little sorry for your friend,
but that's just the perfect situation!
Then, I really should introduce
myself as your guardian.
What part of you is my guardian?
- Now, now... let's go, let's go.
- Don't push me!
Our illustrious Messiah of silence,
the time of your awakening is approaching!
For that, I need powerful awakening energy.
Leave it to me. I will change perfect, pure
hearts of humans into awakening energy.
I hope they suit your tastes...
Amazing!
It's a huge house!
Usagi, push it.
Oh? Yeah, sure.
Oh, hello...
Excuse--
Ka--
K-Kaorinite...
What are you doing, Usagi!?
- Chibiusa.
- Those cookies were for...
May I ask who you are?
Is something wrong?
Is it a guest?
Professor...
Oh, you're one of Hotaru's friends.
Oh, she's Hotaru's...
Hello!
Hello and welcome.
I'm Hotaru's father.
H-Hello...
Oh, this is my assistant, Kaori.
Kaori, Hotaru is a little busy right now.
Lead these ladies to the living room...
Yes.
Should I brew some tasty coffee...?
Please, this way.
Okay!
She looks exactly like her,
but seems to be a different person...
Well, if you think about it,
Kaorinite wouldn't be in a place like this...
"What are you here for, Drop?"
"It's your fault that Andre died."
"No, Auntie, it is not!"
"Yes, it was--"
"Hush! Get out of my room!"
"Drop!"
How, how, how sad this main character is!
Yes, this is Mimet.
You finally answered.
Mimet, have you found a new target?
Of course, I've checked
out a talented pure heart.
This will do.
The target will be holding
an autograph session...
Er, no, appearing at the
Juban Bookstore today.
I see... Then I will hurry up
and make a Daimohn...
...in order for it to make
it to the autograph session.
Delicious coffee is ready!
Uhenshu!
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Please continue to support me.
Yes! I'll cherish this book
for the rest of my life!
The coffee... isn't here yet...
Usagi!
Hotaru... is late...
Chibiusa!
Hotaru!
A g-girl?
Who said it was a boy?
Your older sister...?
My cousin, Usagi.
She tagged along, thinking I was
going on a date with a cute little boy!
Wha-! C-Chibiusa, I just...
It's true, isn't it?
I-I was just wanting to say
hello as your guardian...
What are you saying?
I can see through to what
you really were thinking!
No, you're wrong!
In the first place, it's all because
you're chasing after boys all the time!
Tee hee! Unlike you, klutzy Usagi,
I'm popular with guys!
What?!
See, she's laughing at me!
So it's my fault?
I-I'm sorry...
Welcome here.
I'm Hotaru Tomoe.
Oh, uh, hello...
I hope you don't mind us here...
I'm sorry to keep you waiting...
Please, come up to my room.
Then, we'll take the coffee up to your room...
That's all right!
Don't butt into house affairs, Kaori!
I'm sorry...
My father is a scientist.
Because he's busy with his research,
she comes by to help out, but...
Hotaru, where's your mother?
She died... a long time ago...
Oh, I-I'm sorry... ur...
No, it's all right.
But I want to hear more
about you guys, Chibiusa!
Amazing! It's so beautiful!
Amazing, just amazing! It feels mysterious...
Thanks.
Hotaru!
Hotaru, what's wrong? Are you all right?
I-I'm fine...
I was just a little dizzy.
I'm really all right.
What is... this?
T-This is...?
It's a strange brooch...
As long as I touch it, I feel better and better...
Power fows in...
Hotaru!?
Did I just say something?
I'm sorry. I am rather strange...
T-That's not...
I know! Chibiusa, your gift, your gift!
That's right, yeah, yeah.
This is really interesting!
What's this?
What, what?
Ukon Katakuri... autograph... session!?
It's already started!
Why didn't you realize this earlier!?
You were there in the
bookstore with me, Usagi!
It's your fault!
Why mine!?
Oh, thank you very much for your hard word!
Thank you so much!
Thank you!
Mr. Ukon!
You are...?
Thank you for the autograph earlier!
Oh, yeah...
And, I have one more thing I want from you...
...your heart.
Appear, Daimohn!
W-What's this!?
Uhenshu!
Do you follow your deadlines?
Autograph session!
Are you all right?
I-I'm sorry.
Don't say you're sorry. We're friends.
What's wrong, Usagi?
You take care of Hotaru!
Oh, got it!
Hotaru, we're changing our plans!
Since the autograph session is
already over, let's go to the arcade!
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!
Hold it right there!
There are people who haven't
gotten their autographs yet!
Those who harm handsome
people in this world...
For love and justice,
the pretty soldier in a sailor suit!
I, Sailor Moon...
...will punish you in the name of the moon!
You're here again? You're just a pest!
Uhenshu, get rid of her!
All right, editor-in-chief.
Who's the editor-in-chief?
Just hurry up and get rid of her!
Ultimate attack!
WHITE MANUSCRIPT HELL!
Next up is photocomposition!
I can't move!
Cut and paste!
Snip, snip...
Wait a minute?
What are you planning to do?
Make sure to get a good snipping of her!
Hey!!
DEAD SCREAM...
Pluto.
Leave the fighting to us.
Uranus! Neptune!
Thanks.
Hurry up and get away from here!
Sheesh, why do they
crop up one after another!?
DEEP...
...SUBMERGE!
I'm all right even in sudden storms!
I'm telling you to run!
Why...?
G nibs, round nibs, kabla nibs!
Why? WHY!?
- We're comrades, we're both Soldiers!
- You're in the way!
MANUSCRIPT HELL!
WORLD...
...SHAKING!
The sudden strength right before a deadline!
Borderline... safe!
VENUS LOVE ME CHAIN!
Sailor Venus!
Sailor Mars!
Sailor Jupiter!
Sailor Mercury!
The Sailor Team is here!
W-When did they...?
Guys!
Uranus, guys...
Tuxedo Mask!
Our individual ability
might be inferior to you.
But Sailor Moon has comrades
who combine their forces to fight...
Sheesh, why do they all get together to...
What should we do?
Oh, geez, just get rid of
all of them as a bunch!
But, if there are this many...
What? You have your prized weapons!
But I used up all of them...
- You're no good!
- Now, Sailor Moon!
Oh, okay!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEART ACHE!
See ya. I'm leaving the rest to you.
W-Wait a-- Wait!
Stick to your deadlines!!
Thanks, guys.
I didn't want to help out someone
who ditches their study group...
I apologize for that.
If Chibiusa is with her friend, let's contact her.
I'm sure she's worried right now.
Oh, so you guys went to Crown Arcade.
We had so much fun!
You know, Hotaru had never
gone to an arcade before!
You forgot that we were fighting, didn't you?
Her family seems to be rather complicated...
...but she seems like a good girl.
Yeah. I want to be better friends with her!
Hotaru...
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com