There's a talisman
inside my heart?!
On top of that, the enemy
found out who I really am!!!
Kaorinite took my brooch,
so I can't transform!
And Mamo-chan got imprisoned
in glass trying to protect me!
We're in huge trouble!
Tell me, everyone!
What in the world
should I do?!
Tuxedo Mask!!
That's enough!
The pretty soldiers in sailor
suits now make their entrance!
So, you've shown up...
Usagi Tsukino and
the Sailor Soldiers!
If you want to save Tuxedo Mask,
come to Tokyo Tower!
That will be where
you all will die!
Mamo-chan!
Usagi!
That's...!
Neptune and Uranus...
I'm sure they were
after Usagi's pure heart!
Those guys are like hyenas...!
Usagi!
Wait!
I'm sure the enemy
is waiting for us...
...with a trap
ready to spring!
Now that you can't
transform, Usagi...
...we have to come
up with some plan!
But, but...
Because Mamo-chan
tried to save me...
I'm still going
to save Mamo-chan!
Usagi!
Haruka!
Hey, buns-head.
Going somewhere so late?
Please! Haruka, can you
give me a ride?!
Sure...
Usagi! Usagi!
Usagi, you're so...
She's not thinking at all...!
Do you think you can do
everything all by yourself?!
Usagi.
Have you made up
with your boyfriend?
Y-Yeah...
Buns-head...
Humans all live by
sacrificing someone in the end.
Don't you think so?
What do you mean by that?
For instance...
Let's say that someone
you know is in danger...
...because they were
covering your back.
At times like that,
the person in danger...
...won't think about himself
and wishes you to be safe.
It could be your friend
or it could be your parent...
Everyone lives by
stepping upon someone else.
I know that we
will have victims!
Then why?!
It's our mission!
Nobody wants any victims.
But if that's going to
save the entire world...
What would you do?
Don't you think so, Usagi?
But...
The people doing the stepping
might be fine with that...
...but what about the people
who are getting stepped on?!
Shouldn't you think about the
people who are being sacrificed?!
I can't ignore other people
suffering just to save myself!
It might be impossible
for me alone...
...but if we all joined forces...
...we'd be able to find a way
to avoid sacrificing anyone!
- I'm sure of it!
- Usagi... You're a kind girl.
Is this the place?
Yes. Thank you very much.
Are you all right
with this, Haruka?
That girl...is going to die.
We can't help it!
To get the Grail, to save
the world from silence...
...buns-head will have
to be our sacrifice!!
Welcome, Usagi Tsukino.
Now, get on the elevator.
I will show you a route
straight to heaven.
- No good!
- Looks like it won't even budge.
Guess we'll have
to break it open!
That's impossible! There's a
strong barrier on the front side!
- Let's use the stairs.
- That seems a better way.
All right, let's go!
Wait, Venus!
Whether or not this will
succeed depends on you!
Tuxedo Mask...!
Welcome...
But any closer and I'll
shatter this glass sculpture.
I don't care what
happens to me!
But don't lay a
finger on Tuxedo Mask!
All right... Senishenta!
Yes!
What?!
You...!
Well?
This is...! It's not.
This isn't a talisman!
What?!
Despite the brilliance it emits,
it still isn't a talisman?!
That can't be....!
How brilliant it is seems to
be only a barometer of purity...
...and has nothing to do with
whether or not it's a talisman.
Looks like this was
another wasted trip.
Are you all right?
You guys saved me...?
I'm glad...
Even if it wasn't a talisman...
...I'll have your life,
Usagi Tsukino--
Or, rather, Sailor Moon!
What...?!
That girl
isn't Sailor Moon!
You're...?!
Stalking after an
innocent girl's pure heart...
...and then mistaking
her for me on top of it!
Ten million insults
and a thousand needles!
Y-You're joking...
Ten million insults
and a thousand needles!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
You're...
...Sailor Moon?!
Minako...
But...
You're different, somehow...
What! Do you have something
against my perfect dis--
She's the real one!
We guarantee that she is!
Then, who is this girl-SHENTA?!
I have no clue!
Maybe she's a fan of
mine or something?
First of all,
such a clumsy crybaby...
...can't possibly
be a Sailor Soldier!
- Yeah!
- To be a Sailor Soldier...
T-Then, this is a fake?!
...you have to be smart,
attractive, and cool like me!
Venus, you seem awfully
sincere about all that.
What a farce.
If you'll excuse us...
I won't let you get
away like that!
I have to take care
of you thoroughly.
No need to stay too long.
- Let's go, Neptune.
- Right.
I won't let you escape.
Senishenta!
You take care of Sailor
Moon and her entourage!
Yes-SHENTA!
You give me no choice.
If you really want
to settle things...
...we will accept
your challenge!
How long can you keep
up with your wisecracks?
SAILOR KICK!
My arm, my arm!!
"If the merchandise breaks,
we'll replace it with a new one."
Whew! I'm glad
I'm under warranty...
How can you be
so violent-SHENTA?!
You're the violent one!
Special Attack --
LOVE ME MOON CHAIN!!
There's no such attack!
Usagi!
Don't just sit there.
Transform!
MOON COSMIC POWER, MAKE UP!
What?!
So you really were
Sailor Moon-SHENTA?!
That's right!
The one, the only,
the most famous!
Fashionable, attractive, and cool!
The pretty soldier
in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!!
Dammit!
MOON SPIRAL HEART ATTACK!
YOU LIAR!
LOVELY!
Tuxedo Mask!!
I'm so glad!!
Mamo-chan... I'm so glad...
Usako...
Mamo-chan!
Senishenta...!
So, you were defeated!
WORLD SHAKING!
Uranus!
Don't let your
guard down, Neptune.
She's quite powerful!
Hurry over here, Sailor Soldiers!
Up above!
That's right! Everyone, we have
to help those two up there!
Why?!
We should just
leave them be!
We can't! Besides,
they saved me before!!
They're not bad guys!
All right, that's it!
I guess we'll give it our best!
But before that, Venus...
Please, get rid
of that disguise.
Why? Why? Is something
wrong with it?
I borrowed the transformation
pen from Luna and everything!
Dammit!
Hold it right there!
I won't allow you to
blow up the tower...
...that sends happy
fun TV programs...
...to living rooms all
over the country!
In the name of the viewers,
we punish you!
So, you're finally here...
So, now what'll you do?
Run away like usual?
Why do you think I called
you all the way out here?
That shoe!
Listen up.
This is something I
researched on my own...
Growth fluid for Daimohn.
If I combine
these two...
...I get the same power...
...as Senishenta!!
Look out!
Seven glass figurines
of the Sailor Soldiers...
I'm sure our professor
will be happy about this.
Uranus! You're wounded!
This is nothing!!
Leave this fight
to us and run!
What...?!
Now, now... What's wrong?
Where's the fun if you
stand there and do nothing?!
Hurry! Run away!
Do as she says!
Since you couldn't
find the talisman...
...you have no reason
to stay here, right?
That's true...
Let's go, Neptune...
They're saying that they'll
sacrifice themselves for us.
We should take them
up on their offer.
I thought I said I won't
let you escape!
Now you have nowhere left
to run. Are you ready now?
We will never...
...give up!
BURNING MANDALA!
SUPREME THUNDER!
Impossible...!
She has a strong shield
around herself as well!
It's dangerous if we stay
in one place! Split up!
No! We shouldn't separate!!
Do you have a plan?!
The only way for us to
break through that shield...
...is to use the
Sailor Planet Attack!
Impossible! She'll get us
while we're powering up!!
You're finished!
Tuxedo Mask!!
Kaorinite!
I am your opponent!
Come on!
Mamo-chan....!!
MOON COSMIC POWER...!
MARS STAR POWER...!
MERCURY STAR POWER...!
JUPITER STAR POWER...!
VENUS STAR POWER...!
I've got you now!
NOW!
SAILOR PLANET...
...ATTACK!!
What?!
D-Did we get her...?!
It looks like you just
used up all of your powers.
This can't be...!
The people doing the stepping
might be fine with that...
...but what about the people
who are getting stepped on?!
If we all joined forces...
...we'd be able to find a way
to avoid sacrificing anyone!
DIE!
WORLD SHAKING!
What?!
This can't be...happening...!
PROFESSOR!!!
- We did it...
- Yeah...
Where's Uranus and Neptune?!
Those two... Why, in the very,
very end did they save us?
Really... What kind
of a whim was that?
Don't make so
much fun of me.
For some reason,
I thought Sailor Moon...
...looked like buns-head.
Usako... I'm sorry
that your gift is gone.
No, it's all right...
I'm sorry I put you in
danger because of me.
And I always get a lot of love
from you anyway, Mamo-chan!!
Man, talk about setting up a
mood in someone else's house!
I tried so hard, too!
Really, this
bunch of girls...
They really don't
mesh together.
Hey, are you listening?!
Come on, we aren't an inn!!
If you're going to be all
cuddly-snuggly, go home!
I'm hungry!
It's me.
I see. Kaorinite has been...
Then I want you to
take over her task.
You are my only hope, Yujial.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com