Silence is approaching.
Quietly, but surely...
Is this world really going to disappear!?
Hey, you over there who's cheering
"All right! There will be no more school!"
It's not time to be so easygoing like that!
I, Sailor Moon will punish you
in the name of the moon!
Y-You're the Messiah?!
Please! Save everyone!
- And so...
- Yeah.
This goes over here and does this.
Understand?
Nope.
The ominous dream
gets stronger and stronger...
But, what in the world
is that girl...!?
- Is Usagi here?
- Chibiusa.
This is unusual.
Hey! I told you not
to come here to play!
Come on, Usagi.
I'm sorry to bother you right in the middle
of your preparation for entrance exams.
But I have a favor to ask
of my dear sister Usagi...
"Dear sister Usagi"...!?
Actually, it's this.
The opening of a brand new planetarium?
Chibiusa, you want to
go to the planetarium?
Yeah! It'll be a learning experience, too.
I see... This week, it will be narrated
by that cute boy DJ, Thomas Harris...
In any case, it's close to here,
so I thought I could invite Hotaru...
I see.
I get it...
All right, let's all go tomorrow.
Thanks!
But why is Haruka's group
keeping an eye on Hotaru...?
The enemy is still collecting pure hearts.
Perhaps Hotaru has a special
pure heart or something...
I see, that's possible.
Hotaru is a kind girl, too...
That's impossible...
I can't wait for tomorrow!
And can I count on you for
the admission fees, too?
For the both of us?
So she says...
Usagi, the mother really has to
take care of things like that.
"Mother?"
A mother who takes
good care of her daughter...
I can't possibly do that!
- Mother...
- I haven't given birth to you yet!
It's so noble of you to
start her education now...
Well... I would like to take
care of a cute girl like her!
I'll give her away, yeah,
you can have her!
- Well, I'm no match against her real mom!
- You can have her if you want!
Lately, that dream where
the world falls to ruin...
It's getting stronger than ever before.
We must find the Messiah
as soon as possible...
If they awaken the user of the Grail
as the evil Messiah of Silence...
Hotaru Tomoe...
She possesses strange powers.
We must determine what
she really is quickly!
In any case, she's the only
daughter of Professor Tomoe...
...whom we've been targeting as
a suspected Death Busters member!
That girl who is standing in the
light of the grail in my dream...
I think I'm slowly starting to see her figure.
She is holding a long weapon
of some sort in her hands...
T-That means...
The scythe of silence...
The Silence Glaive.
A-Are you sure about that?
I'm not really sure, but...
It can't be!
Could the Messiah of Silence
be that soldier of ruin...
...the one guarded by
the planet of destruction...!?
If that's the case, we may not be
able to do anything at all anymore.
The world will shortly fall to ruins...
No...
Even if that soldier of ruin were
to be reincarnated into this era...
...we still have a chance if we
strike before she awakens.
This planet will not be destroyed!
I will never give up!
That's right. We shouldn't give up.
In order to protect this planet.
It's almost time...
Soon, I will awaken.
That time will be when what you wish for...
...silence... will cover this planet.
We were not mistaken to choose
you as the Messiah of Silence.
I am the only one who
can fulfill your wishes...
If you wish for me to awaken sooner...
...seek pure hearts that become
energy for my awakening.
Be of use to me!
Try to make me happier!
Yes!
Welcome to the Countdown50!
I'm Thomas Harris.
And now, I'll go over
the top ten hits of the week.
In tenth place is a song
that was #30 last week.
- Thomas... I'll be there to see you soon!
- The artist's album is increasing in sales, too.
- Wait for me!
- All right, let's start with this song.
Let's get it on!
Yes? Oh, Professor!
Yes, it's perfect!
Do you like the stars, Professor?
Oh, I'm glad!
Yes. This time, I'm sure to...
Leave it to me.
I see... You're the only hope, Mimet...
Stars, huh...?
The stars know all...
was something someone said before...
Wish upon a star... was something else...
Wait, Tomomi!
You know, let's work on
today's homework together!
Hotaru!
Chibiusa!
You were... waiting for me?
Yeah!
You know...
There's a new planetarium
that opened up nearby.
I thought about going with you.
That sounds fun...
Then, let's go right now!
Right now...?
I'm on my way back home from school...
I should ask Papa first
whether or not I can go.
If you do that, the show
will begin! Come on...
But...
Girls of this day and age
shouldn't say things like that!
Usagi!
Hotaru, if you can't do something on
your way back home from school...
...without asking your parents,
you won't grow up to be a good adult!
Hey, now...
Actually, straying on the way home isn't
a good thing, but we don't have time today...
If we aren't bothering you, let's go.
Bothering? Not at all...
Please? I'll apologize to your dad with you.
Chibiusa...
All right... Shall we go, then?
I'm so glad!
If that's the case, let's hurry!
And Andromeda, born from
arrogant and selfish parents...
...had both arms and
both legs chained together...
...and with her freedom gone she was
sacrificed to a monster in the sea.
The pain continued until
Perseus came to rescue her.
As you may well know...
...there are many more sad tales
concerning the girls in the stars.
So she is here.
The target is probably the narrator.
But even Usagi's group
is here with that girl.
This might work out even better for us...
This is our chance to see
what Hotaru Tomoe really is.
The giant scorpion let loose by the goddess
of the earth is a summer constellation.
- Orion shows himself only in...
- Thomas...
You're almost mine.
Setsuna?
Why are you here, Setsuna...?
Did an enemy appear?
Or are you still keeping an eye on Hotaru?
Please, tell us. What are you
guys planning to do, Setsuna?
I'm sure we can help you, too.
I believe that we can no longer
fight without telling you the truth.
Uranus, Neptune, and I have an objective...
...to prevent the arrival of
the approaching silence...
Our enemy is an intruder from another
dimension in outer space, the Death Busters.
Death Busters?
What is that "silence?"
It's the destruction of the world...
I'm sure that Sailor Mars,
you have already...
...seen it in the form
of a foretelling dream...?
Is that true?
- Rei!
I wasn't sure about it...
It's just that ever since those monsters
called Daimohns started to appear...
I've been seeing horrible
dreams over and over.
That's the silence we need to prevent...
...the image of Earth's destruction.
Earth's destruction?
Please place your hearts inside the
light from the orb at the tip of this rod.
You should be able to see the image
that Mars has been dreaming about.
T-This...
This can't be...
This is...
This is silence...?
If the enemy,
the Messiah of Silence, awakens...
...this will become reality.
The Messiah of Silence...?
She is the final soldier
that should not be awakened...
The guide to death who appears at the time of
destruction, and returns everything to nothing.
Messiah of Silence...
What in the world...
Soon, she will reveal to
us what she really is.
Uchoten!
In your place...
A wish upon a star!
Everyone! Get down!
A m-monster!
Well done, Uchoten.
It really is much!
Uchoten!
I'll get rid of the crowd,
so you get Thomas' pure heart...
Uchoten!
But, before that...
Thomas, can I have your autograph?
How scary...
Fine, then!
CHARM...
...BUSTER!
Hotaru, are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Hotaru!
I-It's all right.
It's one of those seizures.
I'll be fine in a moment.
We have to hurry to the hospital!
Wait here!
I'll transform, and...
Wait.
Uranus!
See how she fares for a bit longer.
But, Hotaru...
Hold it right there!
Stars that twinkle in the sky!
Sharing your feelings
with the bright stars!
A planetarium is a place full of dreams!
Someone who wrecks
such a place of dreams...
We, the Sailor Team...
...will punish you in
the name of the moon!
Well, no matter what you say...
...there's no way those girls
will just sit quietly and watch.
Yes.
Sheesh! Why do you
always get in my way!?
Uchoten!
Yes?
Save the pure heart for later.
First, get rid of those that get in our way!
Yes!
I'm trusting you to take care of the rest!
Y-Yes!
Then, everyone, with me...
A wish upon a star!
Uchoten!
Look up at the night sky!
Hang in there, Hotaru!
We can't move around like this.
We have to do something.
Due to popular demand...
A wish upon--
A rose?!
That's enough, Daimohn.
I have sealed away the
evil star that tortures people.
You can't wish anymore!
Thanks for the cheers...
Answering your requests...
A wish upon a star!
Everyone, get out of the way!
It looks like it got worse than before.
Duck, Venus!
Hotaru! Duck!
Just as we thought!
Hotaru!
What...!?
Can it be...?
Hotaru...
I-Impossible...
A Sailor Soldier...!?
Y-You are...!
W-What...!?
M-My body...
...doesn't move!
Now, Sailor Moon!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEARTACHE!
Love-Lovely!
WORLD...
...SHAKING!
DEEP...
...SUBMERGE!
DEAD SCREAM...
You can't!
STOP!
Chibiusa!!
Sailor Moon!
What are you doing!?
Get out of the way.
W-What!?
She is the one guarded by Saturn,
the planet of destruction...
...the solder of ruin, Sailor Saturn.
When Sailor Saturn awakens...
...the world is about to end.
Get out of the way!
You don't know the horror of silence!
Unless we kill that girl,
Saturn will awaken.
If Saturn awakens,
it means the end of this planet!!
You can't!
You can't just kill this girl!!
Even if Saturn is the soldier of ruin...
...nobody has the right to
kill Hotaru to seal her away!!
You're too cruel trying to kill Hotaru!
There must be some otherway!
I knew you guys would say that...
But...
There is no other way
to save this world.
No matter what happens,
we can't let Sailor Saturn awaken.
That is the destiny of the stars.
Hotaru!
Where did she...!?
Oh, no!
I was worried.
A bad girl, not to come straight home...
Yes, that is correct, Pharaoh Ninty.
Yes, that girl is Sailor Saturn,
guarded by the planet of destruction.
There can't be a better candidate
for the Messiah of Silence!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com