An evil trap by Eugeal!!
There were talismans inside Uranus
and Neptune's pure heart crystals!
Haruka, Michiru -- don't die!!
Just watch! Even if there aren't any
talismans, I WILL save the world!!
Uranus...
What should I do?
How can I return these
talismans to your bodies?
Buns-head...
No, Sailor Moon...
I don't care what happens to us...
Please, protect these talismans...
And find the one remaining talisman.
Haruka!
Hand the Grail to
the legendary Messiah...
The legendary Messiah...?
Who is that...?
Our savior, who can rescue us
from the time of destruction...
...the horrible world of silence...
When the Messiah gets a hold
of the Grail, the world...
...will be saved...
NOOOOOO!!
I can hear it.
It's faint, but I hear a pulse!
Dammit! How can we
return these talismans...
...these crystals of their
pure hearts... back inside them!?
Sure enough, I have
received the two talismans.
You can't do that!
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!
Those two talismans are the crystals
of Haruka and Michiru's pure hearts!
Give them back!!
FIRE...
...BUSTER!!
How is the power of Fire Buster II, with
its pending practicality model patent...
...now with even more
firepower than before?
SHINE AQUA...
...ILLUSION!
I can't believe Shine Aqua
Illusion didn't work!
An eye for an eye, a fame for a fame!
BURNING...
...MANDALA!
Mars, it's no good!
The fire grew even bigger!
Your attacks will not be able to
extinguish the fame of my Fire Buster.
Now you'll all burn to a crisp,
into crispy black charred masses!
See you!
If we don't think of something,
we'll all die!
LUNA-P...
...FIRE EXTINGUISHER!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
Tuxedo Mask!
I was wondering what
was gonna happen to us!
Whew, I'm glad we made it in time.
Thank you, Sailor Chibi Moon,
Tuxedo Mask.
Hurry, the talismans...
Right!
Wait for me, Uranus, Neptune!
I will make sure... I will make
sure to get the talismans back!
I... I was able to
obtain TWO talismans!!
Damn those pesky girls!
STICKY LIQUID!
What!?
M-My legs...
...are stuck.
Take this!
Now... there!
And... there!
See you later!
Watch out, Sailor Moon!
Eugeal is...!
W-What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do? What should I do?
Sorry, guys!
Sorry!
I'm really sorry! I'm sorry!
There! And there!
She's just like the
white rabbit of Inaba...
Does that make us sharks?
D-Did it hurt!?
I won't forgive you if you
let Eugeal get away now!
Do your best, Sailor Moon!
We'll make sure to follow you!
I have to save them!
I have to get the crystals of
Uranus and Neptune's pure hearts...
I have to get those talismans back!
So you're here!
I can't forgive you for
stepping on someone's heart...
...and then trying to do
away with their life as well!
For love and justice...
The pretty soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!!
Acting tough, are we?
I do hope you remember that I defended
myself against your ultimate attack before.
It's obvious that I'm much
more powerful than you are.
If you don't want to die, it would be
better for you to run away right now!
Even if my body breaks, I'll make sure
that those talismans are back in my hands!
MOON SPIRAL...
FIRE...
...HEART ATTACK!!
...BUSTER!!
Just like I told you...
Fire Buster II is a
wonderful piece of equipment.
I made it by making
alterations to Fire Buster I.
That weak little attack of
yours is nothing against it!
Sailor Moon, you have gotten
in my way so many times before...
Today, I will give my thanks
for all of those times!
FIRE...
Hold it right there!
Who are you!?
Miss Setsuna Meioh?
Eugeal, I will have you
return the talismans to us.
What!?
Sailor Moon!
Who are you?
PLUTO PLANET POWER...
MAKE UP!
You're...!
Sailor Pluto!
It has been a while.
Why are you here?
The remaining talisman...
...is in my possession!
This is perfect...
I don't have to go
searching for the third one.
I will not let you evil beings
get a hold of the talismans!!
Oh, wait!
Uranus!
Neptune!
The crystals of their pure hearts...?
They're going back...
I'm so glad...
The true talismans...
...didn't have to sacrifice anyone...
Talismans... have this
much divine power?
W-What just happened!?
Depending on who uses it...
...it is said that it can lead the
world to destruction or salvation...
...it is the Holy Grail
that has infinite power.
The Grail...
I'll take that!
I won't let you have it!
You're in my way!!
Sailor Moon is...!!
Sailor Moon!
Is this a new awakening!?
Oh? My, my, my...
FIRE BUSTER!!
Sailor Moon is...
...the Messiah that will save
the world from silence!?
Dammit... Sailor Moon, I will make
sure to pay you back for this!!
Chief Eugeal, your jobis over.
Mimet?
I've been tolerating all
of your failures until now.
But they really were
unbearable to watch.
W-What!?
You're tarnishing the name of the
Witches 5, the pride of the Death Busters!
Please die and repent for that!
Die? Impossible!
The battle has just begun!
T-The brakes aren't working!?
What!?
Snail Woman in the Station Wagon
Should Crash and Die!!
Mimet!!
Thanks for the hard work!
Sailor Moon!
Mamo-chan...
Are you all right!?
Hold yourself together!
I'm feeling really lethargic...
I'm feeling weak all over.
Perhaps Sailor Moon
isn't the Messiah...
The true Messiah can
use infinite power.
If she collapses from fatigue with
just this much, Sailor Moon isn't...
Then, the true Messiah
is somewhere else...
It looks like we have
a new mission now.
Professor, the Grail has appeared!
Furthermore, the Grail has landed
in the hands of the Sailor Soldiers!
What's the matter?
Mimet...
It's true that the
Holy Grail has appeared.
However, it seems that someone who can
truly control the Grail has yet to appear.
If someone who could control
the Grail was really among them...
...this building of
the Death Busters...
...as well as all the Daimohn eggs,
should have crumbled into ruins.
However, look around you.
Not one crack has emerged.
Perhaps...
...there is someone who can control
the Grail for us, the Death Busters...
...somewhere amazingly close.
I see!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com