Haruka is attractive,
after all...
Mako-chan, you shouldn't!
Haruka is a girl!
What is that dangerous
look in your eyes!?
While we're saying things like that,
the enemy attacks Mako-chan!
F-For now... I, Sailor Moon...
...will punish you in
the name of the moon!
Oh, boy,
I'm so hungry...
And there's another
study group session tonight.
It's all about your guts!
I'll bring roast beef sandwiches
to tonight's study group, too.
Really!? I'm so lucky!
Everyone should have friends
who are talented at cooking!
Mako-chan, I love you!
My cooking isn't about talent.
I just think that
big, boyish girls...
...need to be good at
something like cooking.
So I find myself trying hard.
Even if you couldn't cook,
you're feminine enough, Mako-chan.
Thanks...
- I mean it.
- Really?
Yeah. When I first
met you, Mako-chan...
...I was thinking what
a cute person you were!
You're praising me too much!
But that makes me happy...
...so I'll give you an
extra-large portion, Usagi.
I did it!
Usagi!
Sorry!
Are you all right?
Are you injured!?
Does it hurt anywhere!?
Ow...
Haruka...
Did you hit your head..?
Oh, no, I'm all right.
What about you, Mako-chan?
You, over there.
You're bleeding a bit.
Huh? You're right.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm fine if
it's only this much.
I was just thinking a
little about something...
...so I wasn't paying attention
to what was in front of me.
I have no excuse for this.
No, it's all right...
You're brave, and you look
out for your friends.
I'm sorry to have
surprised you.
No, no...
See ya!
Bye!
Mako-chan, thanks
for covering for... me...
Mako-chan?
You shouldn't!
Even if she's really attractive,
Haruka is a female!
Sheesh...!
W-What are you saying?
Of course!
It's nothing like that!
You're right,
what AM I saying?
We have to find the
messiah at any cost.
The three talismans that are
the key to finding the messiah...
...are sealed
inside pure hearts.
I will make sure they
fall into our hands.
Even if we sacrifice the
owner of that pure heart?
owner of that pure heart.
For world peace?
For world peace.
We have little time left.
Silence is soon
approaching us...
You're right. We have
to find the messiah.
At any cost.
The sea is in an uproar.
Yeah, it's around here.
I feel a presence,
but it's not moving yet.
Hey, does anyone know
where Haruka's house is?
No, I haven't asked.
Haruka?
You mean THAT Haruka?
What are you going to
do with her address?
W-Well, I have to
return this to her!
The target has
been confirmed.
W-Wait!
If I don't have that, I don't
have an excuse to see Haruka!
Excuse...?
Wait!
Where did it fall...?
It's not here...
It's there!
Just a bit more!
Got it!
SCAR...
W-W-W-What is that!?
I will take your
pure heart, SCAR!
- That's...!
- A Daimohn!
- Mako-cha--
- Let's transform!
Oh, sure thing.
MOON COSMIC POWER, MAKE UP!
MERCURY STAR POWER, MAKE UP!
SCAR...
SHINE AQUA ILLUSION!
SCAR!
What are you doing
so early in the morning!?
Get away from that girl!
I'm already interrupted.
For now, retreat, Scar!
SCAR!
It's flying!?
W-What in the
world is that?
That girl is the
target this time.
I couldn't tell if she was
the owner of a talisman.
Sailor Moon sure did
something unnecessary.
Why don't we tell them
everything and fight together?
Silence is approaching.
To stop it, we must
sacrifice someone.
Can they do that?
So, what are
we going to do?
They'll be after
her again.
We have to keep an eye
on her for a while.
Mako-chan! Let's go home!
Oh? Ms. Kino went home already.
That's funny...
Where did it go?
Mako-chan!
What are you doing here
all by yourself?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Actually, I haven't
found Haruka's scarf...
...since I lost it
here this morning.
Y-You know, Mako-chan, I told
you this yesterday, too...
I-I've been saying
it's nothing like that.
Are you sure?
I'm sure!
Hi. I'm glad I bumped
into you again today.
Haruka...
I have something to ask you.
Do you mind joining me?
Do you mean me?
S-Sure!
Mako-chan, don't you think
there's a slight problem here?
What, girls can't go
on a drive together?
I wasn't saying that...
Then it's all right.
I'll borrow your
friend for a bit.
You'll come with me, right?
S-Sure!
M-Mako-chan?
I don't care about
this anymore...
That's Michiru.
She's in the same grade as I.
I believe we've
met once before.
Nice to meet you.
I-I see... Same grade?
How old are you two?
We're in tenth grade.
Tenth grade? Then is it all
right for you to drive a car?
Is it all right?
Let's see... I-I got
a license overseas.
So she says.
Those are pretty ear rings.
They look good on you.
Do you think so...?
Was it bad for us to
force you like this?
No, not at all!
So, what did you want to ask me?
I want to be better
friends with you...
A DATE!?
Y-Yeah...
But it's with a woman.
A woman?
This is a problem...
Did Mako-chan's
preferences change?
It's not that!
And it was Haruka
she went off with!
I can't laugh that one off.
No matter how
attractive she is...
...I can't believe that
she's chasing after women.
It's not that!
But, Rei, you have THIS, too!
Don't pull out other people's
books without their permission!
That's not the problem!
W-We shouldn't leave
Mako-chan alone.
The enemy is after Mako-chan's
pure heart this time!
Y-Yeah...
I'm pretty close...
I'm at Kaiouzu Park.
We'll be right there.
I'm all right. If an enemy
comes, I'll defeat it.
Please, let me do what
I want for today.
- Mako-chan! Mako-chan!
- Don't give up!
That's right! There are plenty of
good-looking guys in the world!
Sheesh, no wisn't
the time for--
But this is a
big problem, too!
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
problem for Mako-chan!
It's all right. It's really
nothing like that.
I don't know how
to say this...
You know how Haruka
is attractive, right?
I just look up to someone
that attractive...
SCAR!
- Mako-chan!
Your pure heart that looks
up to your ideal woman!
This time, I will...
Haruka!
You monster!
Let go of Mako-chan!
You can't!
Run, both of you! Hurry!
It's dangerous
to throw rocks!
Haruka! Michiru!
The interruptions
have disappeared.
Scar, take the pure
heart from that girl!
SCAR!
Right according to plan.
Yeah... I feel sorry for her,
but we have to do this.
SCAR!
You're...!
Sorry... We need the
talisman at any cost.
Damn you!
Scar! Get rid of them!
SCAR!
I won't let you have
the pure heart!
So, that's why they've
been hiding until now?
They didn't feel
anything at all...
...as they watched Haruka
and Michiru get beaten up!?
That's the end!
SCAR?
The villain that snatches
away a pure maiden's heart!
As a pretty soldier,
I can't forgive you!
In the name ofthe moon,
I punish you!
VENUS LOVE ME CHAIN!
BURNING MANDALA!
SCAR!
This isn't a talisman, either.
Wait!
Please, return
this girl's heart!
Hurry and return it to her.
Hurry, Sailor Moon!
They seem to be
having a tough fight.
They're pathetic.
DEEP SUBMERGE!
SCAR!
Are you all right?
Yeah. Thanks.
- Rest for today.
- No, I can't do that...
JUPITER STAR POWER, MAKE UP!
SCAR!
SPARKLING WIDE PRESSURE!
Jupiter!
Now, Sailor Moon!
MOON SPIRAL HEART ATTACK!
SCAR!
LOVELY!
Wait! I don't know
what you mean by this...
...but you always appear like thieves
and try to steal the pure hearts!
You guys are just
like the Daimohn!
What if that's the case?
I can't forgive you,
especially today.
I'll straighten out that
demented mentality of yours!
Jupiter!
You're being immature.
You should hold back a little.
Uranus?
She's powerful.
This is...
Why is it here?
Haruka and
Michiru are here!
Haruka! Haruka!
Haruka! I'm so glad...
Oh... M-Mako-chan.
What about that monster?
She says the Sailor Soldiers
came and defeated it.
- I see...
- Haruka! I'm so glad!
I'm sorry...
It's because you
were with me...
Haruka, you
injured your hand!
Oh, you're right...
Huh? This is...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I intended to return
this scarf to you.
Haruka is
wonderful after all...
I hope I can be a wonderful
woman like her someday.
Hey, hey, what do you think
of Mako-chan's attitude?
That looks rather serious.
I don't know...
Maybe it's like usual, and she
just resembled that other guy.
But isn't it a little bad?
Yeah, it's bad, it's bad.
Mako-chan?
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com