Do you know how tough it is to jump higher
and more beautifully than anyone else!?
Athletes have their own
set of problems, too!
I can't forgive you for going after
such a sportsman's pure heart!
You're just jealous
because they are so cool!
In the name of the moon,
I'll punish you!
This is the story of a distant past...
Yes. They traveled a path different from the
Sailor Soldier protecting the moon kingdom...
...and had fought against intruders who
came from outside the solar system.
They were:
Guarded by Uranus...
The soldier of the heavens, Sailor Uranus.
Guarded by Neptune...
The soldier of the deep seas, Sailor Neptune.
And guarded by Pluto...
The soldier of the afterlife, Sailor Pluto.
We were given a stronger power that
the other Sailor Soldiers don't have...
It's a power to protect this Earth
from enemies in outer space.
However...
When we were born in this day and age,
and had awakened to our past...
...the enemy had already nested
herself secretly on this planet...
To fight against this intrusion on Earth...
The greatest crisis of this solar system...
I will join the battle from the
boundaries of time and space...
Sailor Soldiers given
stronger powers than us, huh...
Those three... I had thought that they
were somewhat different from us...
And that's why those three
always act separately from us...
They... protected our world in the
distant past, on a star of solitude...
It makes me cry!
And they are back, wanting to fight alone
once again, working separately from us.
Here, Artemis.
Thanks...
You're welcome.
Don't...
Don't think about
fighting along with them...
The world you wish for
and what they wish for...
...is completely different.
Wishing for a different world...
Right hand, Blue 4.
Pretty good...
But, I have Hayase on my side...
Hayase! I'll do my best!
Right foot, Red 3.
Go for it, Mimet!
Hayase is cheering for you, too!
The new world record is right there!
Go for it, Mimet!
And this will make you and
Hayase the perfect couple!
Go for it, Mimet!
The Death Busters are cheering you on, too!
With this, you're assured
of the executive spot!
Go for it, Mimet!
GO FOR IT!!
Mimet!
I'm impressed that you are training, Mimet...
Professor!?
What's the matter?
You coming into a place like this...!
Oh, it's nothing. I had heard that
the next target was an athlete.
Since I had already chosen a Daimohn
most suited for the purpose...
I thought about bringing it to you for once...
Why, thank you!!
I'm counting on you, Mimet...
Leave it to me!
I, Mimet, will be going now!
Now...
Left foot, Blue 4.
I guess I will try for the world record as well...
Now, Hayase will finally jump!
Let's all focus our attention on this young
jumper who appeared out of nowhere!
Hayaseis on the run!
He jumps! A new Japanese record!!
Hayaseis said to have
been very frail when he...
...was a child, and often
went in an dout of the hospital!
And now, he is the proud owner
of a new Japanese record!
Congratulations, Hayase!
Shun...
I didn't know you had such hobbies!
Get out!
I told you to knock at all times
before entering my room!
Oh, my, how strong you've gotten lately!
"To Mr. Shun Hayase..."
Is it a love letter?
Stop it!
Kaori, you've been acting strange lately!
Perhaps it's YOU who
is acting strange, Hotaru...
To write a letter that you
don't have the courage to send...
I'm home...
Oh, man... I'm pretty beat today, too...
We have a guest...
I'm so thrilled that you
would come visit me, Hotaru!
I'm so sorry I came so suddenly.
Oh, of course it's all right!
Stay as long as you want today!
Okay. Thanks.
So... it was Hotaru!
I'm visiting today.
Chibiusa!
You haven't even served tea to our guest!?
Oh, don't mind me...
I can't help it! Mama-Ikuko
isn't here right now!
If you know how, you do it, Usagi!
I'm still just a kid!
Is that the attitude to have when you're
asking someone to do something for you!?
It would be good if you could
at least make some tea!
I mean, you're drawing a blank
when it comes to studying!
That's something you shouldn't have said!
You don't have to pinch me for it!
You don't have to bite me, either!
I'm jealous...
You know, this house...
It really has a gentle feeling...
R-Really?
Hotaru, you wrote a fan letter
to Hayase, the track athlete?
What did you write?
I didn't write anything much...
You know...
I'm not all that strong, right?
So...
It's reassuring to watch Hayase compete,
because he was also frail when he was young.
I hope you get a reply!
Yeah!
But... it doesn't matter now...
This letter... I decided that I won't send it...
Why?
Because I don't know where to send it to...
And besides...
Then... Let's give it to him in person!
That's right!
Then she can talk directly to him, too!
Yeah!
Let's do that, Hotaru!
Wait for me, Hayase...
Right now...
...I will come steal your pure heart!
Fortunately, today is just a practice,
so this place is just for you and me!
What is this thing!?
Anything that gets between
me and Hayase gets THIS!
There was a pest to come
between me and Hayasein there...!
Come on! Both of you,
you're taking too long!
Sheesh... This is embarrassing...
She's talking so loud...
In the end, it's just that
SHE wants to meet Hayase...
This...
...is where Shun is...
That must be Hayase...
There's a rumor that he will break the
Japanese record yet again at the next meet...
An athlete of that caliber might be
sought after by the Death Busters...
Plu!
You're here, too, Plu?
Hello, little one.
Haruka! Michiru!
What's going on?
To come here all alone...
I'm not alone.
Buns-head!?
Hotaru Tomoe!
Hurry, Hotaru!
What are those girls...?!
Hey, what's this!?
You don't have to corner
cute girls with so many people!!
All we want to do is to
give Hayase a letter!
You're so mean!
It's all right...
I... I'm fine just watching
and cheering for him on TV...
That's...
Is something wrong?
Hotaru, your letter! Your letter!
Go!
Hotaru!
Go, go, Hotaru!
Did you want something?
Come on, Hotaru!
What's wrong? Hotaru?
I... Like I thought...
What's this? What's this!?
I was following the rules, and was
Just watching Hayase from far away...
Appear, Daimohn!!
What!?
A Daimohn!
Undohkai!
There you are, you little pests!
Get them!
Undohkai!
ROLL THE BALL!
Look out, Hotaru!
The letter...
Undohkai!
Serves them right!
Undohkai! Rush in and take
Hayase's heart crystal!
Hotaru! Stay here, and sit still!
The letter...
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!
ROLL THE HUMAN!
Finally, Hayase's lips...
I mean, heart crystal will be stolen.
Forgive me... this is myw-o-r-k...
I'm scared! This is scary!
This is too scary!
Stop that!
Trying to steal someone's
dream to jump higher and...
...more beautifully than anyone
else lacks sportsmanship!
For love and justice!
The pretty soldier in a sailor suit!
Sailor Moon!
In the name of the moon, I'll punish you!
And her apprentice!
In the name of the future moon,
I'll punish you!
You don't have to!
You're not that dependable
when you're by yourself, Usagi!
Undohkai! Do something about it!
Undohkai!
THREE-LEGGED RACE!
All right... while that's going on...!
Undohkai!
You can't!
Don't get in my way!
You're the one in the way!
Just give up!
All right! Time to retreat!
Undohkai!
Oh, shoot!
Huh? Something wrong?
If you're not feeling well,
it's better to go to the medical office...
W-What's going on?
Did you see that... That power...?
That girl... she's not normal.
That girl is indeed a dangerous entity...
HEY! What are you doing!?
I'm sorry...
But I'm not sure what happened myself.
That girl... What in the world is she?
In any case... I was saved because
I had this shell on my back...
PINK SUGAR...
...HEART ATTACK!
That hurts!
A chance!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEART ACHE!
Shoot!!
Love-Lovely!!
I'll get you for this!!
Mr. Hayase!
Hotaru came to!
Chibiusa...
You shouldn't do anything
too strenuous yet...
Mr. Hayase...
Um... I...
You're... a frail girl, aren't you?
Yes...
I was like that, too,
when I was a child...
I know.
Really?
Even at this age,
when I wake up in the morning...
I sometimes get the feeling
that my current self...
...that's full of energy and
playing sports is all a dream.
Mr. Hayase...
I know that feeling!
Really?
You're the first person who
seriously listened to me! Thank you...
Please do your best at
the next track meet!
You, too...
...should do your best, so that you can
someday be strong enough to play sports!
Okay!
And he jumps!
Hayase cleared it!
He has yet again marked
a new Japanese record!
Congratulations, Hayase!!
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com