The time for the final
showdown has arrived.
We have to end it here!
We're the only ones who can
stop the approaching silence!
That's right...
I won't hand them over!
I will protect them!
Chibiusa, Hotaru, AND the world!
All preparations are complete.
Now if you, the Messiah of Silence,
sets the Grail onto this device...
...the light of shadow will
shine upon the Tau Nebula.
To guide our great master...
...the energy life form from
another dimension, Pharaoh 90.
We need that light.
When Pharaoh 90
appears in this universe...
...everything will be destroyed and
the Earth will be surrounded in silence.
The age of light filled with lies will end...
...and the age of shadows where true
darkness reigns supreme will begin!
We have to end it here.
Yes...
To save Chibiusa, too.
And we won't let Hotaru die, either!
We are Sailor Soldiers
of love and justice!
Guys!
Wait for us, Chibiusa, Hotaru...
MERCURY STAR POWER...
MARS STAR POWER...
JUPITER STAR POWER...
VENUS STAR POWER...
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!!
We have no time left...
We have to strike before
she completely awakens.
So there was no Messiah after all.
We have to save the
world with our own hands.
No matter what sacrifice
we have to make...
I won't let anybody be sacrificed!
The Grail is approaching...
The Grail is!?
They are foolishly bringing it to us...
That's good for us.
But I still cannot allow...
obstructions to... enter.
Not until I am fully awakened...
Mars...?
What's wrong?
Just now...
I felt a presence so
silent that it was eerie...
What?
A dark energy of immense levels!
To get through that barrier,
we have to use the Sailor Teleport.
All right, then let's do it.
They're coming!
SPARKLING...
...WI DE PRESSURE!
CRESCENT...
...BEAM!
BURNING...
...MANDALA!
Just how many are there!?
This is endless!
At this rate, we can't
use the Sailor Teleport!
Give us a break! Sheesh!
MOON SPIRAL...
...HEART...
...ATTACK!
LOVELY!!
It's no good...
What in the world can we do...?
Amazing!
Mugen Academy is now an
omega-zone protected by dark energy...
Now, no one will be able to
step inside this sacred ground.
Now...
The Grail...
FIRE SOUL!
BUBBLE SPRAY!
Oh, no!
MOON SPIRAL...
...HEART...
...ATTACK!
Now's the time to teleport!
Sailor Moon!
Stop it!
Hang on!
She's gone...
Sailor Moon...
Can this be really happening...?
If Sailor Moon has been captured,
we can't use the Sailor Teleport...
Then, what should we do...?
What is that...?
It looks like it's no ordinary barrier.
Can we enter through that hole?
Dammit!
This is...?
Pluto...
What did you do...?
I have stopped time.
Now, please go now.
You had hidden this
much power even from us...?
No...
This is the greatest taboo that I
cannot break as the guardian of time...
The greatest taboo...?
What will happen to you?
If you are able to
meet the real Messiah...
If we are...?
Pluto...!
To enter by stopping time...
Nothing less from the soldiers of
the outer rim of the solar system...
But more than that, your power is
sincerely grand, oh Messiah of Silence.
This is all thanks to taking in the pure
heart of that sacrifice named Chibiusa.
Don't use that pure heart...
...for bad things...
Is something the matter?
Nothing is wrong!!
I will get a hold of the Grail now...
I want you to get rid of the Sailor
Soldiers that have gotten in here.
Me?
Use the dolls that you created...
Go, Daimohn Germatoid.
Yes...
That wall is continuing
its increase in energy.
To think we can't go in...
Sailor Moon...
All the four of us can do...
...is merely prevent that
wall from getting any bigger.
We need to believe
in Sailor Moon... and...
...and do what ever we can do!
Yeah!
Sailor Moon...
Where is everyone...?
Hotaru...!
What's this...!?
This is...
These are... bodies that I have created...
Both of you... it's against
school rules to come in here.
Go forth for your own justice...
these are your words, chairman.
It's a shame.
I wanted superior students like you
to become bodies for Daimohns...
Just like this man, Soichi Tomoe...
So he was possessed by a Daimohn!!
WORLD...
...SHAKING!
It's no use.
I've already analyzed all your attacks.
You can't win against me.
DEEP...
...SUBMERGE!
TALISMAN!
W-What!?
W-What's going on!?
Uranus!
I thought I heard Pluto's voice...
Yeah...
The Death Busters are
tougher than we thought...
But we won't lose...
Hotaru...
T-The Grail...
Grail? What about the Grail?
I overheard...
...that if Super Sailor Moon let
the Grail shine in this room...
...all enemies would be obliterated...
If you don't hurry,
the enemy will be here...
I'm glad you're all right, Hotaru...
Y-Yes...
Now, please hurry, Usagi.
Hurry and use the Grail
for Chibiusa's sake as well...
Hotaru...
How do you know
that I'm Usagi Tsukino?
You're... not Hotaru.
I'm Hotaru...
But, just in body.
What happened to Hotaru!?
I took her inside my body.
I am a life form
from another dimension.
I came here from the Tau Nebula
and took over Hotaru Tomoe's body.
I am Mistress Nine.
We've finally found you!!
For the future of this planet,
we will defeat you!
Wait! Uranus! Neptune!!
Master Pharaoh 90...
Please wait just a while longer.
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com