The Messiah of Silence finally awakens!
Is defeating Hotaru the only way
to save humans from annihilation!?
No! I won't let that happen!
There has to be some way for everyone
to be happy without anyone getting hurt!!
Come, students.
To Mugen Academy.
Into our hands.
The winds are crying.
This planet is cowering at
the horrors of the unknown as well...
Chibiusa...
Hotaru...
Where did you go...?
Chibiusa...
Chibiusa.
You know, about Hotaru...
I'm sure she's all right--
Usagi!!
Usagi...
Oh, sorry.
I'll get you back!
How dare you!?
Fine!
I give up! I give up!
I won!
Here, take your towel.
Good night!
Don't catch a cold!
Yeah!
Hey, Usagi!
You know...
I'm worried about Hotaru,
but I'll cheer up.
Chibiusa...
Thanks!
Good night!
Good night...
Usagi.
The students of Mugen Academy
are gathering on campus.
It looks like something
is going to happen.
Chibiusa, I'm going to
go without telling you.
I'll make sure to bring Hotaru
back safe and sound.
Chibiusa...
This isn't good...
Hotaru's body is starting to weaken rapidly.
We urgently need pure hearts.
I have already finished the preparations.
I, Cyprin, the last and
greatest witch of the Witches 5...
...will do my best for you, Professor.
I'm counting on you, Cyprin.
Now, the only one I can rely on is you.
Leave it to me.
I am quite different from Kaorinite...
Do your best.
Professor... you're saying
the same thing to Cyprin...
Dammit, Cyprin...
F-Fine! I will get a hold of
the best pure heart there is!
Just you watch, Cyprin...
The best pure heart there is...
The target is that girl who Hotaru
has opened up to the most.
The heart of that girl named Chibiusa.
Chibiusa, help me!
Hotaru!
Hotaru!!
Hotaru...
The superior students of Mugen Academy...
Now is the time...
...to sacrifice your pure hearts
to us, the Death Busters.
The time has come.
Sacrifice your pure hearts...
...to the grand Death Busters.
That's right... your pure hearts.
Young ladies, outsiders are not
allowed to come onto school grounds!!
Then everyone,
please submit your pure hearts.
I have to get rid of those pests.
Upstairs...?
Yes...
This is...!?
Welcome, Sailor Soldiers.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Cyprin, the last and
greatest witch of the Witches 5.
I guess there's no need
to hide our identities.
Everyone, time to transform!
VENUS STAR POWER...
MERCURY STAR POWER...
MARS STAR POWER...
JUPITER STAR POWER...
MOON COSMIC POWER...
MAKE UP!
I will save this planet
with love and beauty!
I won't allow evil silence!
Take a cold shower and repent!
Those who tarnish pure hearts...
In the name of Mars,
I will chastise you!
I won't let you have
whatever you want!
I'll shock you so
much you'll regret it!
We, the sailor team,
will punish you in the name of the moon!
Soon, this planet will be
surrounded by silence.
We, the Death Busters, are victorious.
BURNING...
...MANDALA!
Did I get her?
Sailor Mars!
VENUS LOVE ME CHAIN!
I won't let you escape now!
You think you captured me with this?
What'd you--!
I'm Cyprin.
And I'm Petirol.
Two together to make one.
The one, and the same.
It doesn't matter if it's one or two!
Take this!
SPARKLING WIDE PRESSURE!
Petirol!
Cyprin!
Such a thing...
...has no effect...
...on us!!
Jupiter!
Oh, you just run around?
Sailor Soldiers really
aren't much, are they?
Hotaru...
Just you wait,
I'll make sure to save you.
MOON PRISM POWER...
MAKE UP!
I see... that brat is also a Sailor Soldier...
An unexpected harvest.
I'm not scared, I'm not scared...
Please wait for me, Hotaru...
Hotaru?
Hotaru wants to see you, too.
Hotaru wants to see you
and have your pure heart.
Tuxedo Mask!
The feelings of a girl for her friend.
A pathetic soldier with a heart
so frozen to not feel that warmth.
Take that!
Sailor Chibi Moon!
DEAD SCREAM...
Chibi Moon!
Oh, no!
It's mine... the best pure heart there is...
Sailor Chibi Moon...
SHINE AQUA...
...ILLUSION!
T-They're strong...
W-We have to do something...
Their teamwork is just too good.
If there is a way to separate those two...
Playtime is now over...
We'll be attacking for real now.
If you get hit with
the next one, you'll die!
We have to take a risk now!
All right!
Here we go!
Let's show them...
...our teamwork!
BUBBLE...
...SPRAY!
Blocking our vision?
How useless!
VENUS LOVE ME CHAIN!
Petirol!
Cyprin!
MOON TIARA ACTION!
FIRE SOUL!
Your attacks do nothing against us!
We just absorb all that power,
and it just increases OUR power!
There!
Cyprin!
D-Damn you!!
Cyprin! Don't chase after them!
There!
Dammit!
I'm not letting you get away!
I won't let you escape!
Fool!
What!?
Cyprin!
Petirol!
We did it!
That was a tough opponent!
It's back to normal!
Look!
What in the world is this corridor!?
I sense a distortion
in space from this corridor.
It's connected to another dimension.
The headquarters
of the Death Busters!?
Let's go!
Welcome, young Sailor Soldiers.
So you finally showed up.
You are very lucky.
You get to participate in the
ceremony that is about to begin...
Sailor Chibi Moon!
Uranus!
Dammit!
He's got a strong barrier set up...
Uranus!
Neptune!
It seems as though
you all made it on time.
You are...?
Sailor Chibi Moon!!
Kaorinite.
Yes.
Soon, the Messiah of Silence will awaken.
Using the pure heart of this girl
named Chibiusa as her energy.
The pure heart...
Chibiusa!!
Stop it!
Sailor Moon!
The Messiah of Silence!!
No! Stop it!
Chibi Moon!
H-Hotaru... I'm glad you're okay...
This... is horrible!
This is too horrible!!
Beautiful.
A pure heart fit for
the Messiah of Silence.
This is no good!
If Sailor Saturn revives,
this world will be destroyed!
Hotaru! Stop!!
Please! Stop her!
If you're Hotaru's dad...
...if you love Hotaru...
Please!
Love?
What do you mean?
Could it be...?
That's not Sailor Saturn!
What did you say!?
I am the Messiah of Silence...
Mistress Nine.
W-What's going on!?
She's not Sailor Saturn...!?
It's the Death Busters!
Hotaru was already possessed by
a powerful enemy, and it has awakened!
It is our victory, Professor!
Sorry to have troubled you, Kaorinite.
That thought is the greatest
reward for me, Professor!
I--!
Kaorinite's job is now over.
We will now start preparing
for the next step.
Yes!!
Chibiusa!!
Hurry!
This dimension will disappear soon!!
W-What in the world is this!?
Usagi's group is still inside...
Sailor Moon...!
Chibiusa!?
Mamo-chan!
Chibiusa...
Chibiusa isn't breathing!!
What?!
Small Lady!?
There were students inside the building!
Don't worry, we evacuated them already.
Hurry!
We linked Mamoru and Chibiusa's bodies.
We'll keep Chibiusa alive
using Mamoru's life force.
This is the best that
we can do for now.
What have we been
fighting for all along?
Getting Chibiusa into a mess like this...
Setsuna!
I will head towards Mugen
Academy with Uranus' group.
To defeat the Messiah of Silence.
Are you still saying that!?
The Messiah of Silence is Hotaru!!
There is no other way
to save Small Lady.
No way... I don't want any
more people to be unhappy.
Hotaru, Chibiusa... everyone else.
I don't want to see anyone else's tears!!
Usako...
We have to do whatever we can do.
We need to fight.
Fight for the things that we believe in...
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com