What is your dream?
No matter how far away it is...
...if you have a heart to keep wishing for it...
...your dreams are bound to come true.
So stop doing evil deeds
and be a true good girl.
If you can, Mimet,
you'll be the star tomorrow!
Pure hearts...
Hurry up and collect the pure
hearts that will complete me...
Our messiah of silence.
Now, my excellent minions
are planning as such.
Please, bear with us for just a while longer...
I suddenly look back...
...thinking someone called my name.
A pale fower of doubt suddenly bloomed.
Now, the next song...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
That's right, it's Jinta Araki's
new song, "Blue Crisis Love"!
Araki...
He's so wonderful!
Amazing.
Just like ants crawling over sugar.
I wonder if those chasers
have nothing better to do...
Chasers?
The people who chase after
musicians and other celebrities.
What do they do, chasing after celebrities?
They don't do much about it...
Yeah. I don't know how these people think.
Right, Minako?
Minako?
W-What?
What's wrong? You look dazed.
O-Oh, nothing, really...
Even for us, chasing after
celebrities really isn't something...
O-Of course not!
Hey, Mina? Jinta Araki is...
We're going to be in high school
next year! We can't be chasing...
Yeah, we got entrance exams
coming up, too...
Usagi.
- Do you really realize what that means!?
- ...and you have an announcement?
Yes. We would like to select the heroine
for the movie coming out next July...
...that I'll be the lead in... from one of you.
A public audition.
The first cuts will be from 4:30p.m.
tomorrow at the Town Hallin Minato ward.
Since there'll be a swim suit competitionas
well, don't forget to bring your best swimsuit!
Let's have a hot summer with me next year!
My heroine--
A-About this problem...
Oh, this is...
Mimet.
Our messiah of silence is waiting.
I hope you have the next plan already in gear.
Of course! Look at this, Professor...
Excuse me. Look at this.
He's the next target.
Oh?
Jinta Araki, also known as Alazin!
An 18-year-old with a wonderful smile.
His newly released song
"Blue Crisis Love" is on the rise!
At the rate he's going, it's a matter
of time before he gets to the top...
A singer?
Mimet... It seems like all
your targets are celebrities...
If you confuse our
objective with your hobbies...
...you won't go far here in Death Busters.
Y-You're kidding...!
T-That's not it.
Hobbies, that really isn't...
I choose celebrities only because
the hearts of people with...
...higher charisma are more effective
in awakening the true messiah.
Calling that my hobby...
I think I'm going to cry!
No, Mimet, you don't have to cry...
I am just worried about you, because
you have potential for a bright future.
P-Professor...
Keep doing a solid job from now on, all right?
Sure!
The next high executive is you, Mimet!
I'll do my best!
Do a solid job.
"I love you, Araki!"
"I love Araki with a golden tan!"
And you substitute this X over here...
Usagi, you're amazing!
How do you understand this?
Not at all!
Hey... Where's Mina?
She said she had a fever from her cold,
so she'd stay at home and rest.
That probably means that Mina...
I'm here...
After all, I want to see just
one glimpse of the real Araki...
I didn't start being his fan just recently!
Um...
Yes?
A-Araki... When is Mr. Araki arriving?
He won't be coming to today's audition.
He'll be appearing as a guest
during tomorrow's second round.
That can't be!
I thought I could get one glimpse of him...
You're...!
This...
The original T-shirt that Alazin
released right when he debuted...
Not bad.
We both put in some years, haven't we?
I'm Minako Aino. Nice to meet you.
I'm Mime- no, Mimi. Mimi Hanyu.
Humans just have to put
everything into things they love!
Yeah!
Next, please...
Yes! Minako Aino!
I'm in 9th grade, and
my charm is my energy!
My special move is a flying, spinning dig!
There might be a kissing scene in
the scenario. What would you do?
Well, I will keep the whole movie
deal a secret from both my parents!
If you were to be accepted,
and were invited to dinner with the director...
What would you do?
Oh, I'll be fine!
I don't dislike any foods!
I can eat anything that is served to me!
Oh, but... I'm not too fond
of shitake mushrooms...
Next, please...
Oh, yes...
I-I'm Mime-- Mimi Hanyu.
My best wishes to all.
Why did you decide to take this audition?
Y-Yes... um, ur... uh...
You can talk slowly.
Just calm down...
I'm sorry... U-Um... er...
Thanks, that's enough.
I will announce the results of the first cuts.
Today, these 5 contestants will move on.
Only 5 will pass...
It's all but impossible...
Oh well, I just wanted to
catch a glimpse of Araki...
#251 .
You're kidding!
That's amazing!
#252.
Those accepted, please step forward.
We will have these people move
on to the second cuts tomorrow.
Now, as we informed you earlier,
the final winner of this audition...
...will be playing a role in a movie
slated for release next summer...
If... I get accepted tomorrow...
What should I do?
Maybe I can be accepted...
NO, I'm sure I will be!
I'm beautiful, I got the right curves...
I, Mimet, can't possibly
lose against HUMANS!
Mimet!
Oh, Professor, you came!
How nice of you!
Mimet...
Yes?
It seems you have a fever...
and your eyes are bloodshot...
Working hard is nice and all,
but be careful of your health.
I don't want to lose talented workers like you...
S-Sure.
That's right...
I had totally forgotten.
I'm supposed to steal Araki's pure heart!
But then, Araki would die...
My loving Araki is going to die...
How pitiful...
Maybe this audition really
doesn't have any effect...
...and my professional debut as well...
I see... If I don't attack Araki,
I'll end up being a traitor...
...just when I'm about to fill the
role of the highest executive...
I'm counting on you...
Humans just have to put
everything into things they love!
That's right! That's got to be it!
I don't care about the
Death Busters anymore!
I will burn the summer away along with Araki!
I can become a traitor to
a syndicate like this for Araki!
In the first place, I'm a good girl deep
down, who can't do anything evil!
Who will wear the crown of the heroine...?
Today, we will have the members
of the audience helping us decide.
The person that 80% of the audience
backs up is the winner of our audition.
Now, the first person, please!
Artemis!!
Oh, no, how did you know...
It's not like you, Mina...
to keep it a secret from everyone...
Well... it became rather hard for me to tell
them that I've been chasing after Araki...
Now, please push the switch!
Mm... how unfortunate!
Next, #68.
I'm after the next one.
If you get accepted...
Yeah!
An idol pretty soldier will be born!
That's pretty ama--
This morning, I had my favorite omelet.
In the future...
In the future, I would like
to become a big actress...
...a big actress who can handle any role...
I want to become an actress,
no matter what I do...
I want to be an actress...
We'll do our best...
How unfortunate.
Next, #251 ...
Okay!
#251 , Minako Aino.
I'm a 9th grader at Shiba Park
Junior High, in Minato ward.
It's a small world...
I give my best to you.
This was really close!
Then, next person please...
- Do it well.
- Y-Yeah...
Oh, man, the dream of
becoming an idol pretty soldier...
But I guess it's okay
because I got to see Araki.
I'm honored.
That was really close.
But another chance will come by soon.
Araki... I'll keep cheering for you forever...
Thanks.
But you will someday forget about me...
No, not just you.
Everyone will forget
about me at some point...
But that's all right.
Even if you forget about me...
...the feelings you felt for me will remain.
After they move on from idols,
girls take their feelings of love...
...and learn what real romance is about.
Araki...!
But for now, give me your full support.
I don't plan to end as just an idol, either.
T-This morning, I had my favorite omelet.
In the future, I would like to become a
big actress who can handle any role...
Thank you for your consideration.
This is our final challenger.
Please push the switch!
This is most unfortunate.
Unfortunately, we end this audition
with no one making the cuts...
Are you all right, Miss Hanyu?
Miss Hanyu?
I am Mimet of the Death Busters!
I applied for this audition to take the pure
heart of Jinta Araki standing right there!
Appear, Daimohn Utahime!
Utahime!
CHARM...
...BUSTER!
Everyone is shaken up by my charm!
They're in pain...
Utahime...!
Oh, sorry, they're shaken up, right.
Get to it!
Yes!
A-Araki...
MOON TIARA...
...ACTION!
What are you doing!?
That hurt!
You're the singer, and I'm the listener!
Songs are everyone's friends!
Bad guys who assault our idols!
We, fighters of love and justice...
...the Sailor Team...
...will punish you in the name of the moon!
Guys!
VENUS STAR POWER...
MAKE UP!
Mimet!
Pretending to be a chaser,
only to assault Araki...
You are the enemy to every fan!
Ally to every idol in the world...
Sailor Venus!
I'll have the divine punishment
of love fall upon you.
Shut up!
I wasn't pretending!
But I'm Mimet of the Witches 5!
Then, you really care about Araki...?
That's none of your business!
This way, Araki's heart... is ours forever!
Chasers have their own set of rules!
They're not supposed to cause trouble
to the idols that they chase! Sheesh!
Araki is going to die!
Geez! Of course!
The Death Busters is an evil syndicate!
Utahime! Kill all of them
with your killer songs!
Utahime!
What's wrong? Hurry up!
To get a perfect song,
please wait while I warm up my voice.
Hurry up!
KILLER SONG!
I forgot the lyrics...
W-What!?
N-Now, Sailor Moon!
Yeah!!
CRISIS...
MAKE UP!
RAINBOW...
...MOON...
...HEART ACHE!
I remember now...
L-Love is...
Love-Lovely!
T-This I can't...
VENUS LOVE ME CHAIN!
I'll get you for this!
They seem to be gathering pure hearts...
For what purpose now?
Pure hearts can become energy
for the ones who move the world.
Or, they have already found the evil one...
...the messiah of silence...
Here.
You return it, Venus.
You've been a fan since 7th grade, right?
I heard you've been chasing
after him all this time.
Amazing!
You blabbermouth!
I am terribly sorry.
I have failed.
I'm so frustrated!
I really am frustrated, Professor!
There is always tomorrow, Mimet...
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com